{
    "result": 0,
    "message": "Success",
    "payload": {
        "users": [
            {
                "_id": "6229eee48553e7ab6730c4d2",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a87768bfdc0428e7d466",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee48553e7ab6730c4d2",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f00c594dcace72f5c24",
                            "name": "Steven Pietras",
                            "email": "norgoth12@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-08-07T15:35:10.381Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "This is obviously a very delicate issues and you will have to tread carefully. Perhaps ask all employees, honestly and openly if they have any issues with the way oversight is handled and what can be done to improve it. These suggestions might highlight what aspects, specifically, they find hard to accept. Perhaps conversation style differances or differing previous work cultures may be partially to blame.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-11-29T17:51:34.287Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a87768bfdc0428e7d464",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "I am the hiring manager at a grocery store in a mostly black area. I brought in an outside hire to oversee the staff who is also a person of color who was hired on the strength of her resume and experience but is not black. My staff is having difficulty accepting her, and the new manager is having a hard time navigating the discontent. Has anyone had success dealing with this sort of delicate issue? Are there any team-building exercises that might be wise?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                    "name": "Daniel Daws",
                    "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                    "currentRole": "Founder"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-11-23T22:01:51.017Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee08553e7ab6730c498",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a85868bfdc0428e7d002",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee08553e7ab6730c498",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c413c594dcace72f5b03",
                            "name": "Arijit Basu",
                            "email": "arijitb962@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-04-21T07:34:56.909Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "hi",
                        "createdAt": "2021-10-12T06:21:27.747Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a85868bfdc0428e7d000",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "hello",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "62218f06c594dcace72f5c6a",
                    "name": "Irfan Irshad",
                    "email": "irfanirshadsal@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-09-30T22:36:41.129Z",
                    "currentRole": "Other"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-10-05T15:00:46.073Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6369fcb57bdc9c17d90c71f3",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6369fdd97bdc9c17d90c779e",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 1,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6369fdb97bdc9c17d90c7785",
                        "answer": "I went with my instinct and took that decision after evaluting everything ",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636905907bdc9c17d90be744",
                            "currentRole": "Co-Founder",
                            "email": "cooper@mailinator.com",
                            "name": "Cooper",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-07T13:18:08.656Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-08T06:07:46.456Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6369fcb57bdc9c17d90c71f3",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-08T06:57:29.667Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6369fe2f7bdc9c17d90c7a8c",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6369fdb97bdc9c17d90c7785",
                        "answer": "ok",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6369fb377bdc9c17d90c6e5d",
                            "currentRole": "Founder",
                            "email": "ajnish@mailinator.com",
                            "name": "Ajnish Rana",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-08T06:46:15.280Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-08T06:46:15.281Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6369fcb57bdc9c17d90c71f3",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-08T06:58:55.064Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Tell me about a tough decision you had to make recently at work , how did you go about making the decision?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6369fb377bdc9c17d90c6e5d",
                    "currentRole": "Founder",
                    "email": "ajnish@mailinator.com",
                    "name": "Ajnish Rana",
                    "createdAt": "2022-11-08T06:46:15.280Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-11-08T06:46:15.281Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-11-08T06:52:37.734Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eef18553e7ab6730c5a3",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a81068bfdc0428e7c59c",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef18553e7ab6730c5a3",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3fdc594dcace72f599b",
                            "name": "Alison Bagwell",
                            "email": "abagwell@shieldtecinc.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-01-11T15:43:43.206Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "Risk Analysis and Risk Mitigation Planning",
                        "createdAt": "2021-02-04T03:54:00.796Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a81068bfdc0428e7c59a",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How do you consider downstream consequences of your decisions?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3ecc594dcace72f58f8",
                    "name": "MollyDriscoll",
                    "email": "mdriscoll2@luc.edu",
                    "createdAt": "2020-10-07T01:12:14.277Z",
                    "currentRole": "CEO"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-02-04T01:02:39.903Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee08553e7ab6730c49c",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a87368bfdc0428e7d3cf",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee08553e7ab6730c49c",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f00c594dcace72f5c24",
                            "name": "Steven Pietras",
                            "email": "norgoth12@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-08-07T15:35:10.381Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Thanks for the advice! I've taken to talking with team members individually after conversations to ask them what they thought of my ideas and gage thier understanding. I feel like this has helped too.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-11-22T16:13:05.586Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a85968bfdc0428e7d032",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a85968bfdc0428e7d034",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee08553e7ab6730c49c",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f04c594dcace72f5c4e",
                            "name": "Iryna Chaban",
                            "email": "irynachaban98@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-09-07T19:20:12.002Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "Yes! Many people struggle with presenting their thoughts to an audience. But, I would say that it is something that disappears with growth and experience. When you start feeling that you are a valued member of your team and your input matters, it becomes a minor struggle.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-10-12T17:41:41.685Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a85968bfdc0428e7d032",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Does anyone else struggle communicating new ideas to a small team when speaking to them all at once?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "62218f00c594dcace72f5c24",
                    "name": "Steven Pietras",
                    "email": "norgoth12@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-08-07T15:35:10.381Z",
                    "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-10-11T15:59:33.373Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eef08553e7ab6730c599",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a81268bfdc0428e7c5e2",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef08553e7ab6730c599",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3fdc594dcace72f599b",
                            "name": "Alison Bagwell",
                            "email": "abagwell@shieldtecinc.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-01-11T15:43:43.206Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "I never let them see my frustration and bring energy to all meetings regardless of the outcome. Don't add to problem, Be the solution.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-02-04T04:11:20.343Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a81268bfdc0428e7c5e0",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How have you fostered workplace culture during the pandemic?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3ecc594dcace72f58f5",
                    "name": "Claire Beltmann",
                    "email": "cbeltmann@luc.edu",
                    "createdAt": "2020-10-20T20:34:37.140Z",
                    "currentRole": "Assistant Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-01-31T23:22:09.682Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eedb8553e7ab6730c453",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84068bfdc0428e7cc67",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedb8553e7ab6730c453",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c41cc594dcace72f5b95",
                            "name": "Alec Jiggins",
                            "email": "mralecjiggins@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-06-08T20:46:27.500Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "\"Only do what only you can do\"\nThat is the rule of entrepreneurs and CEOs.\nIf you are spending your time doing administrative tasks, that could be delegated, allowing you to focus on scaling your business, then that's what you should do. \nWhen I coach entrepreneurs, the biggest challenge is believing in themselves, their ideas, and their project. Entrepreneurs who succeed are those who build a team, delegate and motivate, allowing them to focus on business growth and development. \n",
                        "createdAt": "2021-06-22T12:20:12.892Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84068bfdc0428e7cc65",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84168bfdc0428e7cc94",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedb8553e7ab6730c453",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3f5c594dcace72f5919",
                            "name": "J. Mandell Carter",
                            "email": "j.m.carter2021@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2020-11-23T17:57:09.494Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "Perhaps that answer is more relative than definitive. You may find it better to ease into it depending on the nature of the business. I would suggest an assessment of the work load then research of the industry standard of what the FTE number should be. As a safety, perhaps if the standard for the load is 2 FTEs, start with one and increase when feasible.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-06-25T18:07:40.989Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84168bfdc0428e7cc92",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Director of Start-Up Companies....When is it the right time to consider taking on your first full-time employee, without external funding?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-06-16T15:48:55.690Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eedc8553e7ab6730c45f",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84868bfdc0428e7cd9a",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedc8553e7ab6730c45f",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                            "name": "Saima Omar",
                            "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Have you created a pitch deck?",
                        "createdAt": "2021-07-21T00:01:44.984Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84868bfdc0428e7cd98",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Does anyone in the UK have any tips for initial funding for a mental health care statup please?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c41fc594dcace72f5bba",
                    "name": "Dean Malpass",
                    "email": "deanmalpass@yahoo.co.uk",
                    "createdAt": "2021-06-24T18:54:58.017Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-07-03T09:11:23.301Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eef18553e7ab6730c5ac",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a81568bfdc0428e7c657",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef18553e7ab6730c5ac",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3f9c594dcace72f5961",
                            "name": "John Cruz",
                            "email": "johncruzrn@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2020-12-18T23:38:21.151Z",
                            "currentRole": "Manager"
                        },
                        "answer": "Closed-loop communications and effective use of health information tech through electronic health records that are interoperable.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-02-12T01:14:05.440Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a81568bfdc0428e7c655",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "What are some best practices for effective coordination of patient care?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3ecc594dcace72f58f5",
                    "name": "Claire Beltmann",
                    "email": "cbeltmann@luc.edu",
                    "createdAt": "2020-10-20T20:34:37.140Z",
                    "currentRole": "Assistant Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-02-08T17:01:48.147Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee38553e7ab6730c4c9",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a87268bfdc0428e7d3ad",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee38553e7ab6730c4c9",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                            "name": "Saima Omar",
                            "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Avenues you can use to find VC firms include:\nAccountants, lawyers, and bankers who work with your business.\nPitch and networking events that allow you to meet potential investors.\nBusiness incubators that provide services, advice, and resources to new business owners.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-11-22T16:05:43.640Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a87268bfdc0428e7d3ab",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "how do i find vcs to raise capital for my startup clients",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "62218f0ac594dcace72f5cb5",
                    "name": "amir hegazi",
                    "email": "amir@intomena.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-11-19T05:52:19.568Z",
                    "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-11-19T05:56:10.874Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee78553e7ab6730c4ff",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a89668bfdc0428e7d7c6",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee78553e7ab6730c4ff",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                            "name": "Saima Omar",
                            "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Asking how best you can support them and having an open and honest conversation about what you have noticed is the best way to go. Reinforcing the idea that you are not in any way, shape or form, reprimanding them, but, instead you are simply concerned about their well-being.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-08T01:33:14.737Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a89668bfdc0428e7d7c4",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8a768bfdc0428e7da43",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee78553e7ab6730c4ff",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "It's important to be objective about their performance and to highlight your concern for their well-being. Be sure to listen to what he or she says and repeat it back to them so they know you understand.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-03T16:43:07.324Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8a768bfdc0428e7da41",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a89768bfdc0428e7d7f3",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee78553e7ab6730c4ff",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3e6c594dcace72f589f",
                            "name": "John Parker",
                            "email": "jrparkny@aol.com",
                            "createdAt": "2022-01-10T01:23:08.367Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "I think you need to have a sit down with this person.  Show them it is for them you are concerned.  I always try to have some 1:1 relationship to my employees so that when these times come, and they do, we have a rapport already in place.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-10T01:32:57.405Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a89768bfdc0428e7d7f1",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a89568bfdc0428e7d78f",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee78553e7ab6730c4ff",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3f5c594dcace72f591c",
                            "name": "Jim Red",
                            "email": "rojjim@hotmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2020-11-25T21:44:54.463Z",
                            "currentRole": "Manager"
                        },
                        "answer": "Ask as if you would a family member or close friend.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-07T01:33:36.715Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a89568bfdc0428e7d78d",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "I've noticed that one of my top employees has not been performing well, lately (showing up late, missing deadlines, overall seeming down). How do I go about checking on their well-being, without making it seem like I'm reprimanding them or trying to pry?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c41dc594dcace72f5b9b",
                    "name": "Madeleine",
                    "email": "maddykindler11@yahoo.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-06-10T18:10:27.425Z",
                    "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-01-06T16:09:05.485Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 4
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee38553e7ab6730c4c8",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a87268bfdc0428e7d3b6",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee38553e7ab6730c4c8",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                            "name": "Saima Omar",
                            "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "You must remember, that taking time off work recharges your productivity and ability to perceive new directions. Vacation time also allows us to pursue other interests, an initiative many innovative companies encourage their employees to do during the work week in order to see what new solutions or ideas they might come up with that can be pooled into the organization’s directive. When it comes to good leadership practices, a common axiom that is shared is to “lead by example” – that you encourage the behaviours and commitments you’d like to see in your employees by exhibiting it first in your own actions. Hopefully you will use your given vacation time according to what your organization has planned and take leave when you know you are able to delegate responsibility accordingly.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-11-22T16:07:58.875Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a87268bfdc0428e7d3b4",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a87968bfdc0428e7d49f",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee38553e7ab6730c4c8",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3f5c594dcace72f591c",
                            "name": "Jim Red",
                            "email": "rojjim@hotmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2020-11-25T21:44:54.463Z",
                            "currentRole": "Manager"
                        },
                        "answer": "Schedule your vacations and stick to it. No \"decisions\" needed.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-12-01T00:53:28.661Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a87968bfdc0428e7d49d",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "I work for myself and have a hard time deciding when to take vacations. How do you decide when you are not cutting yourself enough slack?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c421c594dcace72f5be4",
                    "name": "Steven J. Pietras",
                    "email": "spietras43@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-07-13T15:28:46.788Z",
                    "currentRole": "Manager",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-29T15:36:07.160Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-11-18T14:39:08.348Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee48553e7ab6730c4cf",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a87368bfdc0428e7d3d8",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee48553e7ab6730c4cf",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f00c594dcace72f5c24",
                            "name": "Steven Pietras",
                            "email": "norgoth12@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-08-07T15:35:10.381Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "I personally have never sought out a co-founder. I feel like the main trade off would be risking the possibility your vision being diluted in exchange for having someone to infuse new ideas and help catch oversights.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-11-22T16:48:27.070Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a87368bfdc0428e7d3d6",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "I am a solo founder. Is it a good idea for me to look for a co-founder? What are the pros and cons to getting a co-founder?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-11-22T15:34:35.726Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee78553e7ab6730c4fb",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a89468bfdc0428e7d77a",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee78553e7ab6730c4fb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "They can be useful. It's nice to have an organized time to develop new plans and goals. However, it's easy to get lost in the catharsis of fantasizing about a better future, rather than exercising the steps to reach your target.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-05T17:20:12.326Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a89468bfdc0428e7d778",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a89768bfdc0428e7d7d8",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee78553e7ab6730c4fb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                            "name": "Saima Omar",
                            "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "As a leader, it's a good time of the year to think strategy. Thus, if you are not already breaking your year down into quarters and setting goals, then this time of the year is better than any other!",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-08T01:36:31.858Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a89768bfdc0428e7d7d6",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "What do you think of New Year's resolutions? Do you have any, or do you find them to not be that important?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c41dc594dcace72f5b9b",
                    "name": "Madeleine",
                    "email": "maddykindler11@yahoo.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-06-10T18:10:27.425Z",
                    "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-01-03T22:46:45.178Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee48553e7ab6730c4d6",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a88068bfdc0428e7d5b4",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee48553e7ab6730c4d6",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "It might be useful to meet any defensiveness by acknowledging the strengths they bring to the team. It could also be useful to frame your suggestions within the context of this employee's development and the company's goals and expectations.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-12-09T02:26:28.897Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a88068bfdc0428e7d5b2",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "I have an employee who always seems to get rather defensive when I make suggestions about improving their day-to-day performance. I honestly think they know themselves better than I do, but feel like my opinions might be helpful. How can I make it clear to them that I am offering a suggestion, not a critique?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "62218f00c594dcace72f5c24",
                    "name": "Steven Pietras",
                    "email": "norgoth12@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-08-07T15:35:10.381Z",
                    "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-11-29T17:07:38.898Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee68553e7ab6730c4ee",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8a868bfdc0428e7da67",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee68553e7ab6730c4ee",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "Asking this question is an important step. One great way that will also boost morale is to invite targeted feedback from your team.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-03T20:56:54.103Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8a768bfdc0428e7da65",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a89468bfdc0428e7d768",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee68553e7ab6730c4ee",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3ecc594dcace72f58f8",
                            "name": "MollyDriscoll",
                            "email": "mdriscoll2@luc.edu",
                            "createdAt": "2020-10-07T01:12:14.277Z",
                            "currentRole": "CEO"
                        },
                        "answer": "I find that reflection makes everyone better. You won't grow without evaluating your decisions and outcomes. Also, getting advice from others and reading the latest journals help me when I'm stuck.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-04T17:47:57.888Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a89468bfdc0428e7d766",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How do you continue to grow and develop as a leader?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-12-20T15:53:19.382Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee88553e7ab6730c508",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a89968bfdc0428e7d844",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee88553e7ab6730c508",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "It sounds like you need to speak to him privately about what you're perceiving and see if he has any alternative thoughts on what's happening. From there you might be able to find grounds for a resolution.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-13T00:40:46.207Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a89968bfdc0428e7d842",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "I have someone on my team that has a problem with every decision I make because \"I'm a millennial\". He adds value to the team but can't seem to accept me as the leader. What can I do about this?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3ecc594dcace72f58f8",
                    "name": "MollyDriscoll",
                    "email": "mdriscoll2@luc.edu",
                    "createdAt": "2020-10-07T01:12:14.277Z",
                    "currentRole": "CEO"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-01-09T18:20:37.693Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eef38553e7ab6730c5d4",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a83768bfdc0428e7cb19",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef38553e7ab6730c5d4",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c416c594dcace72f5b31",
                            "name": "Todd Harrison",
                            "email": "todd.harrison@deltafaucet.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-04-30T11:58:30.420Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Our organization is in its infancy in data analytics and insights, but we are started by orienting leaders at every level on what it is and what tools are available. Our internal analytics experts then work with each leader on a self-determined project to show them how to use the tools and technologies available to gain new insights for making better daily decisions. Involving leaders in the process around data that is meaningful to them has been the key to behavior change.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-04-30T12:30:04.265Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a83768bfdc0428e7cb17",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Wondering what other organizations are doing to build data analytic capability for the future?  Our organization is very sophisticated in terms of what we offer our clients (i.e., spss and advanced statistics with the ability to develop a story around the data) but when it comes to our internal focus there is room for growth (i.e., we use excel pivot tables and means with difficulty building a story around the data).  Curios to know how other organizations are building this capability internally.",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c405c594dcace72f5a20",
                    "name": "Beth Linderbaum",
                    "email": "beth.linderbaum@right.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-08T01:47:03.464Z",
                    "currentRole": "Vice President"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-03-25T13:45:11.561Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee78553e7ab6730c501",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8a668bfdc0428e7da1f",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee78553e7ab6730c501",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "If you're unsure of how to combine the cultures of the two companies and they'll need to be unified, then yes, probably you should.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-03T16:13:04.314Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8a668bfdc0428e7da1d",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "I have made the decision of acquiring a competitor company. Is it recommended that I hire a Change Management Consultant to make the process of aligning two separate companies into one, easier, and streamline processes?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-01-07T14:06:27.828Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeed8553e7ab6730c55b",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8b768bfdc0428e7dcc4",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeed8553e7ab6730c55b",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3e6c594dcace72f58aa",
                            "name": "Amarachi Emezie",
                            "email": "amarachieemezie@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2022-01-12T18:41:13.277Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-05-09T15:13:09.331Z",
                            "currentRole": "Other"
                        },
                        "answer": "Leadership is huge. Having an established leader who is there to assign roles and interact with employees can lead to employees willing to ask more questions and ultimately enhance work environment.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-22T06:35:29.176Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8b768bfdc0428e7dcc2",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How much does leadership impact employee engagement?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3e8c594dcace72f58c9",
                    "name": "Nina Blackmon",
                    "email": "ninasblackmon@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2022-02-08T19:19:31.120Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-05-05T17:43:54.724Z",
                    "currentRole": "Other"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-02-22T00:10:50.188Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f0775ab7d43ebe61af82",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f06b5ab7d43ebe61af46",
                        "answer": "1980",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "628e0f5c942ead2b0d942d26",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "xacivel676@lockaya.com",
                            "name": "xacivel",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-25T11:13:32.977Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-28T09:16:59.974Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T10:39:51.274Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f1345ab7d43ebe61b126",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f06b5ab7d43ebe61af46",
                        "answer": "dfdf",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "628e0f5c942ead2b0d942d26",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "xacivel676@lockaya.com",
                            "name": "xacivel",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-25T11:13:32.977Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-28T09:16:59.974Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T10:43:00.748Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f2c96e3a230c54ed4e82",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f06b5ab7d43ebe61af46",
                        "answer": "sdsd",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "628e0f5c942ead2b0d942d26",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "xacivel676@lockaya.com",
                            "name": "xacivel",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-25T11:13:32.977Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-28T09:16:59.974Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T10:49:45.116Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f2d56e3a230c54ed4ec2",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f06b5ab7d43ebe61af46",
                        "answer": "sdsd",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "628e0f5c942ead2b0d942d26",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "xacivel676@lockaya.com",
                            "name": "xacivel",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-25T11:13:32.977Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-28T09:16:59.974Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T10:49:57.362Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f31c6e3a230c54ed4f00",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f06b5ab7d43ebe61af46",
                        "answer": "567",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "628e0f5c942ead2b0d942d26",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "xacivel676@lockaya.com",
                            "name": "xacivel",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-25T11:13:32.977Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-28T09:16:59.974Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T10:51:08.496Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f3306e3a230c54ed4f58",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f06b5ab7d43ebe61af46",
                        "answer": "uyu",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "628e0f5c942ead2b0d942d26",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "xacivel676@lockaya.com",
                            "name": "xacivel",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-25T11:13:32.977Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-28T09:16:59.974Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T10:51:28.586Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f375674f811e304ba2bf",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f06b5ab7d43ebe61af46",
                        "answer": "bvmnvbm",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "628e0f5c942ead2b0d942d26",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "xacivel676@lockaya.com",
                            "name": "xacivel",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-25T11:13:32.977Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-28T09:16:59.974Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T10:52:37.559Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f3fda83e7a1220d40946",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f06b5ab7d43ebe61af46",
                        "answer": "cvbcv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "628e0f5c942ead2b0d942d26",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "xacivel676@lockaya.com",
                            "name": "xacivel",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-25T11:13:32.977Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-28T09:16:59.974Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T10:54:53.104Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f3ffa83e7a1220d40967",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f06b5ab7d43ebe61af46",
                        "answer": "ccv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "628e0f5c942ead2b0d942d26",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "xacivel676@lockaya.com",
                            "name": "xacivel",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-25T11:13:32.977Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-28T09:16:59.974Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T10:54:55.483Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f45f88d60b1a04deaf75",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f06b5ab7d43ebe61af46",
                        "answer": "ffhghfg",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "628e0f5c942ead2b0d942d26",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "xacivel676@lockaya.com",
                            "name": "xacivel",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-25T11:13:32.977Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-28T09:16:59.974Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T10:56:31.557Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f491a4055e1bccfd729b",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f06b5ab7d43ebe61af46",
                        "answer": "xcvbcvc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "628e0f5c942ead2b0d942d26",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "xacivel676@lockaya.com",
                            "name": "xacivel",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-25T11:13:32.977Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-28T09:16:59.974Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T10:57:21.024Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f491a4055e1bccfd72bf",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f06b5ab7d43ebe61af46",
                        "answer": "cvbcv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "628e0f5c942ead2b0d942d26",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "xacivel676@lockaya.com",
                            "name": "xacivel",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-25T11:13:32.977Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-28T09:16:59.974Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T10:57:21.910Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f492a4055e1bccfd72f3",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f06b5ab7d43ebe61af46",
                        "answer": "cvbc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "628e0f5c942ead2b0d942d26",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "xacivel676@lockaya.com",
                            "name": "xacivel",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-25T11:13:32.977Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-28T09:16:59.974Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T10:57:22.503Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f493a4055e1bccfd7328",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f06b5ab7d43ebe61af46",
                        "answer": "cvbcv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "628e0f5c942ead2b0d942d26",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "xacivel676@lockaya.com",
                            "name": "xacivel",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-25T11:13:32.977Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-28T09:16:59.974Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T10:57:23.020Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f493a4055e1bccfd7364",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f06b5ab7d43ebe61af46",
                        "answer": "cvvbcv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "628e0f5c942ead2b0d942d26",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "xacivel676@lockaya.com",
                            "name": "xacivel",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-25T11:13:32.977Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-28T09:16:59.974Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T10:57:23.505Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f494a4055e1bccfd738f",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f06b5ab7d43ebe61af46",
                        "answer": "cvvbc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "628e0f5c942ead2b0d942d26",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "xacivel676@lockaya.com",
                            "name": "xacivel",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-25T11:13:32.977Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-28T09:16:59.974Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T10:57:24.069Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f494a4055e1bccfd73c3",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f06b5ab7d43ebe61af46",
                        "answer": "cvbc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "628e0f5c942ead2b0d942d26",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "xacivel676@lockaya.com",
                            "name": "xacivel",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-25T11:13:32.977Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-28T09:16:59.974Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T10:57:24.361Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f495a4055e1bccfd73f5",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f06b5ab7d43ebe61af46",
                        "answer": "cvbcv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "628e0f5c942ead2b0d942d26",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "xacivel676@lockaya.com",
                            "name": "xacivel",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-25T11:13:32.977Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-28T09:16:59.974Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T10:57:25.119Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f495a4055e1bccfd7427",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f06b5ab7d43ebe61af46",
                        "answer": "cvbvcb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "628e0f5c942ead2b0d942d26",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "xacivel676@lockaya.com",
                            "name": "xacivel",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-25T11:13:32.977Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-28T09:16:59.974Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T10:57:25.450Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f496a4055e1bccfd7469",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f06b5ab7d43ebe61af46",
                        "answer": "cvbcv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "628e0f5c942ead2b0d942d26",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "xacivel676@lockaya.com",
                            "name": "xacivel",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-25T11:13:32.977Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-28T09:16:59.974Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T10:57:26.199Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f496a4055e1bccfd7498",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f06b5ab7d43ebe61af46",
                        "answer": "cvbvc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "628e0f5c942ead2b0d942d26",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "xacivel676@lockaya.com",
                            "name": "xacivel",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-25T11:13:32.977Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-28T09:16:59.974Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T10:57:26.456Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f4ffa4055e1bccfd7581",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f4fca4055e1bccfd755e",
                        "answer": "fhgfhfggf",
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T10:59:11.606Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f501a4055e1bccfd75c2",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f4fca4055e1bccfd755e",
                        "answer": "fghgf",
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T10:59:13.383Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f52f95b69b1eecb12586",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f4fca4055e1bccfd755e",
                        "answer": "nvgnvbhnvbnvb",
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T10:59:59.951Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f53095b69b1eecb125a4",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f4fca4055e1bccfd755e",
                        "answer": "nvb",
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T11:00:00.412Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f53095b69b1eecb125b6",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f4fca4055e1bccfd755e",
                        "answer": "nvbbvn",
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T11:00:00.546Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f53095b69b1eecb125fd",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f4fca4055e1bccfd755e",
                        "answer": "bvnvbn",
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T11:00:00.989Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f53195b69b1eecb12622",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f4fca4055e1bccfd755e",
                        "answer": "vb",
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T11:00:01.247Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f5bc9695b22628c5641a",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f4fca4055e1bccfd755e",
                        "answer": "cvnvnvb",
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T11:02:20.165Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f5bf9695b22628c5645b",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f4fca4055e1bccfd755e",
                        "answer": "vbnvbnbbv",
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T11:02:23.649Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f5c29695b22628c5649a",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f4fca4055e1bccfd755e",
                        "answer": "nvbnbv",
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T11:02:26.603Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f5e2eff24f0f84082a11",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f4fca4055e1bccfd755e",
                        "answer": "cxbcbvbcvbv",
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T11:02:58.980Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f61b5ab7d43ebe61b6eb",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f06b5ab7d43ebe61af46",
                        "answer": "iililil",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "628e0f5c942ead2b0d942d26",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "xacivel676@lockaya.com",
                            "name": "xacivel",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-25T11:13:32.977Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-28T09:16:59.974Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T11:03:55.461Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f628b79a16202049869c",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f4fca4055e1bccfd755e",
                        "answer": "bcvbcvbcv",
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T11:04:08.341Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f6315ab7d43ebe61b75e",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f06b5ab7d43ebe61af46",
                        "answer": "yuyuyu",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "628e0f5c942ead2b0d942d26",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "xacivel676@lockaya.com",
                            "name": "xacivel",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-25T11:13:32.977Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-28T09:16:59.974Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T11:04:17.460Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f64611482711b8adddd0",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f4fca4055e1bccfd755e",
                        "answer": "cvnbvnvv",
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T11:04:38.904Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f76b11482711b8adde11",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f4fca4055e1bccfd755e",
                        "answer": "cbcv",
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T11:09:31.238Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f79411482711b8adde52",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f4fca4055e1bccfd755e",
                        "answer": "vnvbnvb",
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T11:10:12.342Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f7b511482711b8adde91",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f4fca4055e1bccfd755e",
                        "answer": "bcvbvcb",
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T11:10:45.656Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f7eddabed83b7c31ebfd",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f4fca4055e1bccfd755e",
                        "answer": "cvnvb",
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T11:11:41.882Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f82651171c2b188193c0",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f4fca4055e1bccfd755e",
                        "answer": "bcv",
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T11:12:38.927Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f89b8f7a152c8418bc07",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f4fca4055e1bccfd755e",
                        "answer": "nbv",
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T11:14:35.514Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f8bf873d5723a08c9d94",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f4fca4055e1bccfd755e",
                        "answer": "vbnbmb",
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T11:15:11.552Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f8cc5ab7d43ebe61b84e",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f06b5ab7d43ebe61af46",
                        "answer": "sdsd",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "628e0f5c942ead2b0d942d26",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "xacivel676@lockaya.com",
                            "name": "xacivel",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-25T11:13:32.977Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-28T09:16:59.974Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T11:15:24.353Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f8d45ab7d43ebe61b87b",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f06b5ab7d43ebe61af46",
                        "answer": "hello",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "628e0f5c942ead2b0d942d26",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "xacivel676@lockaya.com",
                            "name": "xacivel",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-25T11:13:32.977Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-28T09:16:59.974Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T11:15:32.159Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f8e6873d5723a08c9dd0",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f4fca4055e1bccfd755e",
                        "answer": "gfhgf",
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T11:15:50.699Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f8f6873d5723a08c9e11",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f4fca4055e1bccfd755e",
                        "answer": "vcbcv",
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T11:16:06.806Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295f908873d5723a08c9e52",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f4fca4055e1bccfd755e",
                        "answer": "nvb",
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T11:16:24.208Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295fcf75ab7d43ebe61bb5e",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295f06b5ab7d43ebe61af46",
                        "answer": "djbfjdf",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "628e0f5c942ead2b0d942d26",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "xacivel676@lockaya.com",
                            "name": "xacivel",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-25T11:13:32.977Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-28T09:16:59.974Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T11:33:11.544Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6299d8e036b309680ffe0b0d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6299d8dc36b309680ffe0af0",
                        "answer": "i dont know",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6284ce1afa4fe26e531732ab",
                            "currentRole": "Founder",
                            "email": "ligedov825@akapple.com",
                            "name": "Lige",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-18T10:44:42.887Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-03T12:51:10.092Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-06-03T09:48:16.876Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "629a03cbe8a1397ddb9559cb",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6299d8dc36b309680ffe0af0",
                        "answer": "kfngfnkg",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6284ce1afa4fe26e531732ab",
                            "currentRole": "Founder",
                            "email": "ligedov825@akapple.com",
                            "name": "Lige",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-18T10:44:42.887Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-03T12:51:10.092Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-06-03T12:51:23.173Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "629a03dfe8a1397ddb955a1c",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6299d8dc36b309680ffe0af0",
                        "answer": "hello",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6284ce1afa4fe26e531732ab",
                            "currentRole": "Founder",
                            "email": "ligedov825@akapple.com",
                            "name": "Lige",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-18T10:44:42.887Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-03T12:51:10.092Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-06-03T12:51:43.173Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "629a04ddce786646c46c3600",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6299d8dc36b309680ffe0af0",
                        "answer": "bv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6284ce1afa4fe26e531732ab",
                            "currentRole": "Founder",
                            "email": "ligedov825@akapple.com",
                            "name": "Lige",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-18T10:44:42.887Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-03T12:51:10.092Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-06-03T12:55:57.125Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "629a056b73fa9e200c779769",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6299d8dc36b309680ffe0af0",
                        "answer": "cbcvbcv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6284ce1afa4fe26e531732ab",
                            "currentRole": "Founder",
                            "email": "ligedov825@akapple.com",
                            "name": "Lige",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-18T10:44:42.887Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-03T12:51:10.092Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-06-03T12:58:19.954Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "629a057073fa9e200c7797a8",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6299d8dc36b309680ffe0af0",
                        "answer": "vbvcbvcccbcvbc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6284ce1afa4fe26e531732ab",
                            "currentRole": "Founder",
                            "email": "ligedov825@akapple.com",
                            "name": "Lige",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-18T10:44:42.887Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-03T12:51:10.092Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-06-03T12:58:24.628Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "62bad2c8f6ac59655dddf4db",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "62a77def97dd855eaa0f75a5",
                        "answer": "hello",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "624d5ba9d500ad509757879c",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer",
                            "email": "tehav55741@nuesond.com",
                            "name": "Tehav",
                            "createdAt": "2022-04-06T09:21:45.077Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-10-10T04:11:45.916Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-06-28T10:07:04.473Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "62bad3a1f6ac59655dddf580",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "62a77def97dd855eaa0f75a5",
                        "answer": "check link for amazon.com\n",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "624d5ba9d500ad509757879c",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer",
                            "email": "tehav55741@nuesond.com",
                            "name": "Tehav",
                            "createdAt": "2022-04-06T09:21:45.077Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-10-10T04:11:45.916Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-06-28T10:10:41.355Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "62bad3b4f6ac59655dddf5d0",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "62a77def97dd855eaa0f75a5",
                        "answer": "www.amazon.com",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "624d5ba9d500ad509757879c",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer",
                            "email": "tehav55741@nuesond.com",
                            "name": "Tehav",
                            "createdAt": "2022-04-06T09:21:45.077Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-10-10T04:11:45.916Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-06-28T10:11:00.196Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "62bad3daf6ac59655dddf698",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "62a77def97dd855eaa0f75a5",
                        "answer": "check Link for www.amazon.com",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "624d5ba9d500ad509757879c",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer",
                            "email": "tehav55741@nuesond.com",
                            "name": "Tehav",
                            "createdAt": "2022-04-06T09:21:45.077Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-10-10T04:11:45.916Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-06-28T10:11:38.057Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "62bc1cd4f6ac59655ddeb3fd",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "62baee95f6ac59655dde2386",
                        "answer": "hello",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "624d5ba9d500ad509757879c",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer",
                            "email": "tehav55741@nuesond.com",
                            "name": "Tehav",
                            "createdAt": "2022-04-06T09:21:45.077Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-10-10T04:11:45.916Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6295f05e6e3a230c54ed4a87",
                        "createdAt": "2022-06-29T09:35:16.975Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "In which decade was the American Institute of Ec Eng. Founded?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "624d5ba9d500ad509757879c",
                    "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer",
                    "email": "tehav55741@nuesond.com",
                    "name": "Tehav",
                    "createdAt": "2022-04-06T09:21:45.077Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-10-10T04:11:45.916Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-05-31T10:39:26.212Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 60
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee58553e7ab6730c4e1",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a87e68bfdc0428e7d56c",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee58553e7ab6730c4e1",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "Thanks for your response. There are several jobs I am wanting to apply for that deal with external affairs, so I'm trying to get up to speed on alderman-political-organizational dynamics and what I need to know from an HR standpoint.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-12-07T19:49:42.213Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a87d68bfdc0428e7d53b",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a87d68bfdc0428e7d53d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee58553e7ab6730c4e1",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c417c594dcace72f5b45",
                            "name": "Scott Kuperman",
                            "email": "scott.kuperman@paintplatoon.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-05-04T18:23:00.565Z",
                            "currentRole": "President",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T16:24:41.811Z"
                        },
                        "answer": "I'm from Chicago. Are you asking to get a grasp on alderman network to gain a grasp on politics, orient yourself to the city or to help you with HR? Each would probably require a different answer.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-12-07T03:52:50.295Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a87d68bfdc0428e7d53b",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "I'm an HR professional who just moved to St. Louis from Chicago and am trying to get a grasp on the alderman network. Are there any clear resources for orienting myself?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                    "name": "Daniel Daws",
                    "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                    "currentRole": "Founder"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-12-06T17:49:57.854Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eef08553e7ab6730c58e",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231928b1a063710a820ab3e",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef08553e7ab6730c58e",
                        "answer": "2022",
                        "createdAt": "2021-01-11T08:23:06.360Z",
                        "roomId": "6231928b1a063710a820ab3c",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a80b68bfdc0428e7c4ef",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef08553e7ab6730c58e",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3fdc594dcace72f599f",
                            "name": "Test 30",
                            "email": "test30@inscriptio.in",
                            "createdAt": "2021-01-13T06:23:05.122Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "soon enough ",
                        "createdAt": "2021-01-13T09:20:09.080Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a80b68bfdc0428e7c4ed",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "When all people will get vaccination for covid19",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3fcc594dcace72f5986",
                    "name": "Hema P H",
                    "email": "hema.vayuz@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-01-06T10:14:53.946Z",
                    "currentRole": "Manager"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-01-06T11:40:46.791Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeeb8553e7ab6730c537",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8ac68bfdc0428e7db18",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeeb8553e7ab6730c537",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "If you have open lines of communication in the workplace, it's often best to address your thoughts to whoever your opinion will have the most relevance. However, if you're not sure, it might be wise to schedule some time with your group leader and your superior so that you can all discuss openly what you're thinking!",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-09T18:11:42.840Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8ac68bfdc0428e7db16",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8b868bfdc0428e7dce8",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeeb8553e7ab6730c537",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3e6c594dcace72f58a1",
                            "name": "Srijal",
                            "email": "srijalsharma01@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2022-01-10T12:30:06.951Z",
                            "currentRole": "Manager"
                        },
                        "answer": "agreed",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-23T12:30:24.501Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8ab68bfdc0428e7daf2",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Is it important that you should be open about your opinions with you Group leader or you should just wait to pass it your superior and hope he/she passes to your leader?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3e6c594dcace72f58a1",
                    "name": "Srijal",
                    "email": "srijalsharma01@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2022-01-10T12:30:06.951Z",
                    "currentRole": "Manager"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-02-07T13:03:21.534Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeec8553e7ab6730c548",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8b468bfdc0428e7dc48",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeec8553e7ab6730c548",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3e5c594dcace72f5893",
                            "name": "Firzana",
                            "email": "firzana218@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-12-29T20:45:55.686Z",
                            "currentRole": "Other"
                        },
                        "answer": "People can sometimes underestimate the power of marketing and really targeting the specific demographic group that your product satisfies a need for. Your product can be amazing in your eyes but you need to tactfully ensure that the need for your product is very clear at first glance.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-16T14:40:31.987Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8b468bfdc0428e7dc46",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8b368bfdc0428e7dc2d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeec8553e7ab6730c548",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c41dc594dcace72f5b9b",
                            "name": "Madeleine",
                            "email": "maddykindler11@yahoo.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-06-10T18:10:27.425Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "while the value of your app might be clear to those that are using it, I would not underestimate the importance of getting this value proposition out to your intended audience in the first place. If you are not communicating the value of your app out to the public and inviting them to use it, it is likely that your app will not gain the traction it needs",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-15T20:59:24.130Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8b368bfdc0428e7dc2b",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "My team and I have developed an app that we think speaks to its own value, but we're having trouble gaining traction. Am I being arrogant thinking that our product should speak for itself?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                    "name": "Daniel Daws",
                    "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                    "currentRole": "Founder"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-02-15T16:58:56.185Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eedf8553e7ab6730c486",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a85168bfdc0428e7cf08",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedf8553e7ab6730c486",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f00c594dcace72f5c24",
                            "name": "Steven Pietras",
                            "email": "norgoth12@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-08-07T15:35:10.381Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "test",
                        "createdAt": "2021-09-21T19:28:52.163Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a85168bfdc0428e7cf06",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "THIS IS A TEST POST.",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c421c594dcace72f5be4",
                    "name": "Steven J. Pietras",
                    "email": "spietras43@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-07-13T15:28:46.788Z",
                    "currentRole": "Manager",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-29T15:36:07.160Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-09-21T19:26:56.835Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee78553e7ab6730c503",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a89a68bfdc0428e7d856",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee78553e7ab6730c503",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "First, identify the areas where you're most uncertain, then we can begin to talk.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-13T00:43:32.195Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a89a68bfdc0428e7d854",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "I have recently been promoted to COO of my company. I feel like I am 'winging it' - and not very prepared to do this role justice. I don't want to admit this to my internal peers. How can I improve my confidence and competency for this role?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-01-07T14:10:23.445Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eedd8553e7ab6730c46c",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "62e0d6d50901f7178891ff3a",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "rating": 1,
                        "upVote": 1,
                        "downVote": 0,
                        "roomId": "62e0d69d0901f7178891fed5",
                        "answer": "Accounting is the process of recording financial transactions pertaining to a business. The accounting process includes summarizing, analyzing, and reporting these transactions to oversight agencies, regulators, and tax collection entities.",
                        "question": "6229eedd8553e7ab6730c46c",
                        "createdAt": "2022-07-27T06:10:29.918Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "What is Accouting ?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "62218f01c594dcace72f5c2d",
                    "name": "Harshit Bhargav",
                    "email": "harshitbhargav627@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-08-11T15:34:24.342Z",
                    "currentRole": "Associate Vice President"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-08-11T15:43:00.168Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee88553e7ab6730c509",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a89968bfdc0428e7d834",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee88553e7ab6730c509",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "You might invite them to do so specifically. But rather than open up a broad range for criticism, if you can identify a key area or two where you'd like feedback and invite your team to speak on that in one-on-ones, you'll likely find people start to open up as they discover it's safe.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-13T00:39:10.590Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a89968bfdc0428e7d832",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "As a leader, how can I demonstrate to my team that I am not only willing but find it extremely important that I receive and take criticism? It is starting to feel like most of my employees don't think that they should be criticizing me in any way, but that is not the example I want to be putting out. Constructive criticism is important at all levels, but I am unsure how to communicate this to my team.",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c41dc594dcace72f5b9b",
                    "name": "Madeleine",
                    "email": "maddykindler11@yahoo.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-06-10T18:10:27.425Z",
                    "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-01-10T17:53:12.492Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeda8553e7ab6730c43e",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a83568bfdc0428e7cadf",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeda8553e7ab6730c43e",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c416c594dcace72f5b31",
                            "name": "Todd Harrison",
                            "email": "todd.harrison@deltafaucet.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-04-30T11:58:30.420Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "If this question is about delivering the feedback to the leader, then I would say the individual leader needs to read and reflect on the results of the feedback, identify the areas where they are most effective as well as the areas where they could be even more effective, then they should meet with their direct manager to jointly develop a plan for leveraging their strengths and further developing areas that are critical to the leader's ongoing success. The results must be owned by the leader and supporting by their manager.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-04-30T12:12:13.845Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a83568bfdc0428e7cadd",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84068bfdc0428e7cc70",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeda8553e7ab6730c43e",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c41cc594dcace72f5b95",
                            "name": "Alec Jiggins",
                            "email": "mralecjiggins@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-06-08T20:46:27.500Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "If you can, hire a leadership coach and they can manage both the feedback and the coaching to help the leader improve.\nI am an Associate with a global coaching company, we work with Fortune 500 companies through to SME and startups.\nA 360 in itself is only part of the process. Behavioural interviews, identifying blindspots, and developing a coaching improvement plan are all essential to improve leadership behaviours. ",
                        "createdAt": "2021-06-22T12:23:01.455Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84068bfdc0428e7cc6e",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How to manage a 360 Degree feedback report of a Leader ?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c40dc594dcace72f5a9f",
                    "name": "Sunil Deshmukh",
                    "email": "sd@sunil-deshmukh.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-04-02T04:17:25.511Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-04-23T06:41:06.545Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "636e1dd873b0c95328c1d1bf",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "636f78f341830c7233cb072d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 1,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "636f758e41830c7233cb03bb",
                        "answer": "hello",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b6ecb7a3ce63a87b809a1",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer",
                            "email": "vijay74@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:11:39.718Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-25T08:54:15.709Z"
                        },
                        "question": "636e1dd873b0c95328c1d1bf",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-12T10:44:03.927Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "636f78f441830c7233cb0731",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 1,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "636f758e41830c7233cb03bb",
                        "answer": "hello",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b6ecb7a3ce63a87b809a1",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer",
                            "email": "vijay74@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:11:39.718Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-25T08:54:15.709Z"
                        },
                        "question": "636e1dd873b0c95328c1d1bf",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-12T10:44:04.174Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "636f796a41830c7233cb07ff",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 1,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "636f758e41830c7233cb03bb",
                        "answer": "abc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b6ecb7a3ce63a87b809a1",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer",
                            "email": "vijay74@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:11:39.718Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-25T08:54:15.709Z"
                        },
                        "question": "636e1dd873b0c95328c1d1bf",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-12T10:46:02.931Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6377431cb9947d5834ca932f",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63774301b9947d5834ca9318",
                        "answer": "unable to find data from sources",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637652cbb9947d5834ca63eb",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer",
                            "email": "virat@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "VIRAT",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-17T15:27:07.215Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-21T12:05:15.876Z"
                        },
                        "question": "636e1dd873b0c95328c1d1bf",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-18T08:32:28.325Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "What are the challenges we face while carrying out Market Research?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "636dd6f273b0c95328c1ab19",
                    "currentRole": "Assistant Director",
                    "email": "william@yopmail.com",
                    "name": "William",
                    "createdAt": "2022-11-11T05:00:34.548Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-11-15T05:45:08.329Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-11-11T10:03:04.646Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 4
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eef08553e7ab6730c58d",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a80b68bfdc0428e7c4e6",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef08553e7ab6730c58d",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3fdc594dcace72f599f",
                            "name": "Test 30",
                            "email": "test30@inscriptio.in",
                            "createdAt": "2021-01-13T06:23:05.122Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "affected",
                        "createdAt": "2021-01-13T09:10:24.302Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a80b68bfdc0428e7c4e4",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How the pandemic affected your career",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3fcc594dcace72f5986",
                    "name": "Hema P H",
                    "email": "hema.vayuz@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-01-06T10:14:53.946Z",
                    "currentRole": "Manager"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-01-06T11:19:43.073Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eef18553e7ab6730c5a0",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a81068bfdc0428e7c5b1",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef18553e7ab6730c5a0",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3fdc594dcace72f599b",
                            "name": "Alison Bagwell",
                            "email": "abagwell@shieldtecinc.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-01-11T15:43:43.206Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "Allow ownership in decision making but also with ownership comes accountability. Holding people accountable is the only way they can grow from success and from mistakes. You can't allow them to only accept their successes but not own their failures as well.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-02-04T04:00:05.968Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a81068bfdc0428e7c5af",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "What strategies do you have for maintaining accountability in your organization?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3ecc594dcace72f58f5",
                    "name": "Claire Beltmann",
                    "email": "cbeltmann@luc.edu",
                    "createdAt": "2020-10-20T20:34:37.140Z",
                    "currentRole": "Assistant Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-02-02T22:58:10.923Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eef08553e7ab6730c594",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231928a1a063710a820ab06",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef08553e7ab6730c594",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3fac594dcace72f5963",
                            "name": "V Boss",
                            "email": "cyp@inscriptio.in",
                            "createdAt": "2020-12-21T05:09:58.438Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "yes",
                        "createdAt": "2021-01-11T07:31:26.852Z",
                        "roomId": "6231928a1a063710a820ab04",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231928b1a063710a820ab2e",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef08553e7ab6730c594",
                        "answer": "yes",
                        "createdAt": "2021-01-11T08:18:48.047Z",
                        "roomId": "6231928b1a063710a820ab2c",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a80c68bfdc0428e7c508",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef08553e7ab6730c594",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3fec594dcace72f59a2",
                            "name": "Sam Matta",
                            "email": "daktermatta@hotmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-01-13T18:14:15.852Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Absolutely",
                        "createdAt": "2021-01-13T18:36:31.727Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a80c68bfdc0428e7c506",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a80d68bfdc0428e7c546",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef08553e7ab6730c594",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3f5c594dcace72f591c",
                            "name": "Jim Red",
                            "email": "rojjim@hotmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2020-11-25T21:44:54.463Z",
                            "currentRole": "Manager"
                        },
                        "answer": "Yes",
                        "createdAt": "2021-01-27T06:50:55.127Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a80d68bfdc0428e7c544",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a81268bfdc0428e7c5fc",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef08553e7ab6730c594",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3fdc594dcace72f599b",
                            "name": "Alison Bagwell",
                            "email": "abagwell@shieldtecinc.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-01-11T15:43:43.206Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "Yes, always a firm believer in science.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-02-04T04:12:57.041Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a81268bfdc0428e7c5fa",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a80a68bfdc0428e7c4d4",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef08553e7ab6730c594",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3fdc594dcace72f599f",
                            "name": "Test 30",
                            "email": "test30@inscriptio.in",
                            "createdAt": "2021-01-13T06:23:05.122Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Yes",
                        "createdAt": "2021-01-13T08:56:14.326Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a80a68bfdc0428e7c4d2",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a82b68bfdc0428e7c988",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef08553e7ab6730c594",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c411c594dcace72f5ae2",
                            "name": "Devin Marks",
                            "email": "devin.ridleymarks@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-04-16T02:36:55.760Z",
                            "currentRole": "President"
                        },
                        "answer": "Done. Pfizer.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-04-17T01:45:33.006Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a82b68bfdc0428e7c986",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231928b1a063710a820ab35",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef08553e7ab6730c594",
                        "answer": "yes",
                        "createdAt": "2021-01-11T08:19:46.673Z",
                        "roomId": "6231928b1a063710a820ab2c",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Will you take the COVID-19 vaccine?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3fcc594dcace72f5989",
                    "name": "Geoffrey Lau",
                    "email": "dr.geoffrey.lau@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-01-07T12:08:27.506Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-01-07T12:21:55.881Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 8
            },
            {
                "_id": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "637f11cc7b05b546b09123c2",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "hii",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T06:40:12.320Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380819e02a84429d8f77cc7",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "bnvb\n",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T08:49:34.288Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63808e0a448dda0ac07f37ff",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "bnbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T09:42:34.626Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63808e22448dda0ac07f3854",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "vbnbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T09:42:58.353Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63808e2d448dda0ac07f3887",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "vcbcv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T09:43:09.602Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638094e5448dda0ac07f3b62",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "vbnvbnbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T10:11:49.467Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63809615448dda0ac07f3c29",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "b",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T10:16:53.408Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63809616448dda0ac07f3c4b",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "mbnmb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T10:16:54.315Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638096e9439adb5324baec13",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "cvbvc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T10:20:25.253Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380974586a78f274447c9a0",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": " nbmbnm",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T10:21:57.551Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63809b621bfdda1ea8368cc5",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "bnb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T10:39:30.244Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63809de01bfdda1ea8368d28",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "vbvc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T10:50:08.699Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63809df41bfdda1ea8368dfa",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "bbn",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T10:50:28.236Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63809dfd1bfdda1ea8368e48",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "nbvn",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T10:50:37.747Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380a0d104ca6e48345f30ec",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "bnbmb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:02:41.773Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380a0e404ca6e48345f31b7",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "mn",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:03:00.792Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380a13604ca6e48345f3258",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "bnb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:04:22.672Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380a1b60264a72cd4ac2dba",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "vnvb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:06:30.741Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380a1c00264a72cd4ac2df9",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "b",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:06:40.426Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380a1c10264a72cd4ac2e28",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "nbmnbnb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:06:41.954Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380a2f70264a72cd4ac2e7b",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "b",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:11:51.448Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380a2f80264a72cd4ac2eba",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "nbmnb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:11:52.870Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380a3050264a72cd4ac2f58",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "b bnnb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:12:05.443Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380a3080264a72cd4ac2f8c",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "bnmnbmn",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:12:08.615Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380a3150264a72cd4ac3011",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "vcbvc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:12:21.905Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380a32d0264a72cd4ac306f",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "vbvc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:12:45.644Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380a3330264a72cd4ac30bb",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "vcbc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:12:51.739Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380a4310264a72cd4ac3167",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "vn bn",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:17:05.286Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380a57c1524cc4df03bddb1",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "vcbvc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:22:36.692Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380a58e1524cc4df03bddf0",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "c",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:22:54.180Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380a58f1524cc4df03bde27",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "vbvcv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:22:55.111Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380a5931524cc4df03bde6e",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "vv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:22:59.946Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380a5971524cc4df03bdeaf",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "v",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:23:03.932Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380a6983b2aa1488cddb896",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "vnvbnbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:27:20.543Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380a7401d1d1244e89f4fee",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "vcnvnbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:30:08.442Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380a7f6e31b30409c519364",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "vbnv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:33:10.902Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380a81dace41d21e8a7fc73",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "vcbc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:33:49.418Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380a82face41d21e8a7fd4d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "vbc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:34:07.255Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380a8aaace41d21e8a7fd8a",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "vbbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:36:10.428Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380a8b7ace41d21e8a7fdcb",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "ffdfd",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:36:23.531Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380a8c7ace41d21e8a7fe08",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "cvbvc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:36:39.088Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380aabcace41d21e8a7fe9d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "jmbhj",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:45:00.145Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380acf1ace41d21e8a7ffe3",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "vcbvc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:54:25.733Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638439a6f448d226dcdfafed",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "638439a2f448d226dcdfafae",
                        "answer": "klj",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "vijay789@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:31:34.601Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638439b2f448d226dcdfb036",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "638439a2f448d226dcdfafae",
                        "answer": "vbvc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "vijay789@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:31:46.273Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638439b5f448d226dcdfb064",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "638439a2f448d226dcdfafae",
                        "answer": "b",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "vijay789@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:31:49.541Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638439b6f448d226dcdfb092",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "638439a2f448d226dcdfafae",
                        "answer": "mnb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "vijay789@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:31:50.437Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638439bbf448d226dcdfb0c0",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "638439a2f448d226dcdfafae",
                        "answer": "nmnb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "vijay789@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:31:55.041Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638439bff448d226dcdfb0ee",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "638439a2f448d226dcdfafae",
                        "answer": "vbnvbbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "vijay789@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:31:59.556Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638439c3f448d226dcdfb11c",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "638439a2f448d226dcdfafae",
                        "answer": "nvbnbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "vijay789@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:32:03.581Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638439c7f448d226dcdfb14d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "638439a2f448d226dcdfafae",
                        "answer": "bnmnb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:32:07.480Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638439cdf448d226dcdfb18f",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "638439a2f448d226dcdfafae",
                        "answer": "bmnbmnb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "vijay789@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:32:13.899Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638439d6f448d226dcdfb1da",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "638439a2f448d226dcdfafae",
                        "answer": "bnv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "vijay789@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:32:22.007Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638439d8f448d226dcdfb208",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "638439a2f448d226dcdfafae",
                        "answer": "v",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "vijay789@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:32:24.798Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638439daf448d226dcdfb233",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "638439a2f448d226dcdfafae",
                        "answer": "bnvb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "vijay789@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:32:26.410Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638439def448d226dcdfb264",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "638439a2f448d226dcdfafae",
                        "answer": "vcnbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "vijay789@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:32:30.812Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638439e3f448d226dcdfb29f",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f11c87b05b546b091235e",
                        "answer": "bvnbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:32:35.457Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638439e8f448d226dcdfb2d7",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "638439a2f448d226dcdfafae",
                        "answer": "vbnbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "vijay789@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:32:40.119Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638439eff448d226dcdfb322",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "638439a2f448d226dcdfafae",
                        "answer": "bnvbbnv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "vijay789@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:32:47.009Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638439f3f448d226dcdfb353",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "638439a2f448d226dcdfafae",
                        "answer": "bvnvn",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:32:51.464Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638439f8f448d226dcdfb395",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "638439a2f448d226dcdfafae",
                        "answer": "bcvbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "vijay789@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:32:56.327Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638439fcf448d226dcdfb3c3",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "638439a2f448d226dcdfafae",
                        "answer": "c",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "vijay789@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:33:00.424Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638439fdf448d226dcdfb3f1",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "638439a2f448d226dcdfafae",
                        "answer": "vvvbn",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "vijay789@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f11b77b05b546b091226a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:33:01.689Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "add new question",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                    "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                    "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                    "name": "vijay",
                    "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-11-24T06:39:51.028Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 63
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eef48553e7ab6730c5d5",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a83668bfdc0428e7cb10",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef48553e7ab6730c5d5",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c416c594dcace72f5b31",
                            "name": "Todd Harrison",
                            "email": "todd.harrison@deltafaucet.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-04-30T11:58:30.420Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "I do not believe it is about balance anymore but is more about work-life integration. I have had to build in the life balance into my calendar just to be able to separate work from home. I also used a visual cue to help remind me that my home office was closed by putting a closed sign on the door at the end of each day. It was simple but effective in reminding me that I didn't need to pop in just to check voicemail or email.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-04-30T12:27:09.410Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a83668bfdc0428e7cb0e",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a82468bfdc0428e7c88f",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef48553e7ab6730c5d5",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3f5c594dcace72f591c",
                            "name": "Jim Red",
                            "email": "rojjim@hotmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2020-11-25T21:44:54.463Z",
                            "currentRole": "Manager"
                        },
                        "answer": "I set a limit to work time and actually spend a lot more time combined on family activities, hobbies, rest, and sleep.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-04-15T23:19:18.356Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a82468bfdc0428e7c88d",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a82368bfdc0428e7c85d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef48553e7ab6730c5d5",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c40dc594dcace72f5a9d",
                            "name": "Kevin Fisher",
                            "email": "jkf@dartmouth-research.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-04-02T01:25:04.217Z",
                            "currentRole": "President"
                        },
                        "answer": "I train to maintain my fitness level.  I try to swim 2,500 - 4000 yards five days a week.  It has been difficult but it pays off.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-04-07T19:20:50.721Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a82368bfdc0428e7c85b",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a82c68bfdc0428e7c9b3",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef48553e7ab6730c5d5",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c40ec594dcace72f5ab2",
                            "name": "Julia Feng",
                            "email": "julia@pcpcglobal.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-04-06T22:22:54.482Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "First thing you do in the morning when you just get up is not to look at your phone. You need to activate your body first, from slow stretching work to a bit active workout like running at home. I recommend you to do Taiji, slow movement in a small space, let your energy start to flow through your whole body. You can do 10-15 minutes several times through the day when you feel your body is stiff and your brain starts to slow down. Close your eyes for 5 minutes between the tasks, slow down your breathing, let go everything, stay calm and still. Turn off your phone after your office hour, do something like cooking, listening to the music, singing, dancing, gardening, any hobby you have.  Eat a light dinner, play light music, read a book, not on electronic device. After that, write a short self-reflection journal about the day, or any issue in your mind, just empty it, go to sleep no later than 10pm, then get up at 6am.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-04-20T08:30:57.805Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a82c68bfdc0428e7c9b1",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a85568bfdc0428e7cf93",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef48553e7ab6730c5d5",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3ecc594dcace72f58f5",
                            "name": "Claire Beltmann",
                            "email": "cbeltmann@luc.edu",
                            "createdAt": "2020-10-20T20:34:37.140Z",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Setting boundaries for when you are available. Clear expectations of when you are working and upholding those expectations.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-10-03T19:02:23.238Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a85568bfdc0428e7cf91",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "how do you maintain  work life balance now that we have been working from home over the past year? ",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c409c594dcace72f5a63",
                    "name": "Walter Dusseldorp",
                    "email": "wdusseldor@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-18T12:58:13.094Z",
                    "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-03-26T01:30:40.991Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 5
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee18553e7ab6730c4ab",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a86668bfdc0428e7d204",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee18553e7ab6730c4ab",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "It sounds like your cofounder should step down.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-11-02T14:26:19.201Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a86668bfdc0428e7d202",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a85d68bfdc0428e7d0c7",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee18553e7ab6730c4ab",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c83",
                            "name": "Omar AlHajjaj",
                            "email": "saudimed@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-21T16:14:07.874Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "can’t you work to arrange for that? it is team effort not a single person effort! \ngive a chance, discuss, talk , be honest and then you will reach to a decision ",
                        "createdAt": "2021-10-27T17:00:52.610Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a85d68bfdc0428e7d0c5",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a85e68bfdc0428e7d0f8",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee18553e7ab6730c4ab",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c41ac594dcace72f5b6d",
                            "name": "Mary Louise Luczkowski",
                            "email": "luczkowskiml@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-05-13T02:34:31.438Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "I'm not sure it's you who step down. I think is important to plan out a conversation with your cofounder as to why he/she has not participated. Are your roles clearly defined? Does fear, anxiety, or doubt exist?  As a co-founder it's everyone's job to bring in money and sales. Don't rely on someone else to be responsible for two of the top 3 things a new company needs.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-10-28T14:56:35.691Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a85e68bfdc0428e7d0f6",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Should I step down? My cofounder hasn't brought any funding, nor real business.",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-10-26T02:52:42.871Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 3
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee98553e7ab6730c515",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8a168bfdc0428e7d96b",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee98553e7ab6730c515",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c40dc594dcace72f5aa7",
                            "name": "Nick Welham",
                            "email": "nick.welham@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-04-04T16:02:49.314Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-07T12:56:16.743Z"
                        },
                        "answer": "Simply put, we try harder and work harder for people we like. If you show your team you care enough to take an interest in them (and not just what they can do for you) and try to communicate in a way that suits them, then they will appreciate it. The golden rule is to do on to others, as you want done to you. The platinum rule is to do on to others as they want done to them. I'm happy to talk more about interpersonal and team dynamics; let me know if you are interested.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-25T21:48:20.057Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8a168bfdc0428e7d969",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8a268bfdc0428e7d99c",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee98553e7ab6730c515",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "Well, on the one hand, if you have a personal relationship with your employees, they'll be more likely to buy into your business's success: take initiative and pride in their work, think strategically about their tasks, and feel aligned with your goals. It's a bidirectional process though. You may find your goals amended by the perspectives of the staff that you build relationships with.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-26T15:28:30.172Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8a268bfdc0428e7d99a",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Should I take the time to understand my employee personalities? How can this benefit my business?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-01-17T16:33:31.173Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeda8553e7ab6730c440",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a83268bfdc0428e7ca5f",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeda8553e7ab6730c440",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c416c594dcace72f5b2b",
                            "name": "Charlie Atkinson",
                            "email": "charlie.atkinson@hfi.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-04-29T16:41:57.283Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "I'm not sure that the pandemic has changed the fundamentals of leadership. Lewin kicked it all off in the '30s with his designation of autocratcratic and laissez-faire leaders. Bass' concept of the transformational leader may originate in the 1970's but still feels every bit as relevant. His 4 i's, idealized influence, inspirational motivation, intellectual stimulation and individual consideration are a fantastic framework for any leader. Then there is Blanchard and Hersey's Situational Leadership, a practical model for leading individuals. In my personal experience the best leaders are self-aware, authentic and humble. They hold themselves accountable and they face up to issues and conflict. These are capabilities that transcend the moment and so are as importnat now as they ever were.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-04-29T17:01:28.966Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a83268bfdc0428e7ca5d",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a83568bfdc0428e7cad6",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeda8553e7ab6730c440",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c416c594dcace72f5b31",
                            "name": "Todd Harrison",
                            "email": "todd.harrison@deltafaucet.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-04-30T11:58:30.420Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "For myself and most of the leaders in my company, the most important skill needed during the pandemic is self-regulation while working remotely from home. The virtual work environment has created an \"always on\" effect that is creating substantial fatigue in leaders, and by default, their teams.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-04-30T12:08:56.251Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a83568bfdc0428e7cad4",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "623ac31cd611f8193cb498ce",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "623ac30bd611f8193cb498b3",
                        "answer": "Strangely, but for our company it is human caring",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "623ac1d9d611f8193cb4971c",
                            "currentRole": "Co-Founder",
                            "email": "alla@maddevs.io",
                            "name": "Alla Klimenko",
                            "createdAt": "2022-03-23T06:44:41.192Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-03-23T06:44:41.193Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6229eeda8553e7ab6730c440",
                        "createdAt": "2022-03-23T06:50:04.081Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Which skill has become most important to succeed as a leader post-pandemic?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3ecc594dcace72f58f8",
                    "name": "MollyDriscoll",
                    "email": "mdriscoll2@luc.edu",
                    "createdAt": "2020-10-07T01:12:14.277Z",
                    "currentRole": "CEO"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-04-28T19:14:38.529Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 3
            },
            {
                "_id": "6279cc96b993497cc6239ef0",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6289bd86d0a01e70a277ef96",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6289bd67d0a01e70a277ef7a",
                        "answer": "it was bound to happen because of high inflation",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6289bcdfd0a01e70a277eef1",
                            "currentRole": "Manager",
                            "email": "z.wang12@icloud.com",
                            "name": "Christy Wang",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-22T04:32:31.532Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-26T22:50:00.514Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6279cc96b993497cc6239ef0",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-22T04:35:18.926Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6289bfb5d0a01e70a277efd1",
                        "isUpdated": true,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6289bd67d0a01e70a277ef7a",
                        "answer": "high inflation caused it",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6289bcdfd0a01e70a277eef1",
                            "currentRole": "Manager",
                            "email": "z.wang12@icloud.com",
                            "name": "Christy Wang",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-22T04:32:31.532Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-26T22:50:00.514Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6279cc96b993497cc6239ef0",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-22T04:44:37.993Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "thoughts on federal interest rates rising?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "626591fb6b39681abb55d829",
                    "currentRole": "Product Manager",
                    "email": "christyz@stanford.edu",
                    "name": "Christy Wang",
                    "createdAt": "2022-04-24T18:07:55.617Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-05-09T05:35:10.337Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-05-10T02:23:18.860Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "636909f57bdc9c17d90bec0f",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "63690a377bdc9c17d90bec95",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 1,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63690a1b7bdc9c17d90bec87",
                        "answer": "Add relevant goals and keep track of it. you can use GA for example ",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6368968c78440371fa3ec003",
                            "currentRole": "Manager",
                            "email": "abdu@mailinator.com",
                            "name": "Abdu",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-07T05:24:28.489Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-07T05:42:50.500Z"
                        },
                        "question": "636909f57bdc9c17d90bec0f",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-07T13:37:59.018Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6369f2c67bdc9c17d90c628b",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6369f2c17bdc9c17d90c626d",
                        "answer": "Test",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636540abf4f4e45f9d94f2a9",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "gautam@mailinator.com",
                            "name": "Gautam",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-04T16:41:15.654Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-24T06:35:14.506Z"
                        },
                        "question": "636909f57bdc9c17d90bec0f",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-08T06:10:14.626Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6369fd3e7bdc9c17d90c7468",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 1,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6369fd0e7bdc9c17d90c7410",
                        "answer": "Use tracking code for validating strategy",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6369fb377bdc9c17d90c6e5d",
                            "currentRole": "Founder",
                            "email": "ajnish@mailinator.com",
                            "name": "Ajnish Rana",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-08T06:46:15.280Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-08T06:46:15.281Z"
                        },
                        "question": "636909f57bdc9c17d90bec0f",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-08T06:54:54.267Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6369fd757bdc9c17d90c75c5",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6369fd0e7bdc9c17d90c7410",
                        "answer": "ok thanks for sharing this. it will be helpful ",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636905907bdc9c17d90be744",
                            "currentRole": "Co-Founder",
                            "email": "cooper@mailinator.com",
                            "name": "Cooper",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-07T13:18:08.656Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-08T06:07:46.456Z"
                        },
                        "question": "636909f57bdc9c17d90bec0f",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-08T06:55:49.139Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "What are the ways to validate a marketing strategy ?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "636905907bdc9c17d90be744",
                    "currentRole": "Co-Founder",
                    "email": "cooper@mailinator.com",
                    "name": "Cooper",
                    "createdAt": "2022-11-07T13:18:08.656Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-11-08T06:07:46.456Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-11-07T13:36:53.034Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 4
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eedd8553e7ab6730c46b",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84b68bfdc0428e7ce0b",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedd8553e7ab6730c46b",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c422c594dcace72f5bf6",
                            "name": "Sarah Smith-Barry",
                            "email": "ssmithbarry@freegoconsulting.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-07-21T22:24:55.438Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "There is no one answer to this question. However, there are a number of contributing traits that help, say a CEO to be successful and others that would help a mid line manager to also be successful. An example would be the Big 5 trait of extroversion. In the United States extroversion is directly correlated with level of success. The more extroverted you are the more likely you are to be successful in your position and rise the ranks within corporate America. This is because extroverts are great at managing relationships, voicing their opinions and asking for what they want.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-08-10T13:24:36.953Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84b68bfdc0428e7ce09",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84b68bfdc0428e7ce1d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedd8553e7ab6730c46b",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f02c594dcace72f5c2f",
                            "name": "Arushi",
                            "email": "arushi2790@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-08-11T17:26:35.063Z",
                            "currentRole": "Manager"
                        },
                        "answer": "1. The ones that are Goals oriented. 2. Never giving uo Attitude.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-08-11T17:40:21.364Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84b68bfdc0428e7ce1b",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84d68bfdc0428e7ce57",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedd8553e7ab6730c46b",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c418c594dcace72f5b56",
                            "name": "Julie Hamilton",
                            "email": "juliehamilton88@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-05-07T14:33:45.520Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "collaborative, positive mindset, and tenacity ",
                        "createdAt": "2021-08-28T14:25:50.816Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84d68bfdc0428e7ce55",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "what kind of personalities succeed in business?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c425c594dcace72f5c18",
                    "name": "Len Wysocki",
                    "email": "wysock@comcast.net",
                    "createdAt": "2021-08-01T21:42:38.341Z",
                    "currentRole": "President"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-08-01T21:55:21.710Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 3
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eef18553e7ab6730c5aa",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a81368bfdc0428e7c609",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef18553e7ab6730c5aa",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3f5c594dcace72f591c",
                            "name": "Jim Red",
                            "email": "rojjim@hotmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2020-11-25T21:44:54.463Z",
                            "currentRole": "Manager"
                        },
                        "answer": "Telehealth and AI.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-02-06T00:36:18.857Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a81368bfdc0428e7c607",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a81568bfdc0428e7c673",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef18553e7ab6730c5aa",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c404c594dcace72f5a08",
                            "name": "Shivam Bhargava",
                            "email": "deepakn.vayuz@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-02-25T14:22:46.643Z",
                            "currentRole": "Vice President"
                        },
                        "answer": "Heyebxbnamxxmmsmskakakwkkakajsjsbdbdndnjdjdndbdbjsjssjajanjjw",
                        "createdAt": "2021-02-25T14:32:01.649Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a81568bfdc0428e7c671",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84e68bfdc0428e7ce7f",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef18553e7ab6730c5aa",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f04c594dcace72f5c4d",
                            "name": "Robert Varnam",
                            "email": "robert@varnam.org.uk",
                            "createdAt": "2021-09-02T09:01:31.012Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "For me (in no particular order): ~ Access changes (use of tech as an alternative to face-to-face, more patient-initiated follow-up, greater use of a multidisciplinary team on first contact, enhanced training for clerical staff to signpost patients to the right person/service).  ~ Integrated care (beginning to realise it's about joining up the teams and processes of care rather than just merging organisations).  ~ Improving IT (esp a move towards \"one patient, one record, all of my care and all of my life\").",
                        "createdAt": "2021-09-02T09:34:53.480Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84e68bfdc0428e7ce7d",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a85068bfdc0428e7cecf",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef18553e7ab6730c5aa",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3ecc594dcace72f58f8",
                            "name": "MollyDriscoll",
                            "email": "mdriscoll2@luc.edu",
                            "createdAt": "2020-10-07T01:12:14.277Z",
                            "currentRole": "CEO"
                        },
                        "answer": "thank you for your insight!",
                        "createdAt": "2021-09-17T17:27:28.800Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84e68bfdc0428e7ce7d",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "What current trends or recent innovations provide the greatest opportunities for healthcare improvement?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3ecc594dcace72f58f8",
                    "name": "MollyDriscoll",
                    "email": "mdriscoll2@luc.edu",
                    "createdAt": "2020-10-07T01:12:14.277Z",
                    "currentRole": "CEO"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-02-05T03:21:23.206Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 4
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeef8553e7ab6730c586",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "623192821a063710a820aa2d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeef8553e7ab6730c586",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3fac594dcace72f5963",
                            "name": "V Boss",
                            "email": "cyp@inscriptio.in",
                            "createdAt": "2020-12-21T05:09:58.438Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "ncjf",
                        "createdAt": "2020-12-31T04:49:47.196Z",
                        "roomId": "623192811a063710a820aa16",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "623192821a063710a820aa34",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeef8553e7ab6730c586",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3fac594dcace72f5963",
                            "name": "V Boss",
                            "email": "cyp@inscriptio.in",
                            "createdAt": "2020-12-21T05:09:58.438Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "gjfj",
                        "createdAt": "2020-12-31T04:49:47.196Z",
                        "roomId": "623192811a063710a820aa16",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "623192841a063710a820aa86",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeef8553e7ab6730c586",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3fac594dcace72f5963",
                            "name": "V Boss",
                            "email": "cyp@inscriptio.in",
                            "createdAt": "2020-12-21T05:09:58.438Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "yes\n\n\nm\n\n\n\n\n\n.\nmm\n",
                        "createdAt": "2020-12-31T04:49:47.196Z",
                        "roomId": "623192811a063710a820aa16",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a82168bfdc0428e7c80f",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeef8553e7ab6730c586",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c409c594dcace72f5a63",
                            "name": "Walter Dusseldorp",
                            "email": "wdusseldor@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-18T12:58:13.094Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "we prioritize discussion around the four factors of work life balance... mental, spiritual, physical and relationship health... taking regular time off to rebalance and refocus... especially for management team not to work more than 10 hours per day.. acknowledging that the pressure is real and providing a safe space for folks to debrief. ",
                        "createdAt": "2021-03-26T02:33:49.500Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a82168bfdc0428e7c80d",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "623192821a063710a820aa1f",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeef8553e7ab6730c586",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3fac594dcace72f5963",
                            "name": "V Boss",
                            "email": "cyp@inscriptio.in",
                            "createdAt": "2020-12-21T05:09:58.438Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "ygdf",
                        "createdAt": "2020-12-31T04:49:47.196Z",
                        "roomId": "623192811a063710a820aa16",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "623192811a063710a820aa18",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeef8553e7ab6730c586",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3fac594dcace72f5963",
                            "name": "V Boss",
                            "email": "cyp@inscriptio.in",
                            "createdAt": "2020-12-21T05:09:58.438Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "The frontline burnout being addressed is the only way to get the ",
                        "createdAt": "2020-12-31T04:49:47.196Z",
                        "roomId": "623192811a063710a820aa16",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "623192821a063710a820aa26",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeef8553e7ab6730c586",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3fac594dcace72f5963",
                            "name": "V Boss",
                            "email": "cyp@inscriptio.in",
                            "createdAt": "2020-12-21T05:09:58.438Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "fjcjfjf",
                        "createdAt": "2020-12-31T04:49:47.196Z",
                        "roomId": "623192811a063710a820aa16",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How is frontline burnout being addressed in your respective healthcare facilities, in light of staffing shortages, especially now that we're almost a year into the Covid-19 pandemic?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3f9c594dcace72f5961",
                    "name": "John Cruz",
                    "email": "johncruzrn@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2020-12-18T23:38:21.151Z",
                    "currentRole": "Manager"
                },
                "createdAt": "2020-12-19T00:01:05.655Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 7
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eedb8553e7ab6730c454",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84268bfdc0428e7ccc1",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedb8553e7ab6730c454",
                        "answer": "hello, this is a great question! so far mostly I've been tryI ing to listen as much as possible. some people are sending emails, others are telling their boss, and others are just \"hinting\" at their strong preference to be allowed to continue working from home (or to get back into the office)... we have a team of people working on compiling information we are receiving, and we will very soon be creating a general policy as well as a list of \"exceptions\"... our thinking is that we will need to be very flexible, acknowleding the whole range of people's needs,... some want to return to the office and others want to remain at home, and everything in between... we are learning that many employers and recruiters are building \"freedom to work from home\" into their \"soft incentives\", and interestingly other employers and recruiters are building \"beautiful office environment\" into their \"soft incentives... and some of the variance seems to be industry specific...",
                        "createdAt": "2021-06-27T22:05:42.329Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84268bfdc0428e7ccbf",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84368bfdc0428e7ccce",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedb8553e7ab6730c454",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c420c594dcace72f5bcb",
                            "name": "Dick Augspurger",
                            "email": "richardaugspurger@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-06-30T11:26:10.738Z",
                            "currentRole": "President"
                        },
                        "answer": "Our Team has focused a great deal upon the mental health needs of every employee during and post COVID-19 challenges. We are attempting to be more supportive of one another.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-06-30T11:39:40.324Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84368bfdc0428e7cccc",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "What planning have you done to prepare for a more hybrid work environment (remote + in office) following the pandemic?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c41fc594dcace72f5bc5",
                    "name": "Laurie Winger",
                    "email": "lwinger37@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-06-27T14:00:28.281Z",
                    "currentRole": "Executive Vice President"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-06-27T14:09:28.025Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eef38553e7ab6730c5c9",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a82168bfdc0428e7c818",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef38553e7ab6730c5c9",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c40bc594dcace72f5a77",
                            "name": "Rahul Sinha",
                            "email": "rahul.sinha1604@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-23T17:37:27.932Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "i have a very interesting insight on this. will update in a few days. a very big project is coming our way, might be able to share general details on how to build a hospital from scratch and design operations flow.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-03-26T12:17:10.086Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a82168bfdc0428e7c816",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "what are the basic elements for hospital operating plan? ( new hospital)",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c408c594dcace72f5a4b",
                    "name": "Amjad Kiwan",
                    "email": "dr.amjadtawfiq@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-15T07:04:58.179Z",
                    "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-03-19T15:41:37.696Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee08553e7ab6730c490",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a85668bfdc0428e7cfb7",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee08553e7ab6730c490",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f04c594dcace72f5c4e",
                            "name": "Iryna Chaban",
                            "email": "irynachaban98@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-09-07T19:20:12.002Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "I would make sure that my replacement knows that clear communication with other coworkers is beneficial in terms of getting work done correctly.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-10-07T13:59:34.762Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a85668bfdc0428e7cfb5",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a85968bfdc0428e7d022",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee08553e7ab6730c490",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c413c594dcace72f5b03",
                            "name": "Arijit Basu",
                            "email": "arijitb962@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-04-21T07:34:56.909Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "The show must go on! ",
                        "createdAt": "2021-10-12T06:31:02.017Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a85968bfdc0428e7d020",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "If you went on vacation tomorrow, what's something that your replacement would need to know which isn't written down anywhere?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "62218f06c594dcace72f5c69",
                    "name": "Dom Ramirez",
                    "email": "dom+lb@betacanon.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-09-30T17:27:34.155Z",
                    "currentRole": "Founder"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-09-30T17:31:25.123Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeea8553e7ab6730c52e",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8ad68bfdc0428e7db4c",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeea8553e7ab6730c52e",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                            "name": "Saima Omar",
                            "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Yes, I feel that I am. My goal is to help other businesses grow. Thus, my success comes from there success. I understand that when transitioning, you might feel close to letting go of certain elements, but this is a journey, not the destination. Keep going!",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-11T22:15:43.820Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8ad68bfdc0428e7db4a",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Do you feel 100% committed to making your company or its core idea a success? I am struggling to feel fully committed, knowing that a lot of changes to the core idea of my company may be required",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c41dc594dcace72f5b9b",
                    "name": "Madeleine",
                    "email": "maddykindler11@yahoo.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-06-10T18:10:27.425Z",
                    "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-02-03T21:32:17.032Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "637cd76a69e1ac30b216f111",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "637cd79869e1ac30b216f229",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637cd79469e1ac30b216f1f6",
                        "answer": "Answe",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637cd204a8d2472fa6a762eb",
                            "currentRole": "Associate Vice President",
                            "email": "jal@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Jal",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-22T13:43:32.360Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-23T10:34:28.337Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637cd76a69e1ac30b216f111",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-22T14:07:20.355Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637cd7ad69e1ac30b216f2af",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637cd79469e1ac30b216f1f6",
                        "answer": "hyyy",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637cd64c69e1ac30b216eff5",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "kal@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Kal",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-22T14:01:48.730Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-24T05:13:32.000Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637cd76a69e1ac30b216f111",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-22T14:07:41.945Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637db43c1a33343c8375bb64",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637cd79469e1ac30b216f1f6",
                        "answer": "hello",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637cd64c69e1ac30b216eff5",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "kal@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Kal",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-22T14:01:48.730Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-24T05:13:32.000Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637cd76a69e1ac30b216f111",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-23T05:48:44.617Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638088b233f6cd4824b98447",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 1,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "638088ab33f6cd4824b98418",
                        "answer": "hello",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "63805a078760ee61cb82b662",
                            "currentRole": "Executive Vice President",
                            "email": "fal@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Fal",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-25T06:00:39.573Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:50:17.677Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637cd76a69e1ac30b216f111",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T09:19:46.650Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "test",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "637cd64c69e1ac30b216eff5",
                    "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                    "email": "kal@yopmail.com",
                    "name": "Kal",
                    "createdAt": "2022-11-22T14:01:48.730Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-11-24T05:13:32.000Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-11-22T14:06:34.983Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 4
            },
            {
                "_id": "637db3781a33343c8375ba52",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "638082fa40433b6613620d5f",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "638082f240433b6613620d29",
                        "answer": "test....",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b6ecb7a3ce63a87b809a1",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer",
                            "email": "vijay74@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:11:39.718Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-25T08:54:15.709Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637db3781a33343c8375ba52",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T08:55:22.751Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638084e540433b6613620dd1",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "638082f240433b6613620d29",
                        "answer": "ggy",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b6ecb7a3ce63a87b809a1",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer",
                            "email": "vijay74@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:11:39.718Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-25T08:54:15.709Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637db3781a33343c8375ba52",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T09:03:33.605Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380850940433b6613620e40",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "638082f240433b6613620d29",
                        "answer": "df2gr2g",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b6ecb7a3ce63a87b809a1",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer",
                            "email": "vijay74@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:11:39.718Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-25T08:54:15.709Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637db3781a33343c8375ba52",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T09:04:09.426Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380856e40433b6613620eae",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "638082f240433b6613620d29",
                        "answer": "3",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b6ecb7a3ce63a87b809a1",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer",
                            "email": "vijay74@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:11:39.718Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-25T08:54:15.709Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637db3781a33343c8375ba52",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T09:05:50.183Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638085eb40433b6613620f1e",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "638082f240433b6613620d29",
                        "answer": "51",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b6ecb7a3ce63a87b809a1",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer",
                            "email": "vijay74@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:11:39.718Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-25T08:54:15.709Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637db3781a33343c8375ba52",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T09:07:55.317Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380876740433b6613620f9a",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "638082f240433b6613620d29",
                        "answer": "45",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b6ecb7a3ce63a87b809a1",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer",
                            "email": "vijay74@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:11:39.718Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-25T08:54:15.709Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637db3781a33343c8375ba52",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T09:14:15.456Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638087ef40433b661362100b",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "638082f240433b6613620d29",
                        "answer": "14",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b6ecb7a3ce63a87b809a1",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer",
                            "email": "vijay74@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:11:39.718Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-25T08:54:15.709Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637db3781a33343c8375ba52",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T09:16:31.888Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380889726e8e96705fbc01a",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "638082f240433b6613620d29",
                        "answer": "5",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b6ecb7a3ce63a87b809a1",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer",
                            "email": "vijay74@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:11:39.718Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-25T08:54:15.709Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637db3781a33343c8375ba52",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T09:19:19.996Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380900926e8e96705fbc591",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "638082f240433b6613620d29",
                        "answer": "fgdbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b6ecb7a3ce63a87b809a1",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer",
                            "email": "vijay74@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:11:39.718Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-25T08:54:15.709Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637db3781a33343c8375ba52",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T09:51:05.074Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380ab3926e8e96705fbe679",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "638082f240433b6613620d29",
                        "answer": "hiiii",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b6ecb7a3ce63a87b809a1",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer",
                            "email": "vijay74@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:11:39.718Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-25T08:54:15.709Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637db3781a33343c8375ba52",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:47:05.661Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "test suggestion",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6373a7eea5322d31357ff110",
                    "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer",
                    "email": "ym@yopmail.com",
                    "name": "Ym",
                    "createdAt": "2022-11-15T14:53:34.480Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:40.349Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-11-23T05:45:28.005Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 10
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eedd8553e7ab6730c467",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84a68bfdc0428e7cde9",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedd8553e7ab6730c467",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c40ac594dcace72f5a68",
                            "name": "SANJEEV KUMAR MEHTA",
                            "email": "perfect2work@yahoo.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-19T03:28:37.568Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "The answer to this question is to do right the first time \nEvery individual is important, never allow people to assume that you have created a power Center around you \n2. It is time to make course correction to change their view\n3. No point of confrontation\n\nAs an organisation our values need to dictate behaviour \nTherefore every one is equal once they are in their workplace \nEvery individual represents the organisation, so long as he is with you he needs to demonstrate the values whether in office or outside ",
                        "createdAt": "2021-07-31T17:23:45.303Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84a68bfdc0428e7cde7",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Does anyone experience situations where subordinates who share a religious identity with you wrongly assume that you will share all of the same values and treat them exceptionally? I have had multiple employees approach me with inappropriate comments about co-workers because they believe I will automatically side with them. I am never sure how to respond aside from politely telling them that it is none of their business. I was hoping someone might have advice on how to prevent/address these situations.",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c421c594dcace72f5be4",
                    "name": "Steven J. Pietras",
                    "email": "spietras43@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-07-13T15:28:46.788Z",
                    "currentRole": "Manager",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-29T15:36:07.160Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-07-30T20:34:42.612Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eedd8553e7ab6730c46f",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84c68bfdc0428e7ce2f",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedd8553e7ab6730c46f",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c422c594dcace72f5bf3",
                            "name": "Nic Gaddis-Wyatt",
                            "email": "nicgaddis13@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-07-20T03:31:51.476Z",
                            "currentRole": "Manager"
                        },
                        "answer": "If I had an employee exhibiting those behaviors, I would let them know that you noticed they seem off and ask if there is something with their job that you can help improve.  They may open up about a work related issue that you can assist with or there may be something in their personal life. If the latter is the case, then you can reiterate that you offered the days off to promote work/life balance if indeed there is something they need to take care of. Also, does your company offer some sort of employee assistance program (somewhere they can call for counseling or advice)? Some people just need to know their boss cares about their wellbeing and that is enough to help them out of a funk. On the other hand, a few people are just like that and there is nothing you can do for them besides provide the tools they need to be successful in their job. If they choose not to use those tools then that is their choice and their performance or conduct deficiencies should be dealt with accordingly. If that person's sour attitude is impacting the morale and productivity of others then a more serious personnel action may be in order. ",
                        "createdAt": "2021-08-18T04:19:02.827Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84c68bfdc0428e7ce2d",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "I am new to managing employees. One of my employees many days out of the week comes in with a very sad, morose, vibe and we run a high end customer service/courier service company. Professionally, it's a bad look for the company, but I am nervous of the possibility that she is depressed. When I offered that she can take a few days off, she made a remark to someone else that \"[me, her boss] wants me to quit\". And I told her that is nowhere near what I said or intended, I just wanted to offer her days off. Again, I am new to managing employees, we are very close to the same age (I am 24 she is 22), and I am also working through figuring out how to be kind to her without being too much of a friend. Would love any and all advice on managing employees and balancing professional/emotional expectations, managing days off, etc. - thank you.",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c414c594dcace72f5b11",
                    "name": "Ben Morton",
                    "email": "benmorton28@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-04-23T04:02:05.145Z",
                    "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-08-12T15:22:07.367Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eef48553e7ab6730c5d9",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a83968bfdc0428e7cb68",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef48553e7ab6730c5d9",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c41bc594dcace72f5b84",
                            "name": "Eric Dupuis",
                            "email": "artonadigitaltechnology@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-05-27T00:41:06.166Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "by creating our new platform called Nano Neural Bio Computer ",
                        "createdAt": "2021-05-27T01:02:44.934Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a83968bfdc0428e7cb66",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How to plan global outreach of our revolutionary software related to ‘Document Analysis’ ?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c411c594dcace72f5adb",
                    "name": "Brindanivas",
                    "email": "brinda@radyeus.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-04-15T01:46:26.427Z",
                    "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-04-15T13:09:54.550Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeda8553e7ab6730c441",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a83568bfdc0428e7cac9",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeda8553e7ab6730c441",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c415c594dcace72f5b25",
                            "name": "Peter Klein",
                            "email": "pklein@educatedc.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-04-28T23:15:54.161Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "thanks",
                        "createdAt": "2021-04-30T03:32:52.232Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a83368bfdc0428e7ca9f",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a83368bfdc0428e7caa1",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeda8553e7ab6730c441",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c412c594dcace72f5af7",
                            "name": "George Kondrach",
                            "email": "gkondrach@amplikai.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-04-20T02:49:59.436Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "neutral",
                        "createdAt": "2021-04-29T17:36:32.545Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a83368bfdc0428e7ca9f",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How do you like this video https://youtu.be/bTlkueI26cI",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c415c594dcace72f5b25",
                    "name": "Peter Klein",
                    "email": "pklein@educatedc.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-04-28T23:15:54.161Z",
                    "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-04-28T23:20:54.983Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeda8553e7ab6730c445",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a83968bfdc0428e7cb81",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeda8553e7ab6730c445",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c41bc594dcace72f5b84",
                            "name": "Eric Dupuis",
                            "email": "artonadigitaltechnology@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-05-27T00:41:06.166Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "our new technology will change everything ",
                        "createdAt": "2021-05-27T01:04:49.917Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a83968bfdc0428e7cb7f",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "What strategies have helped you move out of a thinking brut?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3ebc594dcace72f58e6",
                    "name": "Manoj Negi",
                    "email": "mannu1993negi@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2020-10-14T10:40:21.335Z",
                    "currentRole": "President",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-10-11T12:44:54.169Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-05-07T07:13:45.643Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eedf8553e7ab6730c484",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a85268bfdc0428e7cf19",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedf8553e7ab6730c484",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f06c594dcace72f5c62",
                            "name": "Dino Maiolo",
                            "email": "dino@cabaretti.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-09-28T16:56:58.702Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "Definitely take them aside. The only time you can do it in front of others is in emergency situations, say if you were in the military or worked for the fire department, but even then, it's rare to have to do that. You can almost always take them aside. The reason for this is that you don't want to undermine their authority or huniliate them. they'll lose motivation. You alwasys want your crticism to be construction. Easier said than done sometimes. Hope that helps.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-09-28T17:14:07.096Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a85268bfdc0428e7cf17",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "As a leader, do you think it is it better to give on-the-spot feedback to your employees, infront of their colleagues, or is it better to have a 1-on-1 discussion?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-09-21T14:10:01.981Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeed8553e7ab6730c563",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8bb68bfdc0428e7dd30",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeed8553e7ab6730c563",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3e5c594dcace72f5893",
                            "name": "Firzana",
                            "email": "firzana218@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-12-29T20:45:55.686Z",
                            "currentRole": "Other"
                        },
                        "answer": "I think it is very important for leaders to take a break. Breaks are necessary for productivity and well-being, your company can't run optimally if you are mentally/physically burnt-out. Plus, many of your employee's livelihood now depends on you, so you must make sure you take breaks and recharge in order to be 100% during the workday and yield ideal outcomes.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-25T17:51:29.554Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8bb68bfdc0428e7dd2e",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8bb68bfdc0428e7dd3c",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeed8553e7ab6730c563",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3e6c594dcace72f58aa",
                            "name": "Amarachi Emezie",
                            "email": "amarachieemezie@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2022-01-12T18:41:13.277Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-05-09T15:13:09.331Z",
                            "currentRole": "Other"
                        },
                        "answer": "1000% yes. Burn out is real, regardless of your position in the company. As a leader, it is important to create an environment that promotes balance. The PTOs granted to employees are for a reason. There are days that we as humans need a reset. As a leader, the pressure to be on 100% can lead to inefficiency. As a leader you need breaks to step away from your work, breaks that allow you to get substantial rest and allow your mind to wonder elsewhere. Through such break, your company, or the individuals you are leading will benefit in the long run. Productivity and efficiency can also be improved by allowing yourself to take a break and prioritize your well-being.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-25T18:19:41.522Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8bb68bfdc0428e7dd3a",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8b968bfdc0428e7dcfa",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeed8553e7ab6730c563",
                        "answer": "I always think finalcially it is not worth is. However the mental and emotional benifits gained from a break are critical to sustain your energy long-term.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-24T01:49:27.458Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8b968bfdc0428e7dcf8",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How important is it for leaders to take a break?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3e6c594dcace72f58a1",
                    "name": "Srijal",
                    "email": "srijalsharma01@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2022-01-10T12:30:06.951Z",
                    "currentRole": "Manager"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-02-23T12:31:25.420Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 3
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee58553e7ab6730c4e4",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a88a68bfdc0428e7d620",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee58553e7ab6730c4e4",
                        "answer": "Keep people in separate section may be to make each group comfortab",
                        "createdAt": "2021-12-15T19:50:31.137Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a88a68bfdc0428e7d61e",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a88168bfdc0428e7d5cd",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee58553e7ab6730c4e4",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3cfc594dcace72f586a",
                            "name": "Hinepa",
                            "email": "hinepa6675@mediafate.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-12-09T11:39:58.580Z",
                            "currentRole": "Partner"
                        },
                        "answer": "I",
                        "createdAt": "2021-12-10T12:38:59.462Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a88168bfdc0428e7d5cb",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a88a68bfdc0428e7d62d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee58553e7ab6730c4e4",
                        "answer": "Keep them in different section and different blocks",
                        "createdAt": "2021-12-15T20:12:19.988Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a88a68bfdc0428e7d62b",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a88768bfdc0428e7d604",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee58553e7ab6730c4e4",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3cfc594dcace72f586a",
                            "name": "Hinepa",
                            "email": "hinepa6675@mediafate.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-12-09T11:39:58.580Z",
                            "currentRole": "Partner"
                        },
                        "answer": "I",
                        "createdAt": "2021-12-11T05:55:57.945Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a88168bfdc0428e7d5cb",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Our company has not enforced the vaccine mandate and we want to make sure all of our workers feel safe, and also are not divided over the issue. Any suggestions on how to facilitate an understanding based conversation around the vaccination and those that are for and those that are wary of it?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                    "name": "Daniel Daws",
                    "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                    "currentRole": "Founder"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-12-09T02:18:41.781Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 4
            },
            {
                "_id": "637de4e69e8cfd59fc129fc5",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "637de5149e8cfd59fc12a28f",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637de5119e8cfd59fc12a26c",
                        "answer": "hii",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637da81d1a33343c8375a58a",
                            "currentRole": "Manager",
                            "email": "vijay087.rejoice@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-23T04:57:01.461Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-23T04:57:01.462Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637de4e69e8cfd59fc129fc5",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-23T09:17:08.566Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637de9d39e8cfd59fc12ac5a",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637de5119e8cfd59fc12a26c",
                        "answer": "hiii",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637da81d1a33343c8375a58a",
                            "currentRole": "Manager",
                            "email": "vijay087.rejoice@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-23T04:57:01.461Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-23T04:57:01.462Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637de4e69e8cfd59fc129fc5",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-23T09:37:23.847Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637e191df29aff45dc0ea772",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637e18e4f29aff45dc0ea67d",
                        "answer": "hii\n",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6378990a89e55b771e3f1132",
                            "currentRole": "Other",
                            "email": "vijay0844@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-19T08:51:22.393Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-23T12:54:20.549Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637de4e69e8cfd59fc129fc5",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-23T12:59:09.002Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380ad91ace41d21e8a805ce",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad8eace41d21e8a8058e",
                        "answer": "cbvc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637de4e69e8cfd59fc129fc5",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:57:05.619Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380aea2ace41d21e8a80806",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad8eace41d21e8a8058e",
                        "answer": "vnbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637de4e69e8cfd59fc129fc5",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:01:38.969Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380aee4ace41d21e8a80845",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad8eace41d21e8a8058e",
                        "answer": "vcbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637de4e69e8cfd59fc129fc5",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:02:44.356Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380aeeface41d21e8a80884",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad8eace41d21e8a8058e",
                        "answer": "vcbvc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637de4e69e8cfd59fc129fc5",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:02:55.306Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380aefbace41d21e8a808c3",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad8eace41d21e8a8058e",
                        "answer": "v",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637de4e69e8cfd59fc129fc5",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:03:07.865Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380aefcace41d21e8a808f8",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad8eace41d21e8a8058e",
                        "answer": "cb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637de4e69e8cfd59fc129fc5",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:03:08.649Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380af4ad853ea4f5c402af9",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad8eace41d21e8a8058e",
                        "answer": "c",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637de4e69e8cfd59fc129fc5",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:04:26.624Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380af4bd853ea4f5c402b21",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad8eace41d21e8a8058e",
                        "answer": "vb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637de4e69e8cfd59fc129fc5",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:04:27.421Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380af81d853ea4f5c402b57",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad8eace41d21e8a8058e",
                        "answer": "vbvnvb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637de4e69e8cfd59fc129fc5",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:05:21.966Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380af91d853ea4f5c402b96",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad8eace41d21e8a8058e",
                        "answer": "v",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637de4e69e8cfd59fc129fc5",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:05:37.582Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380af92d853ea4f5c402bca",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad8eace41d21e8a8058e",
                        "answer": "cb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637de4e69e8cfd59fc129fc5",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:05:38.338Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380af9ed853ea4f5c402c12",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad8eace41d21e8a8058e",
                        "answer": "vc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637de4e69e8cfd59fc129fc5",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:05:50.869Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380b01a76ec434c984388ab",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad8eace41d21e8a8058e",
                        "answer": "vcbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637de4e69e8cfd59fc129fc5",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:07:54.808Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380b0e776ec434c984388fe",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad8eace41d21e8a8058e",
                        "answer": "vbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637de4e69e8cfd59fc129fc5",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:11:19.754Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380b103950a64501c4bffd2",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad8eace41d21e8a8058e",
                        "answer": "vcbc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637de4e69e8cfd59fc129fc5",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:11:47.969Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380b229e52d9b5f6c7f30e0",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad8eace41d21e8a8058e",
                        "answer": "bvnv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637de4e69e8cfd59fc129fc5",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:16:41.069Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380b2b8d24343497c74398a",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad8eace41d21e8a8058e",
                        "answer": "fvdfd",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637de4e69e8cfd59fc129fc5",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:19:04.103Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380b2e95df10215e438d99b",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad8eace41d21e8a8058e",
                        "answer": "cvcbvc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637de4e69e8cfd59fc129fc5",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:19:53.026Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380b3065df10215e438d9ca",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad8eace41d21e8a8058e",
                        "answer": "v",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637de4e69e8cfd59fc129fc5",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:20:22.475Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380b3075df10215e438d9fd",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad8eace41d21e8a8058e",
                        "answer": "bc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637de4e69e8cfd59fc129fc5",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:20:23.541Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380b3375df10215e438da75",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad8eace41d21e8a8058e",
                        "answer": "cvbvc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637de4e69e8cfd59fc129fc5",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:21:11.194Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380b3525df10215e438dad3",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad8eace41d21e8a8058e",
                        "answer": "fdfd",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637de4e69e8cfd59fc129fc5",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:21:38.156Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380b35d5df10215e438db4a",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad8eace41d21e8a8058e",
                        "answer": "cvcbc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637de4e69e8cfd59fc129fc5",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:21:49.081Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380b37e5df10215e438dbb5",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad8eace41d21e8a8058e",
                        "answer": "vcvb cv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637de4e69e8cfd59fc129fc5",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:22:22.178Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380b3c25df10215e438dc7e",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad8eace41d21e8a8058e",
                        "answer": "bvcvc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637de4e69e8cfd59fc129fc5",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:23:30.780Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380b3cc5df10215e438dce3",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad8eace41d21e8a8058e",
                        "answer": "nbbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637de4e69e8cfd59fc129fc5",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:23:40.308Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380b48f5df10215e438dea3",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad8eace41d21e8a8058e",
                        "answer": "bvnv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637de4e69e8cfd59fc129fc5",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:26:55.216Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380b4975df10215e438df0a",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad8eace41d21e8a8058e",
                        "answer": "bnbvn",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637de4e69e8cfd59fc129fc5",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:27:03.056Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380b4d25df10215e438e094",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad8eace41d21e8a8058e",
                        "answer": "bnn",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637de4e69e8cfd59fc129fc5",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:28:02.105Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "TTT",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                    "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                    "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                    "name": "vijay",
                    "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-11-23T09:16:22.030Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 32
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee68553e7ab6730c4ef",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a88c68bfdc0428e7d660",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee68553e7ab6730c4ef",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c40ac594dcace72f5a68",
                            "name": "SANJEEV KUMAR MEHTA",
                            "email": "perfect2work@yahoo.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-19T03:28:37.568Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "if the employee has demonstrated most qualities required for the next role in his current assignment ",
                        "createdAt": "2021-12-21T03:43:51.090Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a88b68bfdc0428e7d65e",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8a768bfdc0428e7da5e",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee68553e7ab6730c4ef",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "Their long-term goals, the new position's requirements, what support they may need in new responsibilities, just as a broad sweep of considerations.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-03T16:45:23.272Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8a768bfdc0428e7da5c",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "What do you consider before promoting someone?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-12-20T15:53:45.106Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeee8553e7ab6730c56d",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8bf68bfdc0428e7ddb5",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeee8553e7ab6730c56d",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "If you're selling a specific niche product you could partner with other businesses who target a similar audience but sell different products!",
                        "createdAt": "2022-03-03T18:48:19.022Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8bf68bfdc0428e7ddb3",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "What kind of marketing can my start-up e-commerce business focus on?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-03-01T01:12:23.137Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "62b9c55cf6ac59655dddbcff",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "62bafb40f6ac59655dde383d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "62bafb3ef6ac59655dde381c",
                        "answer": "asasass",
                        "question": "62b9c55cf6ac59655dddbcff",
                        "createdAt": "2022-06-28T12:59:44.833Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "62bc7293f6ac59655ddef317",
                        "isUpdated": true,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 1,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "62bc71b8f6ac59655ddef308",
                        "answer": "I believe so. It doesn't necessarily have to overstep boundries or impact employee relationships. reaching out to local officials or officials in states with disagreeable policies to make it known that you will or will not do business in areas with inhumane laws is an easy step.",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c421c594dcace72f5be4",
                            "name": "Steven J. Pietras",
                            "email": "spietras43@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-07-13T15:28:46.788Z",
                            "currentRole": "Manager",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-29T15:36:07.160Z"
                        },
                        "question": "62b9c55cf6ac59655dddbcff",
                        "createdAt": "2022-06-29T15:41:07.130Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "62c48a7df6ac59655ddfa469",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "62c48a79f6ac59655ddfa446",
                        "answer": "No",
                        "question": "62b9c55cf6ac59655dddbcff",
                        "createdAt": "2022-07-05T19:01:17.809Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "62c48de2f6ac59655ddfb007",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "62c48a79f6ac59655ddfa446",
                        "answer": "Hell Yes",
                        "question": "62b9c55cf6ac59655dddbcff",
                        "createdAt": "2022-07-05T19:15:46.853Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Do small businesses have a clear role to play in responding to U.S. state trigger laws? We want to provide equitable service to our female employees but don't want to overstep personal-political boundaries.",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                    "name": "Daniel Daws",
                    "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                    "currentRole": "Founder"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-06-27T14:57:32.205Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 4
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee38553e7ab6730c4c5",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a86f68bfdc0428e7d334",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee38553e7ab6730c4c5",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                            "name": "Saima Omar",
                            "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "What kind of organization do you lead? What style of leadership are you adopting?",
                        "createdAt": "2021-11-17T14:22:08.275Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a86e68bfdc0428e7d32b",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a86f68bfdc0428e7d33d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee38553e7ab6730c4c5",
                        "answer": "both",
                        "createdAt": "2021-11-18T01:43:59.779Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a86f68bfdc0428e7d33b",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Is transformational leadership critical or should a leader focus on maintaining the status quo instead?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-11-17T00:49:10.190Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeea8553e7ab6730c52b",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8ad68bfdc0428e7db28",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeea8553e7ab6730c52b",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3e5c594dcace72f589a",
                            "name": "Robert",
                            "email": "yiwexi8958@whecode.com",
                            "createdAt": "2022-01-06T14:42:11.315Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "ok",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-10T06:14:58.507Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8a468bfdc0428e7d9cd",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Today's 2nd Question : 02 Feb, 2022",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3e5c594dcace72f589a",
                    "name": "Robert",
                    "email": "yiwexi8958@whecode.com",
                    "createdAt": "2022-01-06T14:42:11.315Z",
                    "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-02-02T04:04:23.493Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeda8553e7ab6730c43f",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a83a68bfdc0428e7cba3",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeda8553e7ab6730c43f",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c41bc594dcace72f5b84",
                            "name": "Eric Dupuis",
                            "email": "artonadigitaltechnology@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-05-27T00:41:06.166Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "not ",
                        "createdAt": "2021-05-27T01:06:34.113Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a83a68bfdc0428e7cba1",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "What’s ",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3ebc594dcace72f58e6",
                    "name": "Manoj Negi",
                    "email": "mannu1993negi@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2020-10-14T10:40:21.335Z",
                    "currentRole": "President",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-10-11T12:44:54.169Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-04-28T07:01:25.847Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee08553e7ab6730c499",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a86768bfdc0428e7d216",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee08553e7ab6730c499",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "Your order of priorities depends on your business's mission. If you are community-driven, the three parts are going to be determined by who you're servicing.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-11-02T14:30:55.385Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a86768bfdc0428e7d214",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "I run a small business and have been working on identifying stakeholders. Does anyone have advice on how to decide when to prioritize customers, the community, or employees?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c421c594dcace72f5be4",
                    "name": "Steven J. Pietras",
                    "email": "spietras43@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-07-13T15:28:46.788Z",
                    "currentRole": "Manager",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-29T15:36:07.160Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:28:14.061Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "62b013c297dd855eaa0fab7a",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "62bb1640f6ac59655dde7928",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "62b6ffdff6ac59655ddd8dc3",
                        "answer": "vcnvbn",
                        "question": "62b013c297dd855eaa0fab7a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-06-28T14:54:56.911Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How to dilute Equity while raising funds?\n",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "62b0122f97dd855eaa0fa91e",
                    "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                    "email": "matol42946@giftcv.com",
                    "name": "John",
                    "createdAt": "2022-06-20T06:22:39.225Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-20T06:22:39.226Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-06-20T06:29:22.394Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6284dad5fa4fe26e53174cdf",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6284db5efa4fe26e5317524a",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6284db3efa4fe26e53175128",
                        "answer": "this is best decision for country and public for freedom",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "624d5ba9d500ad509757879c",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer",
                            "email": "tehav55741@nuesond.com",
                            "name": "Tehav",
                            "createdAt": "2022-04-06T09:21:45.077Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-10-10T04:11:45.916Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6284dad5fa4fe26e53174cdf",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-18T11:41:18.372Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6284dc86fa4fe26e531757bc",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6284db3efa4fe26e53175128",
                        "answer": "okayyy\n",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6284ce1afa4fe26e531732ab",
                            "currentRole": "Founder",
                            "email": "ligedov825@akapple.com",
                            "name": "Lige",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-18T10:44:42.887Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-03T12:51:10.092Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6284dad5fa4fe26e53174cdf",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-18T11:46:14.102Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6284dc96fa4fe26e53175847",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6284db3efa4fe26e53175128",
                        "answer": "thats right",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "624d5ba9d500ad509757879c",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer",
                            "email": "tehav55741@nuesond.com",
                            "name": "Tehav",
                            "createdAt": "2022-04-06T09:21:45.077Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-10-10T04:11:45.916Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6284dad5fa4fe26e53174cdf",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-18T11:46:30.243Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "we are going to take leadership for country",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6284ce1afa4fe26e531732ab",
                    "currentRole": "Founder",
                    "email": "ligedov825@akapple.com",
                    "name": "Lige",
                    "createdAt": "2022-05-18T10:44:42.887Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-03T12:51:10.092Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-05-18T11:39:01.369Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 3
            },
            {
                "_id": "6368997478440371fa3ec6e2",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "63689b5678440371fa3ecb75",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63689a2c78440371fa3ec859",
                        "answer": "Just call them up and give the assignment and then track the progress and approach taken by the user to work.\n",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6365436af4f4e45f9d94f847",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director",
                            "email": "tina@mailinator.com",
                            "name": "tina",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-04T16:52:58.590Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-24T06:35:04.547Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6368997478440371fa3ec6e2",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-07T05:44:54.498Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63689c0678440371fa3ece71",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63689a2c78440371fa3ec859",
                        "answer": "let me try this and i will update you how it went",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6368968c78440371fa3ec003",
                            "currentRole": "Manager",
                            "email": "abdu@mailinator.com",
                            "name": "Abdu",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-07T05:24:28.489Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-07T05:42:50.500Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6368997478440371fa3ec6e2",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-07T05:47:50.054Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63689c4178440371fa3ecff2",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63689a2c78440371fa3ec859",
                        "answer": "Great. Keep me posted about the same",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6365436af4f4e45f9d94f847",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director",
                            "email": "tina@mailinator.com",
                            "name": "tina",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-04T16:52:58.590Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-24T06:35:04.547Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6368997478440371fa3ec6e2",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-07T05:48:49.402Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "When delegating a recent assignment, describe how you showed your confidence in the person’s ability to do the job?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6368968c78440371fa3ec003",
                    "currentRole": "Manager",
                    "email": "abdu@mailinator.com",
                    "name": "Abdu",
                    "createdAt": "2022-11-07T05:24:28.489Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-11-07T05:42:50.500Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-11-07T05:36:52.776Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 3
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee18553e7ab6730c4a3",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a85a68bfdc0428e7d05a",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee18553e7ab6730c4a3",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f04c594dcace72f5c4e",
                            "name": "Iryna Chaban",
                            "email": "irynachaban98@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-09-07T19:20:12.002Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "I would suggest experimenting with inexpensive marketing strategies first. For instance, pay a small amount to email marketing software. You should also be careful about the sources you are using, as some of them can be resource-draining.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-10-18T18:56:26.665Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a85a68bfdc0428e7d058",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "I have a start-up B2C brand. My company has been running for around 5 months but sales are not as I'd hoped at present. I'm in the process of getting the word out there. I have a modest marketing budget. How can I be savvy about where I spend my marketing budget?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-10-14T00:03:09.297Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eef08553e7ab6730c58f",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a80d68bfdc0428e7c53d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef08553e7ab6730c58f",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3fdc594dcace72f599f",
                            "name": "Test 30",
                            "email": "test30@inscriptio.in",
                            "createdAt": "2021-01-13T06:23:05.122Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Hello",
                        "createdAt": "2021-01-23T06:00:06.338Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a80d68bfdc0428e7c53b",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "how pandemic affected in your place",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3fcc594dcace72f5986",
                    "name": "Hema P H",
                    "email": "hema.vayuz@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-01-06T10:14:53.946Z",
                    "currentRole": "Manager"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-01-06T11:59:01.117Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "637f7a39231ce456a1a40f75",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "637f7a8e231ce456a1a410bd",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f7a88231ce456a1a41083",
                        "answer": "Testetygagggkdas",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637cd204a8d2472fa6a762eb",
                            "currentRole": "Associate Vice President",
                            "email": "jal@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Jal",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-22T13:43:32.360Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-23T10:34:28.337Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f7a39231ce456a1a40f75",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:07:10.100Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "test",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                    "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                    "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                    "name": "Baju",
                    "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:05:45.980Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeee8553e7ab6730c56c",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8bf68bfdc0428e7ddcb",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeee8553e7ab6730c56c",
                        "answer": "When it is financially appropriate. When making your first hire, be sure you are both on the same page about the company's goals, mission and vision.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-03-04T04:07:46.194Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8bf68bfdc0428e7ddc9",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8c168bfdc0428e7de14",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeee8553e7ab6730c56c",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                            "name": "Saima Omar",
                            "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "How much does your company need to make to ensure you can fund a position? 10k ? 15k? Let's say overheads are 5k at the moment...",
                        "createdAt": "2022-03-05T03:42:28.692Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8bf68bfdc0428e7ddc9",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8bc68bfdc0428e7dd67",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeee8553e7ab6730c56c",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "If you're talking about lower-level work, then you may want to hire before you begin turning a profit. At a higher level, it might be wise to wait until you are further into the market and evaluate what your needs are.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-03-01T16:02:19.997Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8bc68bfdc0428e7dd65",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "When is a start-up ready to make its first hire?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-02-28T22:39:38.285Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 3
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eedd8553e7ab6730c46d",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84c68bfdc0428e7ce26",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedd8553e7ab6730c46d",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c414c594dcace72f5b11",
                            "name": "Ben Morton",
                            "email": "benmorton28@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-04-23T04:02:05.145Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "Listened to a problem that someone was having and thought I might have a way to solve it",
                        "createdAt": "2021-08-12T15:22:49.918Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84b68bfdc0428e7ce24",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How did you get an idea about your startup?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "62218f02c594dcace72f5c2f",
                    "name": "Arushi",
                    "email": "arushi2790@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-08-11T17:26:35.063Z",
                    "currentRole": "Manager"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-08-11T17:37:53.539Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee58553e7ab6730c4dd",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a87f68bfdc0428e7d599",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee58553e7ab6730c4dd",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "Type in a question",
                        "createdAt": "2021-12-09T02:20:10.949Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a87f68bfdc0428e7d597",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a88968bfdc0428e7d60f",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee58553e7ab6730c4dd",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f08c594dcace72f5c91",
                            "name": "conov24061",
                            "email": "conov24061@dukeoo.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-11-01T09:35:21.469Z",
                            "currentRole": "Product Manager"
                        },
                        "answer": "Ok",
                        "createdAt": "2021-12-14T12:59:02.115Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a87f68bfdc0428e7d597",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a87a68bfdc0428e7d4cf",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee58553e7ab6730c4dd",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f00c594dcace72f5c24",
                            "name": "Steven Pietras",
                            "email": "norgoth12@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-08-07T15:35:10.381Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "I like to ask others about specific problems I've encountered to see if anyone else has had similar experiances and can offer advice",
                        "createdAt": "2021-12-03T13:41:45.206Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a87a68bfdc0428e7d4cd",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "how to use Leader bridge?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "62218f08c594dcace72f5c91",
                    "name": "conov24061",
                    "email": "conov24061@dukeoo.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-11-01T09:35:21.469Z",
                    "currentRole": "Product Manager"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-12-03T08:58:15.139Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 3
            },
            {
                "_id": "63654f20f4f4e45f9d953623",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "63654f3df4f4e45f9d95370c",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63654f37f4f4e45f9d9536a9",
                        "answer": "Hii",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6256d6b74f929c559b2183eb",
                            "currentRole": "Partner",
                            "email": "kevin088.rejoice@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Kevin",
                            "createdAt": "2022-04-13T13:57:11.884Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-15T09:09:19.527Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63654f20f4f4e45f9d953623",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-04T17:43:25.102Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6365547bf4f4e45f9d9544f7",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63654f37f4f4e45f9d9536a9",
                        "answer": "etywtw",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6256d6b74f929c559b2183eb",
                            "currentRole": "Partner",
                            "email": "kevin088.rejoice@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Kevin",
                            "createdAt": "2022-04-13T13:57:11.884Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-15T09:09:19.527Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63654f20f4f4e45f9d953623",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-04T18:05:47.130Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Do small businesses have a clear role to play in responding to U.S. state trigger laws? We want to provide equitable service to our female employees but don't want to overstep personal-political boundaries part..",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "63650ec99e7f3559ed38bb92",
                    "currentRole": "Founder",
                    "email": "keving@yopmail.com",
                    "name": "Kevin",
                    "createdAt": "2022-11-04T13:08:25.542Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-11-05T05:14:05.986Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-11-04T17:42:56.009Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeec8553e7ab6730c54c",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8b668bfdc0428e7dc8e",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeec8553e7ab6730c54c",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c41dc594dcace72f5b9b",
                            "name": "Madeleine",
                            "email": "maddykindler11@yahoo.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-06-10T18:10:27.425Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "In my experience, if you really want your company to grow and be successful, outside funding will eventually become a necessity. I think it is important, however, to not just accept funding from anyone but from someone who aligns (mostly) with the vision and values of your company. Some adjustments are unavoidable, but I don't believe that external funding should be accepted at the complete expense of your vision.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-21T18:37:48.971Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8b668bfdc0428e7dc8c",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "I am currently figuring out how to sustainably fund my startup and am heavily considering outside funding but I really don't know how much I am willing to 'give up'. How do you navigate through the entire process of deciding whether to receive outside funding?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3e5c594dcace72f5893",
                    "name": "Firzana",
                    "email": "firzana218@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-12-29T20:45:55.686Z",
                    "currentRole": "Other"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-02-16T14:34:05.589Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee98553e7ab6730c51d",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a89f68bfdc0428e7d925",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee98553e7ab6730c51d",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "Accountability can be the difference between your service being delivered and you getting paid vs your company going under. If there is no accountability, there is a diffusion of responsibility across a team. This leaves teams disorganized and unmotivated without a clear set of priorities.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-21T20:04:31.072Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a89f68bfdc0428e7d923",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How important role \"Accountability\" hold in a workplace?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3e6c594dcace72f58a1",
                    "name": "Srijal",
                    "email": "srijalsharma01@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2022-01-10T12:30:06.951Z",
                    "currentRole": "Manager"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-01-19T15:20:29.267Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee68553e7ab6730c4f5",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a89068bfdc0428e7d6d6",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee68553e7ab6730c4f5",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c419c594dcace72f5b63",
                            "name": "Alireza Akbari",
                            "email": "aakbari@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-05-10T16:32:35.870Z",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "The answer is within you, don't look to find it out there. If you don't believe that you deserve to be the leader, others won't.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-12-25T05:30:00.192Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a89068bfdc0428e7d6d4",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a89968bfdc0428e7d82b",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee68553e7ab6730c4f5",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "It might be helpful to examine the ways you're trying to establish authority. Are you handing out commands, or are you beside your team? Are you delegating towards growth?",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-13T00:38:12.068Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a89968bfdc0428e7d829",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a89068bfdc0428e7d6f0",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee68553e7ab6730c4f5",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3e4c594dcace72f588d",
                            "name": "John",
                            "email": "mirilo4745@saturdata.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-12-27T16:23:19.105Z",
                            "currentRole": "Vice President"
                        },
                        "answer": "aa",
                        "createdAt": "2021-12-27T17:04:04.915Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a89068bfdc0428e7d6ee",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a89268bfdc0428e7d719",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee68553e7ab6730c4f5",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3e4c594dcace72f5884",
                            "name": "Fosan",
                            "email": "fosan73447@xtrempro.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-12-23T05:44:46.221Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Vice President"
                        },
                        "answer": "f",
                        "createdAt": "2021-12-28T06:19:45.956Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a89268bfdc0428e7d717",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "As a young leader, I find it is hard to establish authority over people older than me. Any advice on how to do this?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3ecc594dcace72f58f8",
                    "name": "MollyDriscoll",
                    "email": "mdriscoll2@luc.edu",
                    "createdAt": "2020-10-07T01:12:14.277Z",
                    "currentRole": "CEO"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-12-23T23:18:23.066Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 4
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eef28553e7ab6730c5b8",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a85068bfdc0428e7ced6",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef28553e7ab6730c5b8",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3ecc594dcace72f58f8",
                            "name": "MollyDriscoll",
                            "email": "mdriscoll2@luc.edu",
                            "createdAt": "2020-10-07T01:12:14.277Z",
                            "currentRole": "CEO"
                        },
                        "answer": "wonderful advice, thank you!",
                        "createdAt": "2021-09-17T17:29:23.468Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84e68bfdc0428e7ce98",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a82568bfdc0428e7c8aa",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef28553e7ab6730c5b8",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3f5c594dcace72f591c",
                            "name": "Jim Red",
                            "email": "rojjim@hotmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2020-11-25T21:44:54.463Z",
                            "currentRole": "Manager"
                        },
                        "answer": "Visit the frontline more frequenty.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-04-16T00:16:03.971Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a82568bfdc0428e7c8a8",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84e68bfdc0428e7ce9a",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef28553e7ab6730c5b8",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f04c594dcace72f5c4d",
                            "name": "Robert Varnam",
                            "email": "robert@varnam.org.uk",
                            "createdAt": "2021-09-02T09:01:31.012Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "For me it begins with changing myself - it's about BEING present (physically) with people; actively soliciting and LISTENING to people's stories of how they're doing; and SHOWING that I'm human, too, by explicitly empathising and being much more open about how I'm doing myself. I ensure I include 'personal stories' from my own life and work when talking with staff in 1:1 and group settings. It's been an interesting journey to get to that point, and didn't feel comfortable initially. But I'm getting there, and have seen some really big results. Hope that helps. Do feel free to get in touch if you'd like to chat further - robert@varnam.org.uk",
                        "createdAt": "2021-09-02T09:47:14.446Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84e68bfdc0428e7ce98",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How can I demonstrate executive presence and compassion amidst frontline staff distress and anxiety?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3ecc594dcace72f58f8",
                    "name": "MollyDriscoll",
                    "email": "mdriscoll2@luc.edu",
                    "createdAt": "2020-10-07T01:12:14.277Z",
                    "currentRole": "CEO"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-02-16T16:03:37.549Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 3
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee98553e7ab6730c521",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a89e68bfdc0428e7d90a",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee98553e7ab6730c521",
                        "answer": "answer",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-21T19:56:12.019Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a89e68bfdc0428e7d908",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "My partners and I have spent a lot of time strategizing about the most effective way to get our small business off the ground. Our problem is we have a lot of solutions that look promising and we're having a difficult time selecting which one looks best. We have a pretty good idea of what market we'd like to corner and how we'd like to market to them, but there are other potential markets out there that are also alluring. How can we really hone in on the best place to start executing?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                    "name": "Daniel Daws",
                    "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                    "currentRole": "Founder"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-01-21T17:23:54.481Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee98553e7ab6730c51f",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8a168bfdc0428e7d962",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee98553e7ab6730c51f",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3e7c594dcace72f58b5",
                            "name": "maddykindlerr",
                            "email": "maddykindler1@aol.com",
                            "createdAt": "2022-01-24T19:31:34.994Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "Hi! Let’s connect",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-24T19:36:54.931Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8a168bfdc0428e7d960",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a89e68bfdc0428e7d8f9",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee98553e7ab6730c51f",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "In the '70s Nike was able to sell a new line of running shoes because it invented a need by convincing people that we were supposed to be running on our heels all along instead of on the balls of our feet. In short, you must at the very least, invent a 'need'. If people don't understand why something will help them, it's rare that pure, directionless curiosity will bring them en mass to your company.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-21T17:26:27.213Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a89e68bfdc0428e7d8f7",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "If there is not a clearly defined ‘need’ that is fulfilled by the product your company offers, is it possible to still be successful?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c41dc594dcace72f5b9b",
                    "name": "Madeleine",
                    "email": "maddykindler11@yahoo.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-06-10T18:10:27.425Z",
                    "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-01-20T20:53:17.770Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6380a4c726e8e96705fbd213",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 1,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380a4c026e8e96705fbd1f1",
                        "answer": "hello",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6380a36026e8e96705fbcec5",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "hub@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "hub",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:13:36.316Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-27T05:21:11.380Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:19:35.713Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380a4eb26e8e96705fbd2f8",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 1,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380a4c026e8e96705fbd1f1",
                        "answer": "huhuh",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6380a36026e8e96705fbcec5",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "hub@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "hub",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:13:36.316Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-27T05:21:11.380Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:20:11.925Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380a50c26e8e96705fbd43c",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 1,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380a4c026e8e96705fbd1f1",
                        "answer": "hbhb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6380a36026e8e96705fbcec5",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "hub@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "hub",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:13:36.316Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-27T05:21:11.380Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:20:44.862Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380a50d26e8e96705fbd445",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 1,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380a4c026e8e96705fbd1f1",
                        "answer": "hbhb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6380a36026e8e96705fbcec5",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "hub@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "hub",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:13:36.316Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-27T05:21:11.380Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:20:45.679Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380a57e26e8e96705fbd753",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 1,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380a4c026e8e96705fbd1f1",
                        "answer": "uhyh",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6380a36026e8e96705fbcec5",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "hub@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "hub",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:13:36.316Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-27T05:21:11.380Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:22:38.133Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380ad63ace41d21e8a801fc",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "vbvc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:56:19.386Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380b92b1272880a7c8e4afc",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "vvcb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:46:35.938Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380b9351272880a7c8e4b78",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "vbvc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:46:45.783Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380b9381272880a7c8e4bc4",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "cvbvc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:46:48.884Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380b93e1272880a7c8e4c46",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "b",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:46:54.446Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380b93f1272880a7c8e4c81",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "vcb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:46:55.483Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380b9921272880a7c8e4cc8",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "ccb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:48:18.504Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380b9e21272880a7c8e4d14",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "hii",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:49:38.501Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380b9eb1272880a7c8e4d60",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "hi\n",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:49:47.276Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380ba38fb437e23e8038ede",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "hi",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:51:04.168Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380ba45fb437e23e8038f20",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "hi\n",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:51:17.734Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380ba4afb437e23e8038f62",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "hi",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:51:22.714Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380ba50fb437e23e8038fa4",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "test",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:51:28.532Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380ba72fb437e23e8038fe4",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "hi",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:52:02.133Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380ba7cfb437e23e8039046",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "hi",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:52:12.810Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380ba8bfb437e23e80390b4",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "hii",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:52:27.478Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380ba92fb437e23e8039100",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "hi",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:52:34.229Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380ba99fb437e23e8039140",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "hi\n",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:52:41.987Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380baa4fb437e23e8039182",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "hi\n\n",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:52:52.593Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380baabfb437e23e80391c4",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "hi\n",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:52:59.898Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380bab1fb437e23e8039204",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "hi",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:53:05.045Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380bab7fb437e23e8039246",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "hi\n\n",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:53:11.997Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380babefb437e23e8039288",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "hi",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:53:18.723Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380bac5fb437e23e80392c8",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "hi\n\n",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:53:25.834Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380bacefb437e23e8039306",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "h\n\n",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:53:34.630Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380bad2fb437e23e8039346",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "gh",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:53:38.665Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380bad6fb437e23e8039386",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "gsgfd",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:53:42.915Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380badafb437e23e80393c6",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "gfdsgdfg",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:53:46.838Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380bae2fb437e23e8039406",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "hi",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:53:54.110Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380bae8fb437e23e8039446",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "dfdaf",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:54:00.361Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380baedfb437e23e8039486",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "fdfads",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:54:05.143Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380baf3fb437e23e80394c6",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "dfasdfdsf",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:54:11.583Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380baf5fb437e23e8039506",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "d",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:54:13.420Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380baf6fb437e23e8039535",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "fdsf",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:54:14.472Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380baf7fb437e23e8039588",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "dfsd",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:54:15.832Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380bafafb437e23e80395c8",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "dfasd",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:54:18.058Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380bafcfb437e23e8039608",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "fsdf",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:54:20.303Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380bb06fb437e23e803965d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "cdscscdsdsc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:54:30.358Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380bb08fb437e23e80396b5",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "new",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:54:32.510Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380bb0dfb437e23e80396fe",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "hi",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:54:37.973Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380bb7353c4601d94a45eb5",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "hi\n",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:56:19.936Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380bb7953c4601d94a45f06",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "cdscscdsdsc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:56:25.657Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380bb7e53c4601d94a45f51",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "hi",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:56:30.786Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380bb8253c4601d94a45f91",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "fas",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:56:34.234Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380bb8853c4601d94a45fcf",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "fdf",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:56:40.176Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380bb8a53c4601d94a46011",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "fdsfsda",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:56:42.050Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380bb8f53c4601d94a46053",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "dfdfdf",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:56:47.347Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380bba753c4601d94a46091",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "hi\n",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:57:11.913Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380bbd034d836251053aa89",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "hi",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:57:52.891Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380bbd634d836251053aad4",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "cdscscdsdsc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:57:58.783Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380bbdb34d836251053ab21",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "hi",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:58:03.859Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380bc261ea7463a4c232234",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "hi\n",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:59:18.125Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380bc2d1ea7463a4c23228b",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "fefw",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:59:25.816Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380bc311ea7463a4c2322ce",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "df",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:59:29.195Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380bd2420f3e02274b5ca7c",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "new",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T13:03:32.977Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380bd2b20f3e02274b5cac3",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "dgsg",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T13:03:39.513Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380bdb682b248159c4f54b6",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "hi\n",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T13:05:58.215Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380bdbe82b248159c4f54ff",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "dgadgd",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T13:06:06.869Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380bdf57c311928ccadad8d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "dvgdsg",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T13:07:01.843Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380bdf87c311928ccadaddb",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "fsd",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T13:07:04.873Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380bdff7c311928ccadae2a",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "fsfesf",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T13:07:11.051Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380be057c311928ccadae65",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "fdsfdfdsg",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T13:07:17.251Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380be147c311928ccadaeac",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "fdfsdf",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T13:07:32.473Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6381981a3204af6a1170a4b5",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "vbnbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-26T04:37:46.895Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638198223204af6a1170a543",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380ad61ace41d21e8a801b8",
                        "answer": "bvnv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-26T04:37:54.717Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63847968dd20fd17320f9365",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63847952dd20fd17320f92f2",
                        "answer": "hello\n",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "63805a078760ee61cb82b662",
                            "currentRole": "Executive Vice President",
                            "email": "fal@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Fal",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-25T06:00:39.573Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:50:17.677Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T09:03:36.164Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63847998dd20fd17320f94a8",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63847952dd20fd17320f92f2",
                        "answer": "Hii",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "63805a078760ee61cb82b662",
                            "currentRole": "Executive Vice President",
                            "email": "fal@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Fal",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-25T06:00:39.573Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:50:17.677Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T09:04:24.310Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638479eadd20fd17320f9602",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63847952dd20fd17320f92f2",
                        "answer": "hjhjm kjm",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "63805a078760ee61cb82b662",
                            "currentRole": "Executive Vice President",
                            "email": "fal@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Fal",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-25T06:00:39.573Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:50:17.677Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T09:05:46.942Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63847a61dd20fd17320f9672",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63847952dd20fd17320f92f2",
                        "answer": "dgfgb ",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "63805a078760ee61cb82b662",
                            "currentRole": "Executive Vice President",
                            "email": "fal@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Fal",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-25T06:00:39.573Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:50:17.677Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T09:07:45.514Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63847a9edd20fd17320f96e1",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63847952dd20fd17320f92f2",
                        "answer": "refv ",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "63805a078760ee61cb82b662",
                            "currentRole": "Executive Vice President",
                            "email": "fal@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Fal",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-25T06:00:39.573Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:50:17.677Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380a4a126e8e96705fbd0ae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T09:08:46.409Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "What do you think of when you hear the word 'technology'?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                    "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                    "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                    "name": "Baju",
                    "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-11-25T11:18:57.362Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 75
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee58553e7ab6730c4e2",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a87f68bfdc0428e7d575",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee58553e7ab6730c4e2",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "One portion might be that it is one of the most dangerous trades by actuarial measures. If you want to draw in serious young people though, you might address ways they can be developed throughout the construction business, you might even highlight paths to retirement.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-12-07T22:23:51.295Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a87e68bfdc0428e7d573",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Why is it so difficult to find young people who are willing to get involved in the construction trades? There is a shortage of labor and many high paying skilled trades jobs are going unfilled.",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c417c594dcace72f5b45",
                    "name": "Scott Kuperman",
                    "email": "scott.kuperman@paintplatoon.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-05-04T18:23:00.565Z",
                    "currentRole": "President",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T16:24:41.811Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-12-07T03:58:58.024Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee58553e7ab6730c4e0",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a87d68bfdc0428e7d546",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee58553e7ab6730c4e0",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c417c594dcace72f5b45",
                            "name": "Scott Kuperman",
                            "email": "scott.kuperman@paintplatoon.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-05-04T18:23:00.565Z",
                            "currentRole": "President",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T16:24:41.811Z"
                        },
                        "answer": "You could give them gift VISA gift cards so they can get what they want, or sign up with THNKS. It's an app that allows you to share a HUGE variety of gifts from a cup of coffee to Kayaks. ",
                        "createdAt": "2021-12-07T03:55:09.098Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a87d68bfdc0428e7d544",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a87f68bfdc0428e7d57e",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee58553e7ab6730c4e0",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "You could probably ask them. But it might also be nice to reward them with a sort of team-building retreat in which they can enjoy each other outside the context of work.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-12-07T22:25:31.835Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a87f68bfdc0428e7d57c",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "After a rush of activity, I want to reward my team. Would gift certificates to an upscale spa in the area be too personal? Would it be strange to ask individuals if they would want this or something else?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c421c594dcace72f5be4",
                    "name": "Steven J. Pietras",
                    "email": "spietras43@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-07-13T15:28:46.788Z",
                    "currentRole": "Manager",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-29T15:36:07.160Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-12-06T16:31:38.528Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee78553e7ab6730c506",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8a068bfdc0428e7d959",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee78553e7ab6730c506",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                            "name": "Saima Omar",
                            "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "That's useful thank you!",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-23T03:20:47.525Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a89b68bfdc0428e7d878",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a89e68bfdc0428e7d8f0",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee78553e7ab6730c506",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "I have had some success with working with people through UpWork!",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-21T17:20:57.559Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a89b68bfdc0428e7d878",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a89b68bfdc0428e7d87a",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee78553e7ab6730c506",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "It might be wise to hire a market researcher to pinpoint some of these areas and trends for you!",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-13T16:24:37.245Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a89b68bfdc0428e7d878",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a89e68bfdc0428e7d8e9",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee78553e7ab6730c506",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                            "name": "Saima Omar",
                            "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Thank you. Can you recommend any market researchers?",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-19T02:48:48.757Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a89b68bfdc0428e7d878",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "I own an e-commerce business selling eco-friendly homewares in the USA. I am doing well in this market and I am at a stage where I am considering penetrating a new market. How do I go about choosing which countries to add to the list of where we can ship to? What research should I do? Do I need to market differently?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-01-07T14:14:37.211Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 4
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eef38553e7ab6730c5c4",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a82d68bfdc0428e7c9bc",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef38553e7ab6730c5c4",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c40ec594dcace72f5ab2",
                            "name": "Julia Feng",
                            "email": "julia@pcpcglobal.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-04-06T22:22:54.482Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "No, don't fight for anything. If you can get them effortlessly, you are in the right place doing the right things.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-04-20T08:32:46.792Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a82d68bfdc0428e7c9ba",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84568bfdc0428e7cd3b",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef38553e7ab6730c5c4",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c418c594dcace72f5b54",
                            "name": "Mark Lawson",
                            "email": "mrmglawson@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-05-07T12:07:54.565Z",
                            "currentRole": "President"
                        },
                        "answer": "It is not the money... it's the stuff",
                        "createdAt": "2021-07-14T15:43:02.120Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84568bfdc0428e7cd39",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a81768bfdc0428e7c6a9",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef38553e7ab6730c5c4",
                        "answer": "aa",
                        "createdAt": "2021-03-17T06:23:02.914Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a81768bfdc0428e7c6a7",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a83068bfdc0428e7ca2e",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef38553e7ab6730c5c4",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c40dc594dcace72f5a9f",
                            "name": "Sunil Deshmukh",
                            "email": "sd@sunil-deshmukh.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-04-02T04:17:25.511Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "No",
                        "createdAt": "2021-04-23T06:45:55.642Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a83068bfdc0428e7ca2c",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Is money worth fighting for ?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a29",
                    "name": "agim sallaku",
                    "email": "agimsallaku1976@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T14:36:43.301Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-03-09T19:36:50.595Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 4
            },
            {
                "_id": "6246d3eed500ad5097570e4f",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "625d21ddfc1660167be3e3e9",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 1,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "625d21bbfc1660167be3e3d9",
                        "answer": "Role of leadership is that, Leader will lead the whole team on his own responsibilities.",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6256d6b74f929c559b2183eb",
                            "currentRole": "Partner",
                            "email": "kevin088.rejoice@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Kevin",
                            "createdAt": "2022-04-13T13:57:11.884Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-15T09:09:19.527Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6246d3eed500ad5097570e4f",
                        "createdAt": "2022-04-18T08:31:25.047Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "hello what is important for leadership role ??",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "62454457db81be26054dc055",
                    "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                    "email": "hiteyaj889@procowork.com",
                    "name": "hiteyaj889",
                    "createdAt": "2022-03-31T06:04:07.679Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-03-31T06:04:07.680Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-04-01T10:29:02.910Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "625fd24afc1660167be40e98",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "62d8f605cccb7636d4a1a7fd",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "62d8f601cccb7636d4a1a7cf",
                        "answer": " selling more to existing profitable customers and finding similar customers to sell to.",
                        "question": "625fd24afc1660167be40e98",
                        "createdAt": "2022-07-21T06:45:25.150Z",
                        "__v": 0,
                        "downVote": 0,
                        "rating": 1,
                        "upVote": 1
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Different  ways to improve Profitability ",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-04-20T09:28:42.869Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeee8553e7ab6730c56b",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8be68bfdc0428e7ddac",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeee8553e7ab6730c56b",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "While this is a more passive approach, you may want to budget out longer payment intervals so that if you're waiting up to 60 days, you'll still be insulated from late payments. Another might be to require at least partial payment up front.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-03-03T18:46:02.085Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8be68bfdc0428e7ddaa",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8c168bfdc0428e7ddff",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeee8553e7ab6730c56b",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                            "name": "Saima Omar",
                            "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Thank you! What is your business?",
                        "createdAt": "2022-03-05T03:38:38.370Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8be68bfdc0428e7ddaa",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Founders - How do you deal with non-payment of invoice? Startup business and year 2 of trading. I need advice on how to ensure timely payments.",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-02-28T22:39:02.872Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eedf8553e7ab6730c482",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a85168bfdc0428e7cef6",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedf8553e7ab6730c482",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f05c594dcace72f5c5a",
                            "name": "Kuresha Ramahotar",
                            "email": "leana_r@hotmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-09-21T06:49:05.750Z",
                            "currentRole": "Other"
                        },
                        "answer": "Not resources specifically but I have been working remotely for quite a while and it is important to set boundaries, just like you leave for work when you have to commute there is a time where you sign in, take few breaks from the screen (have short breaks) and have a specific time to sign off. You may want to keep a buffer of 1h where you can attend to things that have not been planned. There are a lot of tips you can use to make sure you don't work non stop while working from home.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-09-21T07:00:20.243Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a85168bfdc0428e7cef4",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Do you know of any good resources for learning how to better maintain work-life balance while working entirely remote?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c41dc594dcace72f5b9b",
                    "name": "Madeleine",
                    "email": "maddykindler11@yahoo.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-06-10T18:10:27.425Z",
                    "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-09-20T20:22:06.272Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee28553e7ab6730c4b7",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "62b8dc85f6ac59655ddd9e55",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 1,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "62b8dc57f6ac59655ddd9e47",
                        "answer": "practice during team meetings",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "626591fb6b39681abb55d829",
                            "currentRole": "Product Manager",
                            "email": "christyz@stanford.edu",
                            "name": "Christy Wang",
                            "createdAt": "2022-04-24T18:07:55.617Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-05-09T05:35:10.337Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6229eee28553e7ab6730c4b7",
                        "createdAt": "2022-06-26T22:24:05.242Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How to build soft skill for analytics?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "62218f08c594dcace72f5c91",
                    "name": "conov24061",
                    "email": "conov24061@dukeoo.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-11-01T09:35:21.469Z",
                    "currentRole": "Product Manager"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-11-08T06:24:55.914Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eef18553e7ab6730c59c",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a81168bfdc0428e7c5c4",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef18553e7ab6730c59c",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3fdc594dcace72f599b",
                            "name": "Alison Bagwell",
                            "email": "abagwell@shieldtecinc.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-01-11T15:43:43.206Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "Ethics, morals, honesty, integrity, team work, thoughtfulness, empathy and compassion",
                        "createdAt": "2021-02-04T04:05:05.076Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a81168bfdc0428e7c5c2",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a81468bfdc0428e7c63f",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef18553e7ab6730c59c",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c402c594dcace72f59ef",
                            "name": "Joao Incio",
                            "email": "joaoincio@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-02-11T17:12:37.906Z",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Honesty, emphasis on personal values keeping employees at the core of the company's mission",
                        "createdAt": "2021-02-11T17:19:18.605Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a81468bfdc0428e7c63d",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "What qualities do you look for in future leaders?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3ecc594dcace72f58f5",
                    "name": "Claire Beltmann",
                    "email": "cbeltmann@luc.edu",
                    "createdAt": "2020-10-20T20:34:37.140Z",
                    "currentRole": "Assistant Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-02-01T18:28:50.840Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeda8553e7ab6730c43d",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a83568bfdc0428e7cae8",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeda8553e7ab6730c43d",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c416c594dcace72f5b31",
                            "name": "Todd Harrison",
                            "email": "todd.harrison@deltafaucet.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-04-30T11:58:30.420Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Executives need strong emotional intelligence to help them identify and support team members during times of change.  While not a skill, EQ can be developed with intentional focus. Another skill that is important during times of change is for the executive to help create a vision of the change that fits each team member's frame of reference. Help them understand the WIIFM (what's in it for me).",
                        "createdAt": "2021-04-30T12:16:55.084Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a83568bfdc0428e7cae6",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a83d68bfdc0428e7cbed",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeda8553e7ab6730c43d",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c41bc594dcace72f5b85",
                            "name": "ilhami idris",
                            "email": "ilhami@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-05-27T02:53:01.496Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "My experience: (1) team communication (for common messaging) and also one-on-one communication (for individual/personalised chat. Also to demonstrate consistency between team & individual messaging. (2) empathy. being there for the affected team member(s), listening to them, and working out together to address any concerns.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-05-27T08:14:39.540Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a83c68bfdc0428e7cbeb",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84e68bfdc0428e7ce76",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeda8553e7ab6730c43d",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f04c594dcace72f5c4d",
                            "name": "Robert Varnam",
                            "email": "robert@varnam.org.uk",
                            "createdAt": "2021-09-02T09:01:31.012Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "For me, it's about understanding the people and then understanding how the changes will look and feel from their perspective - rather than the other way round, which is how we often tend to do it. Most challenges or resistance to change that trip leaders up seem to be very personal and even \"emotional\" rather than corporate or \"rational\". Hope that helps. Do feel free to get in touch if you'd like to chat further - robert@varnam.org.uk",
                        "createdAt": "2021-09-02T09:30:11.107Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84e68bfdc0428e7ce74",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a83368bfdc0428e7ca90",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeda8553e7ab6730c43d",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c412c594dcace72f5af7",
                            "name": "George Kondrach",
                            "email": "gkondrach@amplikai.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-04-20T02:49:59.436Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "\"transitioning team\" and \"changing workplace\" require deep personal changes within each affected individual, to 'break the good habits that have now beccome outdated.' I suggest reviewing 'Fierce Conversations' [book by Susan Scott] and Root Cause Analysis [a Lean Method], and creating the pathway for each individual that reveal causes-and-effects that are supporting the need to change and evolve.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-04-29T17:34:35.194Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a83368bfdc0428e7ca8e",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Which leadership skills help executives to successfully transition their team members in the changing workplace?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3ecc594dcace72f58f8",
                    "name": "MollyDriscoll",
                    "email": "mdriscoll2@luc.edu",
                    "createdAt": "2020-10-07T01:12:14.277Z",
                    "currentRole": "CEO"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-04-21T16:53:33.488Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 4
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eedb8553e7ab6730c44c",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a83e68bfdc0428e7cc2b",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedb8553e7ab6730c44c",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c41cc594dcace72f5b95",
                            "name": "Alec Jiggins",
                            "email": "mralecjiggins@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-06-08T20:46:27.500Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "Hire a leadership coach.\nThey will lead you through a 360, identify blind spots and strengths, and coach you on improvement.\nI started using a coach 10 years ago and it was fantastic for my career. ",
                        "createdAt": "2021-06-09T21:01:12.342Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a83e68bfdc0428e7cc29",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "What are some effectives ways for leaders to focus on growth from new supervisors to C-suite executives?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3ecc594dcace72f58f8",
                    "name": "MollyDriscoll",
                    "email": "mdriscoll2@luc.edu",
                    "createdAt": "2020-10-07T01:12:14.277Z",
                    "currentRole": "CEO"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-05-26T18:27:08.447Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee98553e7ab6730c51c",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a89f68bfdc0428e7d92e",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee98553e7ab6730c51c",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "This is a simple fix depending on the environment that your organization cultivates. If you are addressing your mistake with peers there is not much to do besides own your mistake and demonstrate more diligence in the future. However, if you are addressing this with staff under you, the situation has two crucial prongs. If are part of an environment in which it is not okay to make a mistake, then this is a difficult situation. But it's an opportunity for you to turn the culture around. If you are running a growth-oriented team, this is a good time for you to lead by example, be outright about your mistake, and be humble about it. This can be an excellent opportunity for you to build rapport with your team members.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-21T20:08:33.055Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a89f68bfdc0428e7d92c",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "I am a leader of an organization. I have created a report and sent it to some members. I have been caught out by someone saying that I have made a mistake in the report. I have reported some wrong numbers and when looking at the feedback I realize my mistake. How can I best approach this situation without losing credibility and respect? I admit, I was rushing to complete this report and feel like I have done some damage by doing this mistake. How can a leader own their mistakes without losing face?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-01-18T15:42:38.978Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eef38553e7ab6730c5c3",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a82168bfdc0428e7c82a",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef38553e7ab6730c5c3",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c40bc594dcace72f5a77",
                            "name": "Rahul Sinha",
                            "email": "rahul.sinha1604@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-23T17:37:27.932Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "Yes. We at Medikin Healthcare are looking for an experienced person to join our board of directors and even join as a shareholder. Our annual report and financials are available on www.medikinhealthcare.com",
                        "createdAt": "2021-03-26T12:20:45.845Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a82168bfdc0428e7c828",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a82268bfdc0428e7c831",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef38553e7ab6730c5c3",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c40bc594dcace72f5a77",
                            "name": "Rahul Sinha",
                            "email": "rahul.sinha1604@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-23T17:37:27.932Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "if anyone is interested, kindly reach out to me.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-03-26T12:21:02.868Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a82168bfdc0428e7c828",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a82768bfdc0428e7c8ed",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef38553e7ab6730c5c3",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c411c594dcace72f5ae2",
                            "name": "Devin Marks",
                            "email": "devin.ridleymarks@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-04-16T02:36:55.760Z",
                            "currentRole": "President"
                        },
                        "answer": "Same here.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-04-17T01:39:45.377Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a82768bfdc0428e7c8eb",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Is anyone aware of an organization searching for a Board Member? If so, I would like to learn more.",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a25",
                    "name": "Christine Baranowski",
                    "email": "christinebaranowski2020@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-08T18:44:00.411Z",
                    "currentRole": "Executive Vice President"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-03-08T19:23:10.988Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 3
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee68553e7ab6730c4f0",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a89468bfdc0428e7d75f",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee68553e7ab6730c4f0",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3ecc594dcace72f58f8",
                            "name": "MollyDriscoll",
                            "email": "mdriscoll2@luc.edu",
                            "createdAt": "2020-10-07T01:12:14.277Z",
                            "currentRole": "CEO"
                        },
                        "answer": "I think we are learning more about effective leadership every day. Through personal experience and broader research, I believe empathy is essential to managing any team. If you don't treat people as people, they are less likely to be satisfied or happy and thus less productive.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-04T17:44:19.219Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a89468bfdc0428e7d75d",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8a768bfdc0428e7da55",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee68553e7ab6730c4f0",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "It's in the top 4, easily",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-03T16:44:25.462Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8a768bfdc0428e7da53",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Does empathy and vulnerability play a role in your leadership?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-12-20T15:59:12.982Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eef18553e7ab6730c5a2",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a81068bfdc0428e7c5a5",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef18553e7ab6730c5a2",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3fdc594dcace72f599b",
                            "name": "Alison Bagwell",
                            "email": "abagwell@shieldtecinc.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-01-11T15:43:43.206Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "Choosing people with character, starting with how the treat others, ensuring that they have skill sets that compliment and don't compete and ask them straight what their succession plan looks like in the first 30 days",
                        "createdAt": "2021-02-04T03:56:00.980Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a81068bfdc0428e7c5a3",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a81368bfdc0428e7c61e",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef18553e7ab6730c5a2",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3f5c594dcace72f591c",
                            "name": "Jim Red",
                            "email": "rojjim@hotmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2020-11-25T21:44:54.463Z",
                            "currentRole": "Manager"
                        },
                        "answer": "Emphasize on competence and integrity.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-02-06T00:49:52.205Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a81368bfdc0428e7c61c",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How are you cultivating the next generation of leaders within your organization?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3ecc594dcace72f58f5",
                    "name": "Claire Beltmann",
                    "email": "cbeltmann@luc.edu",
                    "createdAt": "2020-10-20T20:34:37.140Z",
                    "currentRole": "Assistant Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-02-03T17:09:18.091Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "628740be0a3ac94d3a4a9cf7",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6287414d0a3ac94d3a4aa0be",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6287413e0a3ac94d3a4aa081",
                        "answer": "this is EC ,Mech and IT Industry",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6285c9e5fa4fe26e5317abde",
                            "currentRole": "Founder",
                            "email": "pohebof666@dufeed.com",
                            "name": "Pohebof",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-19T04:39:01.637Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-05-20T12:59:59.029Z"
                        },
                        "question": "628740be0a3ac94d3a4a9cf7",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-20T07:20:45.671Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "628c9a1827105d3ea8e7d210",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "628c99f927105d3ea8e7d1f4",
                        "answer": "bvb",
                        "question": "628740be0a3ac94d3a4a9cf7",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-24T08:40:56.273Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "628daa3c942ead2b0d93d942",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "628c99f927105d3ea8e7d1f4",
                        "answer": "okay",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6284ce1afa4fe26e531732ab",
                            "currentRole": "Founder",
                            "email": "ligedov825@akapple.com",
                            "name": "Lige",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-18T10:44:42.887Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-03T12:51:10.092Z"
                        },
                        "question": "628740be0a3ac94d3a4a9cf7",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-25T04:02:04.753Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "628daa8c942ead2b0d93da22",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6287410a0a3ac94d3a4a9efe",
                        "answer": "okayyy thanks",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6284ce1afa4fe26e531732ab",
                            "currentRole": "Founder",
                            "email": "ligedov825@akapple.com",
                            "name": "Lige",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-18T10:44:42.887Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-03T12:51:10.092Z"
                        },
                        "question": "628740be0a3ac94d3a4a9cf7",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-25T04:03:24.829Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "628e1fa0942ead2b0d943f23",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "628c99f927105d3ea8e7d1f4",
                        "answer": "donee",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6284ce1afa4fe26e531732ab",
                            "currentRole": "Founder",
                            "email": "ligedov825@akapple.com",
                            "name": "Lige",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-18T10:44:42.887Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-03T12:51:10.092Z"
                        },
                        "question": "628740be0a3ac94d3a4a9cf7",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-25T12:22:56.383Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "628e22c5942ead2b0d944283",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "628c99f927105d3ea8e7d1f4",
                        "answer": "sikko",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6284ce1afa4fe26e531732ab",
                            "currentRole": "Founder",
                            "email": "ligedov825@akapple.com",
                            "name": "Lige",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-18T10:44:42.887Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-03T12:51:10.092Z"
                        },
                        "question": "628740be0a3ac94d3a4a9cf7",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-25T12:36:21.047Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "628eff85761b0b4044ccbdfb",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "628eff82761b0b4044ccbdd2",
                        "answer": "vcnbvn",
                        "question": "628740be0a3ac94d3a4a9cf7",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-26T04:18:13.383Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "628f46b233b93148ee7ddf7c",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6287410a0a3ac94d3a4a9efe",
                        "answer": "jdfjkdjg",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "624d5ba9d500ad509757879c",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer",
                            "email": "tehav55741@nuesond.com",
                            "name": "Tehav",
                            "createdAt": "2022-04-06T09:21:45.077Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-10-10T04:11:45.916Z"
                        },
                        "question": "628740be0a3ac94d3a4a9cf7",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-26T09:21:54.360Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "628f46ff33b93148ee7de3ac",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6287410a0a3ac94d3a4a9efe",
                        "answer": "okay ",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6284ce1afa4fe26e531732ab",
                            "currentRole": "Founder",
                            "email": "ligedov825@akapple.com",
                            "name": "Lige",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-18T10:44:42.887Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-03T12:51:10.092Z"
                        },
                        "question": "628740be0a3ac94d3a4a9cf7",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-26T09:23:11.187Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6290cc635de93c50a045ff85",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "628e1719942ead2b0d943289",
                        "answer": "okk",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6284ce1afa4fe26e531732ab",
                            "currentRole": "Founder",
                            "email": "ligedov825@akapple.com",
                            "name": "Lige",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-18T10:44:42.887Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-03T12:51:10.092Z"
                        },
                        "question": "628740be0a3ac94d3a4a9cf7",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-27T13:04:35.439Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6290ccaf5de93c50a0460091",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6287413e0a3ac94d3a4aa081",
                        "answer": "ec tech",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6284ce1afa4fe26e531732ab",
                            "currentRole": "Founder",
                            "email": "ligedov825@akapple.com",
                            "name": "Lige",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-18T10:44:42.887Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-03T12:51:10.092Z"
                        },
                        "question": "628740be0a3ac94d3a4a9cf7",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-27T13:05:51.375Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6290ce935de93c50a0460201",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6287410a0a3ac94d3a4a9efe",
                        "answer": "thanks",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6284ce1afa4fe26e531732ab",
                            "currentRole": "Founder",
                            "email": "ligedov825@akapple.com",
                            "name": "Lige",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-18T10:44:42.887Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-03T12:51:10.092Z"
                        },
                        "question": "628740be0a3ac94d3a4a9cf7",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-27T13:13:55.551Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6290d6f35de93c50a0461015",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6287413e0a3ac94d3a4aa081",
                        "answer": "combine techhhnology",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6284ce1afa4fe26e531732ab",
                            "currentRole": "Founder",
                            "email": "ligedov825@akapple.com",
                            "name": "Lige",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-18T10:44:42.887Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-03T12:51:10.092Z"
                        },
                        "question": "628740be0a3ac94d3a4a9cf7",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-27T13:49:39.650Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "hello robotics is the IT Industry or EC Industry?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6284ce1afa4fe26e531732ab",
                    "currentRole": "Founder",
                    "email": "ligedov825@akapple.com",
                    "name": "Lige",
                    "createdAt": "2022-05-18T10:44:42.887Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-03T12:51:10.092Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-05-20T07:18:22.780Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 13
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee88553e7ab6730c512",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a89b68bfdc0428e7d893",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee88553e7ab6730c512",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "Good day",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-13T16:28:05.621Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a89a68bfdc0428e7d86f",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "My business has just developed its first tier of new hires. But I'm having trouble letting go of the reigns. How will I know when somebody is ready for me to delegate harder tasks to them?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                    "name": "Daniel Daws",
                    "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                    "currentRole": "Founder"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-01-12T21:13:00.980Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "637f401027661551def108ea",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6381aa8b3204af6a1170b1b1",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6373a7eea5322d31357ff110"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6381aa833204af6a1170b170",
                        "answer": "test1.....",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f401027661551def108ea",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-26T05:56:27.826Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "tests",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6373a7eea5322d31357ff110",
                    "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer",
                    "email": "ym@yopmail.com",
                    "name": "Ym",
                    "createdAt": "2022-11-15T14:53:34.480Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:40.349Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-11-24T09:57:36.091Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eede8553e7ab6730c472",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84f68bfdc0428e7ceb3",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eede8553e7ab6730c472",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3ebc594dcace72f58e6",
                            "name": "Manoj Negi",
                            "email": "mannu1993negi@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2020-10-14T10:40:21.335Z",
                            "currentRole": "President",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-10-11T12:44:54.169Z"
                        },
                        "answer": "Helop",
                        "createdAt": "2021-09-06T07:44:30.348Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84f68bfdc0428e7ceb1",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Does anyone find it hard to find others who understand your responsibilities to talk about them with? How did you find someone who understands to listen?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c421c594dcace72f5be4",
                    "name": "Steven J. Pietras",
                    "email": "spietras43@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-07-13T15:28:46.788Z",
                    "currentRole": "Manager",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-29T15:36:07.160Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-08-26T14:10:22.352Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eef08553e7ab6730c59a",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a81168bfdc0428e7c5d9",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef08553e7ab6730c59a",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3fdc594dcace72f599b",
                            "name": "Alison Bagwell",
                            "email": "abagwell@shieldtecinc.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-01-11T15:43:43.206Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "Teach doctors how to listen, be compassionate- drop the text book and use your intuition. Medicine is not always prescriptive and one size fits all.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-02-04T04:10:14.825Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a81168bfdc0428e7c5d7",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "If you had the power to change one thing in the US health system, what would it be?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3ecc594dcace72f58f8",
                    "name": "MollyDriscoll",
                    "email": "mdriscoll2@luc.edu",
                    "createdAt": "2020-10-07T01:12:14.277Z",
                    "currentRole": "CEO"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-01-31T23:35:58.628Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "637f646032a19b46b84b2ea4",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "637f666a071e4808acc171ed",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f6666071e4808acc171b0",
                        "answer": "hiii\n",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f646032a19b46b84b2ea4",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T12:41:14.620Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "cvbvc",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "636b6ecb7a3ce63a87b809a1",
                    "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer",
                    "email": "vijay74@yopmail.com",
                    "name": "vijay",
                    "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:11:39.718Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-11-25T08:54:15.709Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-11-24T12:32:32.594Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeda8553e7ab6730c43a",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a83b68bfdc0428e7cbbd",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeda8553e7ab6730c43a",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c41bc594dcace72f5b84",
                            "name": "Eric Dupuis",
                            "email": "artonadigitaltechnology@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-05-27T00:41:06.166Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "by creating it ",
                        "createdAt": "2021-05-27T01:09:52.355Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a83b68bfdc0428e7cbbb",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a82f68bfdc0428e7c9fd",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeda8553e7ab6730c43a",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                            "name": "Saima Omar",
                            "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Marketing your coaching programme globally will require an in-depth analysis on how others in your niche are doing this. Some of the ideas for marketing your coaching services globally include:- Social Media Ad Campaigns to target geographical locations and interests- Website SEO to make yourself discoverable for relevant keywords and search phrases- PR and Speaking opportunities - Offer Magnet to capture email addresses and to use email marketing to nurture your prospects- Community Management (forums, such as Quora, Reddit, engaging in conversations in social media groups etc) I hope this gives you some food for thought. ",
                        "createdAt": "2021-04-21T01:43:41.984Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a82f68bfdc0428e7c9fb",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How to market a coaching program globally?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c40ec594dcace72f5ab2",
                    "name": "Julia Feng",
                    "email": "julia@pcpcglobal.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-04-06T22:22:54.482Z",
                    "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-04-20T08:20:06.414Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeda8553e7ab6730c43c",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a83068bfdc0428e7ca13",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeda8553e7ab6730c43c",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c40dc594dcace72f5a9f",
                            "name": "Sunil Deshmukh",
                            "email": "sd@sunil-deshmukh.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-04-02T04:17:25.511Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Managing Remote Meetings, Emotional Intellignce, Employee Trust.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-04-23T06:42:04.603Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a83068bfdc0428e7ca11",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a82f68bfdc0428e7ca06",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeda8553e7ab6730c43c",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c414c594dcace72f5b0b",
                            "name": "Paul Ryan Dannar",
                            "email": "pauldannar@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-04-22T13:28:40.895Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "Transition.   The pandemic caused multiple transitions to take place for most of us.  Some of the transitions were; moving from the office and creating a home office, becoming a home school teacher for your children, adjusting responsibilities for the home between spouse or partner, or adjusting to a new position or no work position.  Traditional forms of communication had to be adapted, thus TEAMS and other virtual meetings and workgroups have become the norm.  Virtual might be the new normal.. \nThus new and unfamiliar stressors entered our lives and may have caused strain on relationships because or normal ways of dealing with stress no longer worked for these new situations.  Now the issue is how might we return to a revised new normal --- yet another area for stress.  Can we get comfortable with a faster rate of change?",
                        "createdAt": "2021-04-22T14:02:59.623Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a82f68bfdc0428e7ca04",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a83868bfdc0428e7cb3d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeda8553e7ab6730c43c",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c418c594dcace72f5b54",
                            "name": "Mark Lawson",
                            "email": "mrmglawson@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-05-07T12:07:54.565Z",
                            "currentRole": "President"
                        },
                        "answer": "Team members are more stressed than some leaders realize. The challenge is to keep the employment relationship stable, predictable, reinforcing and uplifting.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-05-07T13:28:05.725Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a83768bfdc0428e7cb3b",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a83b68bfdc0428e7cbb0",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeda8553e7ab6730c43c",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c41bc594dcace72f5b84",
                            "name": "Eric Dupuis",
                            "email": "artonadigitaltechnology@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-05-27T00:41:06.166Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "adjust with people ",
                        "createdAt": "2021-05-27T01:08:17.661Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a83b68bfdc0428e7cbae",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a83168bfdc0428e7ca56",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeda8553e7ab6730c43c",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3ebc594dcace72f58e6",
                            "name": "Manoj Negi",
                            "email": "mannu1993negi@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2020-10-14T10:40:21.335Z",
                            "currentRole": "President",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-10-11T12:44:54.169Z"
                        },
                        "answer": "teststest",
                        "createdAt": "2021-04-29T12:10:46.963Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a83168bfdc0428e7ca54",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a83668bfdc0428e7caf5",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeda8553e7ab6730c43c",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c416c594dcace72f5b31",
                            "name": "Todd Harrison",
                            "email": "todd.harrison@deltafaucet.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-04-30T11:58:30.420Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "The biggest problem we faced during the pandemic was in getting or employees and leaders comfortable working in a virtual environment.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-04-30T12:18:18.576Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a83668bfdc0428e7caf3",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "What problems did you face in your organization during COVID-19?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c411c594dcace72f5ae7",
                    "name": "Jack Matthews",
                    "email": "jack@appcrates.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-04-16T18:11:48.789Z",
                    "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-04-21T11:22:36.807Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 6
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeee8553e7ab6730c569",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8bd68bfdc0428e7dd82",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeee8553e7ab6730c569",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3e5c594dcace72f5893",
                            "name": "Firzana",
                            "email": "firzana218@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-12-29T20:45:55.686Z",
                            "currentRole": "Other"
                        },
                        "answer": "I think targeting employee motivation, incentivization, and goal setting are the biggest and most effective ways to improve employee productivity.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-03-01T21:50:05.198Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8bd68bfdc0428e7dd80",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8bf68bfdc0428e7ddd4",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeee8553e7ab6730c569",
                        "answer": "The employees need to feel emotionally invested in the sucess of the company. If they do not buy into the company's mission, they will not have the motivation to go above and beyond.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-03-04T04:09:25.953Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8bf68bfdc0428e7ddd2",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8bc68bfdc0428e7dd55",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeee8553e7ab6730c569",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                            "name": "Saima Omar",
                            "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Understanding your employees will help you empower them. Incetivise them to work to their potential.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-03-01T01:15:25.725Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8bc68bfdc0428e7dd53",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "62bc12aaf6ac59655ddea277",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "62bc129af6ac59655ddea254",
                        "answer": "dscfdscdfsvc https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_30Nn8urbmU&list=PL8p2I9GklV44X970xDCQvts19-0XQWMeA",
                        "question": "6229eeee8553e7ab6730c569",
                        "createdAt": "2022-06-29T08:51:54.414Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How can employee productivity be improved within a work space?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3e6c594dcace72f58aa",
                    "name": "Amarachi Emezie",
                    "email": "amarachieemezie@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2022-01-12T18:41:13.277Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-05-09T15:13:09.331Z",
                    "currentRole": "Other"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-02-25T18:23:49.991Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 4
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeef8553e7ab6730c588",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "623192831a063710a820aa6f",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeef8553e7ab6730c588",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3fac594dcace72f5963",
                            "name": "V Boss",
                            "email": "cyp@inscriptio.in",
                            "createdAt": "2020-12-21T05:09:58.438Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "yes",
                        "createdAt": "2020-12-30T13:07:08.059Z",
                        "roomId": "623192831a063710a820aa6d",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "623192841a063710a820aa98",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeef8553e7ab6730c588",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3fac594dcace72f5963",
                            "name": "V Boss",
                            "email": "cyp@inscriptio.in",
                            "createdAt": "2020-12-21T05:09:58.438Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "yes",
                        "createdAt": "2020-12-31T05:00:09.397Z",
                        "roomId": "623192831a063710a820aa6d",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231928b1a063710a820ab55",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeef8553e7ab6730c588",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3fac594dcace72f5963",
                            "name": "V Boss",
                            "email": "cyp@inscriptio.in",
                            "createdAt": "2020-12-21T05:09:58.438Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "yes",
                        "createdAt": "2021-01-11T10:17:48.658Z",
                        "roomId": "623192831a063710a820aa6d",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a81268bfdc0428e7c5f3",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeef8553e7ab6730c588",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3fdc594dcace72f599b",
                            "name": "Alison Bagwell",
                            "email": "abagwell@shieldtecinc.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-01-11T15:43:43.206Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "yes",
                        "createdAt": "2021-02-04T04:12:31.724Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a81268bfdc0428e7c5f1",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "623192831a063710a820aa76",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeef8553e7ab6730c588",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3fac594dcace72f5963",
                            "name": "V Boss",
                            "email": "cyp@inscriptio.in",
                            "createdAt": "2020-12-21T05:09:58.438Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "yes",
                        "createdAt": "2020-12-30T13:07:19.475Z",
                        "roomId": "623192831a063710a820aa6d",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "623192851a063710a820aab9",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeef8553e7ab6730c588",
                        "answer": "https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1AwzxO8tC0wPFbXK5bgdNuDSUHjTYAz22WjBJ5EZsQlU/edit?ts=5feecd1e#gid=83600793",
                        "createdAt": "2021-01-02T07:01:56.212Z",
                        "roomId": "623192851a063710a820aab7",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a82c68bfdc0428e7c9a2",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeef8553e7ab6730c588",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c411c594dcace72f5ae2",
                            "name": "Devin Marks",
                            "email": "devin.ridleymarks@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-04-16T02:36:55.760Z",
                            "currentRole": "President"
                        },
                        "answer": "Ha. Great question. These things start slowly... Patience grasshopper.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-04-17T01:47:20.851Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a82c68bfdc0428e7c9a0",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Is anyone else on the platform?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3fbc594dcace72f5971",
                    "name": "Howard Koenig",
                    "email": "howard.koenig@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2020-12-27T21:46:42.998Z",
                    "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer"
                },
                "createdAt": "2020-12-27T22:01:19.512Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 7
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee98553e7ab6730c516",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8a268bfdc0428e7d993",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee98553e7ab6730c516",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "Ideally, everyone at the table this early on should be dialoguing about their objectives, building their cases for why they ought to be high priority with the team corroborating these priorities according to its alignment and the perceived utility of the objectives of each person",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-26T15:26:31.092Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8a268bfdc0428e7d991",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8a168bfdc0428e7d974",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee98553e7ab6730c516",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c40dc594dcace72f5aa7",
                            "name": "Nick Welham",
                            "email": "nick.welham@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-04-04T16:02:49.314Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-07T12:56:16.743Z"
                        },
                        "answer": "I would suggest two things. Firstly, develop a strategy map that links tangible goals/objectives to the elements (and only the elements) that are necessary to complete them. Assign one person as responsible for that area and make them honestly show the status as red/orange/green on the map. That gives you your strategic resource allocation and makes it easy to stop pet projects that are wasting time and money. Secondly, practice a meeting technique called qualified consensus - everyone gets their say and feels heard, but you as the leader remain in control. Let me know if you'd like more information about either of these ideas.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-25T21:58:27.450Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8a168bfdc0428e7d972",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Everyone comes to the table with a unique set of objectives, expecting that most of them will be met. And, unfortunately, what’s important to one stakeholder may not even be on the radar of another. How do we all prioritize what we see as the most important? Should that be me, as the CEO?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-01-17T16:35:23.819Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eedf8553e7ab6730c485",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a85168bfdc0428e7ceff",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedf8553e7ab6730c485",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c421c594dcace72f5be4",
                            "name": "Steven J. Pietras",
                            "email": "spietras43@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-07-13T15:28:46.788Z",
                            "currentRole": "Manager",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-29T15:36:07.160Z"
                        },
                        "answer": "THIS IS A TEST ANSWER",
                        "createdAt": "2021-09-21T19:26:02.200Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a85168bfdc0428e7cefd",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "THIS IS A TEST POST. IGNORE.",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "62218f00c594dcace72f5c24",
                    "name": "Steven Pietras",
                    "email": "norgoth12@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-08-07T15:35:10.381Z",
                    "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-09-21T19:25:31.873Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee98553e7ab6730c518",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8a068bfdc0428e7d940",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee98553e7ab6730c518",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "There is not a single answer for this. It requires getting to know the difficult members of your team, and understanding where their issues are coming from.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-21T20:09:57.146Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8a068bfdc0428e7d93e",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How do you manage difficult people?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-01-17T16:40:21.995Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "637da8621a33343c8375a707",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "637f44c0e400dd5c6c8716cd",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637ddd51a00c393d8f8b828f",
                        "answer": "hii",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637da81d1a33343c8375a58a",
                            "currentRole": "Manager",
                            "email": "vijay087.rejoice@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-23T04:57:01.461Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-23T04:57:01.462Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637da8621a33343c8375a707",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T10:17:36.642Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "This is new funtions ??",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "637da81d1a33343c8375a58a",
                    "currentRole": "Manager",
                    "email": "vijay087.rejoice@yopmail.com",
                    "name": "vijay",
                    "createdAt": "2022-11-23T04:57:01.461Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-11-23T04:57:01.462Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-11-23T04:58:10.697Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6244bf6cdb81be26054db0e4",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "624a04b0d500ad50975724a0",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "624a048ad500ad50975723f8",
                        "answer": "Asana isn't a bad platform for project management.",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "624a0387d500ad509757227b",
                            "currentRole": "Other",
                            "email": "mblanton@gmail.com",
                            "name": "MichaelBlanton",
                            "createdAt": "2022-04-03T20:28:55.906Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-04-25T00:11:15.355Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6244bf6cdb81be26054db0e4",
                        "createdAt": "2022-04-03T20:33:52.582Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "624c9a5cd500ad50975754ff",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "624c9a0dd500ad50975754db",
                        "answer": "Jira, Dev Azure Board",
                        "question": "6244bf6cdb81be26054db0e4",
                        "createdAt": "2022-04-05T19:37:00.523Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "What are the best project management tools for managers?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6238e14fd611f8193cb476db",
                    "currentRole": "Other",
                    "email": "irakozepremices10@gmail.com",
                    "name": "Premices Irakoze",
                    "createdAt": "2022-03-21T20:34:23.277Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-03-21T20:34:23.278Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-03-30T20:37:00.835Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeee8553e7ab6730c564",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8bb68bfdc0428e7dd27",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeee8553e7ab6730c564",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3e6c594dcace72f58aa",
                            "name": "Amarachi Emezie",
                            "email": "amarachieemezie@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2022-01-12T18:41:13.277Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-05-09T15:13:09.331Z",
                            "currentRole": "Other"
                        },
                        "answer": "Before applying to a startup incubator it is important to self evaluate your business. Here are a list of questions you should ask yourself before applying:    -Is this the right time to start my business? (what does the market look like for the startup in question)                                                                                                     -How would the incubator benefit you? (what are you looking to get out of the incubator)                                                                                                                          -What is the niche of your startup and make sure that it aligns with the niche of the incubator.                                                                                                            -Are you ready to listen and adapt to advice given? (open-mind is necessary to get your start-up ahead)                                                                                          -How solid is your team? (make sure you have the people you want working on the startup figured out and weed out the ones who are prolonging advancement.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-25T17:43:50.877Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8bb68bfdc0428e7dd25",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "What are some things that I should consider before applying to a startup incubator?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3e5c594dcace72f5893",
                    "name": "Firzana",
                    "email": "firzana218@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-12-29T20:45:55.686Z",
                    "currentRole": "Other"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-02-24T22:29:41.386Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "623a46f9d611f8193cb49688",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "623ac2e1d611f8193cb497ec",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "623ac2aed611f8193cb497d2",
                        "answer": "You need to have DevOps engineer who knows AWS well and is able to configure your infra on AWS",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "623ac1d9d611f8193cb4971c",
                            "currentRole": "Co-Founder",
                            "email": "alla@maddevs.io",
                            "name": "Alla Klimenko",
                            "createdAt": "2022-03-23T06:44:41.192Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-03-23T06:44:41.193Z"
                        },
                        "question": "623a46f9d611f8193cb49688",
                        "createdAt": "2022-03-23T06:49:05.956Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "623acda4d611f8193cb49b53",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "623acd0dd611f8193cb49b2f",
                        "answer": "1. Start with simple and bare minimum services in AWS. 2. Do not introduce any new service unless it is really needed. 3. Keep your architecture simple to begin with. 4. Monitor cost and try to find alternatives",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "623acbe7d611f8193cb49a57",
                            "currentRole": "Director",
                            "email": "mailtovimal@gmail.com",
                            "name": "Vimal Patel",
                            "createdAt": "2022-03-23T07:27:35.047Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-03-23T07:27:35.047Z"
                        },
                        "question": "623a46f9d611f8193cb49688",
                        "createdAt": "2022-03-23T07:35:00.016Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6265eb4c6b39681abb55db74",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 1,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6265eaea6b39681abb55db65",
                        "answer": "apply for Activate. keep in mind you most likely won’t need to use ec2 at all - you can most likely run what you need using serverless tech and keep monthly compute costs at $0 for a long time. ",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "624a0387d500ad509757227b",
                            "currentRole": "Other",
                            "email": "mblanton@gmail.com",
                            "name": "MichaelBlanton",
                            "createdAt": "2022-04-03T20:28:55.906Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-04-25T00:11:15.355Z"
                        },
                        "question": "623a46f9d611f8193cb49688",
                        "createdAt": "2022-04-25T00:29:00.939Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How do I use AWS effectively to build the startup?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "623a45fed611f8193cb49586",
                    "currentRole": "Co-Founder",
                    "email": "champ.kanwar@gmail.com",
                    "name": "Kanwar Gill",
                    "createdAt": "2022-03-22T21:56:14.418Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-03-22T21:56:14.418Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-03-22T22:00:25.675Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 3
            },
            {
                "_id": "62b9c997f6ac59655dddc12f",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "62be729df6ac59655ddf210d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "62be7278f6ac59655ddf20d4",
                        "answer": "You need to take experience to do tech startup",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6256d6b74f929c559b2183eb",
                            "currentRole": "Partner",
                            "email": "kevin088.rejoice@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Kevin",
                            "createdAt": "2022-04-13T13:57:11.884Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-15T09:09:19.527Z"
                        },
                        "question": "62b9c997f6ac59655dddc12f",
                        "createdAt": "2022-07-01T04:05:49.400Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How are tech startups dealing with layoffs given how the market is? ",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "62b9c632f6ac59655dddbd5c",
                    "currentRole": "Co-Founder",
                    "email": "criojasp@nd.edu",
                    "name": "Cristina Riojas",
                    "createdAt": "2022-06-27T15:01:06.793Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-07-01T14:41:37.907Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-06-27T15:15:35.048Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeda8553e7ab6730c439",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a83b68bfdc0428e7cbc6",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeda8553e7ab6730c439",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c41bc594dcace72f5b84",
                            "name": "Eric Dupuis",
                            "email": "artonadigitaltechnology@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-05-27T00:41:06.166Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "cause we will change the world with it it’s Called Nano Neural Bio Computer ",
                        "createdAt": "2021-05-27T01:10:45.873Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a83b68bfdc0428e7cbc4",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Why do these questions seem so health-care heavy?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c411c594dcace72f5ae2",
                    "name": "Devin Marks",
                    "email": "devin.ridleymarks@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-04-16T02:36:55.760Z",
                    "currentRole": "President"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-04-17T01:43:36.978Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "637f56fb27661551def12332",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "637f57a927661551def12847",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f57a627661551def12807",
                        "answer": "Hello\n",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637e232d7b05b546b090d437",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer",
                            "email": "nal@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Nal",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-23T13:42:05.462Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-25T05:58:30.053Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f56fb27661551def12332",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T11:38:17.361Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "mg t",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "637f550e27661551def11ecb",
                    "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer",
                    "email": "hju@yopmail.com",
                    "name": "Hju",
                    "createdAt": "2022-11-24T11:27:10.003Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-11-24T12:04:13.878Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-11-24T11:35:23.753Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeed8553e7ab6730c555",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8ba68bfdc0428e7dd03",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeed8553e7ab6730c555",
                        "answer": "You have to ask: where are your fundings coming from? If you have an owner who can fund their start-up forever independent of how well the start-up is actually doing, I would consider that finalcially healthy becasue it is sustainable. You could also, for example, apply for grants or have pro bono resources which would hopefully allow for driving down expenses and increasing revenue.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-24T01:55:13.221Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8ba68bfdc0428e7dd01",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How do you define 'financial health' for startups - and how do you determine your own startup's financial health?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c41dc594dcace72f5b9b",
                    "name": "Madeleine",
                    "email": "maddykindler11@yahoo.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-06-10T18:10:27.425Z",
                    "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-02-18T20:28:32.103Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eedf8553e7ab6730c48b",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a85268bfdc0428e7cf22",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedf8553e7ab6730c48b",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f04c594dcace72f5c4e",
                            "name": "Iryna Chaban",
                            "email": "irynachaban98@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-09-07T19:20:12.002Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "Sad to hear about your issues with an employee. You already communicated about her performance problems, so the next best step is to do a performance review and let them know about the results and how they will impact their current position. Make sure you complete the termination confidentially and legally while still maintaining gratitude for the work they have done!",
                        "createdAt": "2021-09-29T00:06:59.998Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a85268bfdc0428e7cf20",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a85468bfdc0428e7cf82",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedf8553e7ab6730c48b",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                            "name": "Saima Omar",
                            "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Thank you, this is my thinking exactly. Performance review is the next option. Have you ever been in a similar situation?",
                        "createdAt": "2021-10-01T18:10:39.167Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a85268bfdc0428e7cf20",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a85268bfdc0428e7cf34",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedf8553e7ab6730c48b",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c413c594dcace72f5b03",
                            "name": "Arijit Basu",
                            "email": "arijitb962@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-04-21T07:34:56.909Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "If you are convinced that the person has attitude issue, it is always better for the organisation to part with such employees. However, to be fair to this person in this specific case, the matter may be approached as below;\n- you may share specifics of your concern or dissatisfaction highlighting clearly wherever you feel a better attitude from her could have resolved the matters. Then to let her know that still you would like to give her a fair chance and in that aspect you would like her to propose 1-3 key impact projects / assignments in her domain which she is confident of implementing within a given time suitable as per her. However if she fails to deliver, you would be left with no other option but to part as good friend. \nThe benefit of this approach is if she succeeds you would have a reformed person with experience while if she fails you can actually terminate her where she knows you gave her a good last chance! ",
                        "createdAt": "2021-09-30T07:53:46.014Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a85268bfdc0428e7cf32",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a85468bfdc0428e7cf7b",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedf8553e7ab6730c48b",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                            "name": "Saima Omar",
                            "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Thank you! This is a really great way for me to approach the situation. What a wonderful well thought-out response.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-10-01T18:09:37.401Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a85268bfdc0428e7cf32",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a85568bfdc0428e7cfa5",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedf8553e7ab6730c48b",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f04c594dcace72f5c4e",
                            "name": "Iryna Chaban",
                            "email": "irynachaban98@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-09-07T19:20:12.002Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "I havent personally had that experience, but some of my covorkers did!",
                        "createdAt": "2021-10-07T13:50:36.648Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a85268bfdc0428e7cf20",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a85868bfdc0428e7d010",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedf8553e7ab6730c48b",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c413c594dcace72f5b03",
                            "name": "Arijit Basu",
                            "email": "arijitb962@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-04-21T07:34:56.909Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "happy that you found my input valuable. good luck! ",
                        "createdAt": "2021-10-12T06:27:45.926Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a85268bfdc0428e7cf32",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "I am thinking of letting an employee go, even though she has been with my company for three years. I feel she brings a poor attitude to work, which rubs off on newer colleagues. She's often late, she's not accountable and I think she is not taking on board feedback. I'm having 1-on-1 discussions with her to express how I feel about her work ethic, but see no change. I would like advice on what steps I should take before formally dismissing her.",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-09-27T15:52:00.516Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 6
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eef08553e7ab6730c591",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a80a68bfdc0428e7c4dd",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef08553e7ab6730c591",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3fdc594dcace72f599f",
                            "name": "Test 30",
                            "email": "test30@inscriptio.in",
                            "createdAt": "2021-01-13T06:23:05.122Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "COVID 19",
                        "createdAt": "2021-01-13T09:07:32.518Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a80a68bfdc0428e7c4db",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "do you know about covid",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3fcc594dcace72f5986",
                    "name": "Hema P H",
                    "email": "hema.vayuz@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-01-06T10:14:53.946Z",
                    "currentRole": "Manager"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-01-06T12:54:38.664Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee48553e7ab6730c4d4",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a87868bfdc0428e7d484",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee48553e7ab6730c4d4",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3f5c594dcace72f591c",
                            "name": "Jim Red",
                            "email": "rojjim@hotmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2020-11-25T21:44:54.463Z",
                            "currentRole": "Manager"
                        },
                        "answer": "Prioritize fixing issues at home first.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-12-01T00:05:21.223Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a87868bfdc0428e7d482",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a87668bfdc0428e7d454",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee48553e7ab6730c4d4",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f00c594dcace72f5c24",
                            "name": "Steven Pietras",
                            "email": "norgoth12@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-08-07T15:35:10.381Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "This is surely a common problem. Encourging each other to immediately speak up if you feel that one side is impacting the other might be helpful. Acknowledging these moments and processing them as soon as they are noticed might not help seperate that two, but it would make you both more aware. (I have had to work through a similar problem with my own spouse)",
                        "createdAt": "2021-11-29T17:43:13.739Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a87668bfdc0428e7d452",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a87968bfdc0428e7d4ad",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee48553e7ab6730c4d4",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                            "name": "Saima Omar",
                            "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Thank you for your response. Much appreciated.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-12-01T14:39:38.577Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a87868bfdc0428e7d482",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a87968bfdc0428e7d4a6",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee48553e7ab6730c4d4",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                            "name": "Saima Omar",
                            "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Thank you for such a thoughtful response. Communication is definitely something we should work on. It's a common problem for sure.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-12-01T14:39:24.380Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a87668bfdc0428e7d452",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8a968bfdc0428e7da9d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee48553e7ab6730c4d4",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "Seek a marriage counselor!",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-03T21:16:05.564Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8a968bfdc0428e7da9b",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "I am a founder of a fairly new business with my spouse. She is the co-founder. How do we keep our personal matters and sour moods towards one another out of business life? Recently, we are disagreeing on certain things in the home, but it's transferring into our professional life. How can we draw that line? Any advice appreciated.",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-11-24T15:23:03.106Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 5
            },
            {
                "_id": "63844feb117fe41bd0bebd27",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "63844ff8117fe41bd0bebe95",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63844ff5117fe41bd0bebe53",
                        "answer": "cvbcv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63844feb117fe41bd0bebd27",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T06:06:48.779Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "cvbcvbvcv",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79",
                    "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                    "email": "vijay789@yopmail.com",
                    "name": "vijay",
                    "createdAt": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-11-28T06:06:35.249Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee48553e7ab6730c4d1",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a87568bfdc0428e7d40b",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee48553e7ab6730c4d1",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "In theory, yes. There is an excellent chance to see where we could both be better serving our communities. However, if there is not a relationship of trust and goodwill, then the outreach will go nowhere.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-11-23T22:02:45.765Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a87468bfdc0428e7d409",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a87668bfdc0428e7d442",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee48553e7ab6730c4d1",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f00c594dcace72f5c24",
                            "name": "Steven Pietras",
                            "email": "norgoth12@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-08-07T15:35:10.381Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "That seems reasonable. I think going into such discussions with the specific intent to foster trust and goodwill will be important to me going forward.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-11-29T17:10:56.424Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a87468bfdc0428e7d409",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a87768bfdc0428e7d47b",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee48553e7ab6730c4d1",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3f5c594dcace72f591c",
                            "name": "Jim Red",
                            "email": "rojjim@hotmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2020-11-25T21:44:54.463Z",
                            "currentRole": "Manager"
                        },
                        "answer": "Yes, I see no problem with that.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-12-01T00:03:12.625Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a87768bfdc0428e7d479",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Competition vs cooperation. Would you appreciate a competing organization reaching out to you to discuss pros/cons in the areas you both market to?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "62218f00c594dcace72f5c24",
                    "name": "Steven Pietras",
                    "email": "norgoth12@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-08-07T15:35:10.381Z",
                    "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-11-22T16:13:24.221Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 3
            },
            {
                "_id": "6287401d0a3ac94d3a4a9936",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "628ccd5efb264024cb1f58c6",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "628ccd39fb264024cb1f5894",
                        "answer": "TCS Is the best performer company in IT Industry",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "628cc9d1fb264024cb1f5579",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "jewiwib825@akapple.com",
                            "name": "jewiwi",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-24T12:04:33.320Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-05-24T12:06:49.575Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6287401d0a3ac94d3a4a9936",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-24T12:19:42.715Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "628ccdaefb264024cb1f5a69",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "628ccd39fb264024cb1f5894",
                        "answer": "ok",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "624d5ba9d500ad509757879c",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer",
                            "email": "tehav55741@nuesond.com",
                            "name": "Tehav",
                            "createdAt": "2022-04-06T09:21:45.077Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-10-10T04:11:45.916Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6287401d0a3ac94d3a4a9936",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-24T12:21:02.795Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "628cd01dfb264024cb1f5f5a",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "628ccd39fb264024cb1f5894",
                        "answer": "done",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "624d5ba9d500ad509757879c",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer",
                            "email": "tehav55741@nuesond.com",
                            "name": "Tehav",
                            "createdAt": "2022-04-06T09:21:45.077Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-10-10T04:11:45.916Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6287401d0a3ac94d3a4a9936",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-24T12:31:25.497Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "628cd033fb264024cb1f5fec",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "628ccd39fb264024cb1f5894",
                        "answer": "working",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "624d5ba9d500ad509757879c",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer",
                            "email": "tehav55741@nuesond.com",
                            "name": "Tehav",
                            "createdAt": "2022-04-06T09:21:45.077Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-10-10T04:11:45.916Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6287401d0a3ac94d3a4a9936",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-24T12:31:47.036Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "628cd257fb264024cb1f62d7",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "628ccd39fb264024cb1f5894",
                        "answer": "test1",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "624d5ba9d500ad509757879c",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer",
                            "email": "tehav55741@nuesond.com",
                            "name": "Tehav",
                            "createdAt": "2022-04-06T09:21:45.077Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-10-10T04:11:45.916Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6287401d0a3ac94d3a4a9936",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-24T12:40:55.953Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "628cd2d4fb264024cb1f6452",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "628cd2c7fb264024cb1f642b",
                        "answer": "Mahindra ",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6284ce1afa4fe26e531732ab",
                            "currentRole": "Founder",
                            "email": "ligedov825@akapple.com",
                            "name": "Lige",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-18T10:44:42.887Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-03T12:51:10.092Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6287401d0a3ac94d3a4a9936",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-24T12:43:00.253Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "628cd2e6fb264024cb1f64cb",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "628cd2c7fb264024cb1f642b",
                        "answer": "okay thanks",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "624d5ba9d500ad509757879c",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer",
                            "email": "tehav55741@nuesond.com",
                            "name": "Tehav",
                            "createdAt": "2022-04-06T09:21:45.077Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-10-10T04:11:45.916Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6287401d0a3ac94d3a4a9936",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-24T12:43:18.016Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "628cd563fb264024cb1f69fa",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "628ccd39fb264024cb1f5894",
                        "answer": "reee",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "624d5ba9d500ad509757879c",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer",
                            "email": "tehav55741@nuesond.com",
                            "name": "Tehav",
                            "createdAt": "2022-04-06T09:21:45.077Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-10-10T04:11:45.916Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6287401d0a3ac94d3a4a9936",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-24T12:53:55.498Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "628cd57cfb264024cb1f6aa2",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "628cd2c7fb264024cb1f642b",
                        "answer": "fff",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "624d5ba9d500ad509757879c",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer",
                            "email": "tehav55741@nuesond.com",
                            "name": "Tehav",
                            "createdAt": "2022-04-06T09:21:45.077Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-10-10T04:11:45.916Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6287401d0a3ac94d3a4a9936",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-24T12:54:20.953Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "628cdb31942ead2b0d93a2c8",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "628ccd39fb264024cb1f5894",
                        "answer": "okay",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "624d5ba9d500ad509757879c",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer",
                            "email": "tehav55741@nuesond.com",
                            "name": "Tehav",
                            "createdAt": "2022-04-06T09:21:45.077Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-10-10T04:11:45.916Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6287401d0a3ac94d3a4a9936",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-24T13:18:41.004Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "628cdb6f942ead2b0d93a39e",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "628cd2c7fb264024cb1f642b",
                        "answer": "okay",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "624d5ba9d500ad509757879c",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer",
                            "email": "tehav55741@nuesond.com",
                            "name": "Tehav",
                            "createdAt": "2022-04-06T09:21:45.077Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-10-10T04:11:45.916Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6287401d0a3ac94d3a4a9936",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-24T13:19:43.233Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "628cdd06942ead2b0d93a516",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "628cd2c7fb264024cb1f642b",
                        "answer": "testtt done\n",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "624d5ba9d500ad509757879c",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer",
                            "email": "tehav55741@nuesond.com",
                            "name": "Tehav",
                            "createdAt": "2022-04-06T09:21:45.077Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-10-10T04:11:45.916Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6287401d0a3ac94d3a4a9936",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-24T13:26:30.831Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "628cdd27942ead2b0d93a5e6",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "628cd2c7fb264024cb1f642b",
                        "answer": "okay",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "624d5ba9d500ad509757879c",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer",
                            "email": "tehav55741@nuesond.com",
                            "name": "Tehav",
                            "createdAt": "2022-04-06T09:21:45.077Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-10-10T04:11:45.916Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6287401d0a3ac94d3a4a9936",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-24T13:27:03.852Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "628cdecb942ead2b0d93a7c6",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "628cd2c7fb264024cb1f642b",
                        "answer": "working",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "624d5ba9d500ad509757879c",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer",
                            "email": "tehav55741@nuesond.com",
                            "name": "Tehav",
                            "createdAt": "2022-04-06T09:21:45.077Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-10-10T04:11:45.916Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6287401d0a3ac94d3a4a9936",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-24T13:34:03.020Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "628cdffb942ead2b0d93a962",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "628cd2c7fb264024cb1f642b",
                        "answer": "ohh",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "624d5ba9d500ad509757879c",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer",
                            "email": "tehav55741@nuesond.com",
                            "name": "Tehav",
                            "createdAt": "2022-04-06T09:21:45.077Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-10-10T04:11:45.916Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6287401d0a3ac94d3a4a9936",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-24T13:39:07.601Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "628ce006942ead2b0d93a9fa",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "628cd2c7fb264024cb1f642b",
                        "answer": "rr",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "624d5ba9d500ad509757879c",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer",
                            "email": "tehav55741@nuesond.com",
                            "name": "Tehav",
                            "createdAt": "2022-04-06T09:21:45.077Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-10-10T04:11:45.916Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6287401d0a3ac94d3a4a9936",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-24T13:39:18.905Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "628ce0b0942ead2b0d93abef",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "628ccd39fb264024cb1f5894",
                        "answer": "lets go",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "624d5ba9d500ad509757879c",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer",
                            "email": "tehav55741@nuesond.com",
                            "name": "Tehav",
                            "createdAt": "2022-04-06T09:21:45.077Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-10-10T04:11:45.916Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6287401d0a3ac94d3a4a9936",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-24T13:42:08.871Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "hello what’s is the best performer in IT Industry Auuutomation ?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "624d5ba9d500ad509757879c",
                    "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer",
                    "email": "tehav55741@nuesond.com",
                    "name": "Tehav",
                    "createdAt": "2022-04-06T09:21:45.077Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-10-10T04:11:45.916Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-05-20T07:15:41.580Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 17
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeed8553e7ab6730c55e",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8b868bfdc0428e7dcda",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeed8553e7ab6730c55e",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c41dc594dcace72f5b9b",
                            "name": "Madeleine",
                            "email": "maddykindler11@yahoo.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-06-10T18:10:27.425Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "I don't know if there is a magic number of people to ask in order to best refine your offering, but I do think that it is very important to consult with people from a variety of different backgrounds and with different specializations/perspectives!",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-22T18:55:25.815Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8b868bfdc0428e7dcd8",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "I want to refine my offering. How many people should I consult with and ask opinions of to make my offering better?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-02-22T15:10:26.802Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6368cc8178440371fa3f2bbd",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "636b45508152c428092f1f53",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "636b45158152c428092f1e94",
                        "answer": "hii\n",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6256d6b74f929c559b2183eb",
                            "currentRole": "Partner",
                            "email": "kevin088.rejoice@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Kevin",
                            "createdAt": "2022-04-13T13:57:11.884Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-15T09:09:19.527Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6368cc8178440371fa3f2bbd",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-09T06:14:40.009Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "636b457c8152c428092f21a0",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "636b45158152c428092f1e94",
                        "answer": "hii",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6368ab3c78440371fa3f0956",
                            "currentRole": "Other",
                            "email": "vijay95@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay95",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-07T06:52:44.596Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-07T06:52:44.597Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6368cc8178440371fa3f2bbd",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-09T06:15:24.111Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Has the fact that divorce is much more common now than it was fifty years ago made divorce easier for adults or children to deal with?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6368ab3c78440371fa3f0956",
                    "currentRole": "Other",
                    "email": "vijay95@yopmail.com",
                    "name": "vijay95",
                    "createdAt": "2022-11-07T06:52:44.596Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-11-07T06:52:44.597Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-11-07T09:14:41.448Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee18553e7ab6730c49f",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a85e68bfdc0428e7d0ef",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee18553e7ab6730c49f",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f08c594dcace72f5c8d",
                            "name": "cahora",
                            "email": "cahora7821@bomoads.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-27T09:04:53.338Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "ascjkashjkas",
                        "createdAt": "2021-10-28T09:00:58.792Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a85e68bfdc0428e7d0ed",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a85968bfdc0428e7d03d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee18553e7ab6730c49f",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                            "name": "Saima Omar",
                            "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Ask this entrepreneur a non-relevant question, or try to get into a conversation with them about sometime entirely different. Ideally something they are more likely to engage in conversation with you about. Once you have a back and forth discourse going on, it is much easier to pop that question within the existing interaction. I guess if they are ignoring you, it will be because either a) they are super busy and have ignored you without any malice or... b) they don't intend to give you the certificate and hope you will disappear/stop asking about it. However, if you were to strike up a conversation about something else, and appear to be useful, there's a bigger chance they will respond.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-10-14T00:06:21.144Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a85968bfdc0428e7d03b",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "I did high-level work as a consultant at a start-up run by a famous entrepreneur. This was my first start-up. Part of the compensation was for Class A shares. I was to receive a stock certificate. To date, one year later, I have not received one. The entrepreneur is ignoring it. Suggestions?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "62218f02c594dcace72f5c38",
                    "name": "Judy Diaz",
                    "email": "diazbusinessmail@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-08-13T14:34:39.819Z",
                    "currentRole": "Founder"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-10-12T15:36:00.166Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6375c5ee8957c84f017a078c",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "637cc00758c50b155046e48d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637cc00358c50b155046e457",
                        "answer": "hyyy",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6375c5ee8957c84f017a078c",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-22T12:26:47.424Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "What are the various assest classes",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6375b9bcd859e540c20bd335",
                    "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                    "email": "eric@yopmail.com",
                    "name": "Eric",
                    "createdAt": "2022-11-17T04:34:04.624Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-11-17T09:15:13.562Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-11-17T05:26:06.429Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eedd8553e7ab6730c46e",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84c68bfdc0428e7ce41",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedd8553e7ab6730c46e",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c422c594dcace72f5bf7",
                            "name": "Isabel Fabre",
                            "email": "ifabre@yahoo.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-07-22T18:36:03.950Z",
                            "currentRole": "Manager"
                        },
                        "answer": "Ask them questions about what makes them tick.  Get to know them.  I had several caterpillars that didn't even know they were butterflies but, through getting to know them, their strengths and their interests and putting them in positions where they can test them, while supporting them through the process, they blossomed.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-08-24T19:14:19.828Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84c68bfdc0428e7ce3f",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "\" There is nothing in a caterpillar that shows that it will be a butterfly\"... How do I identify the right potential(s) in people and make them thrive in a new country?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "62218f02c594dcace72f5c33",
                    "name": "Oluwapelumi Ogeroju",
                    "email": "yogeroju@yahoo.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-08-11T18:33:49.517Z",
                    "currentRole": "Founder"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-08-12T00:58:55.715Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeea8553e7ab6730c525",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8a568bfdc0428e7da0d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeea8553e7ab6730c525",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "There is not a bad time to start funding as long as you have something to show. You can begin reaching out to venture capital firms once you have your product/service in a presentable format. Many firms specialize in getting entrepreneurs off the ground with 'angel' funding!",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-03T15:53:22.204Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8a568bfdc0428e7da0b",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How do you know when your start-up is ready to consider outside funding? I am currently self-funding my venture. We are still not making a profit on this business, but we forecast we will make profit in year 2 of trading. We are coming to the end of year 1 of trading in Feb 2022.",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-01-29T00:58:07.460Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "62b78b27f6ac59655ddd9831",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "62c2dc0df6ac59655ddf7a55",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "62c2dc0af6ac59655ddf7a24",
                        "answer": "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetuer adipiscing elit. Aenean commodo ligula eget dolor. Aenean massa. Cum sociis natoque penatibus et magnis dis parturient montes, nascetur ridiculus mus. Donec quam felis, ultricies nec, pellentesque eu, pretium quis, sem. Nulla consequat massa quis enim. Donec pede justo, fringilla vel, aliquet nec, vulputate eget, arcu. In enim justo, rhoncus ut, imperdiet a, venenatis vitae, justo. Nullam dictum felis eu pede mollis pretium. Integer tincidunt. Cras dapibus. Vivamus elementum semper nisi. Aenean vulputate eleifend tellus. Aenean leo ligula, porttitor eu, consequat vitae, eleifend a",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "628dc2f3942ead2b0d93e54e",
                            "currentRole": "Director",
                            "email": "jatulkumar02@gmail.com",
                            "name": "Jatul kumar",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-25T05:47:31.454Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-04T12:04:31.549Z"
                        },
                        "question": "62b78b27f6ac59655ddd9831",
                        "createdAt": "2022-07-04T12:24:45.831Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Founders, how do you find the RIGHT investors for your startup, when it's an impact/profit-with-purpose/tech4good startup?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-06-25T22:24:39.783Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee78553e7ab6730c502",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a89768bfdc0428e7d7ea",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee78553e7ab6730c502",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3ecc594dcace72f58f8",
                            "name": "MollyDriscoll",
                            "email": "mdriscoll2@luc.edu",
                            "createdAt": "2020-10-07T01:12:14.277Z",
                            "currentRole": "CEO"
                        },
                        "answer": "It's normal to want to check in on your passion project constantly. However, it isn't always productive. A complete vacation may seem unrealistic at this time, but you can still take little breaks throughout your week. If you're questioning whether you should take a break, then give yourself a break. I persnally find that shutting off my laptop and putting down my phone at a certain time every day and all the day on Saturday helps me stay in touch my family and myself.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-09T18:25:40.585Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a89768bfdc0428e7d7e8",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8a568bfdc0428e7da16",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee78553e7ab6730c502",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "The primary thing to consider is your own performance/state of mind. If you are seeing fatigue get in your way, step back and give yourself some breathing room. Take your mind off of it for a short time.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-03T15:54:55.190Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8a568bfdc0428e7da14",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How much annual leave do you take from your own company? Especially founders of start-up businesses? I'm struggling to switch off, and constantly checking emails, news articles and other items on my laptop. I'm so keen to get this company established and the awareness of the brand and industry to be on par with the competition. The early days are hard, so wanting some advice on whether I should give myself a break.",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-01-07T14:08:07.165Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee68553e7ab6730c4ed",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a88c68bfdc0428e7d669",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee68553e7ab6730c4ed",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c40ac594dcace72f5a68",
                            "name": "SANJEEV KUMAR MEHTA",
                            "email": "perfect2work@yahoo.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-19T03:28:37.568Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "Leaders i have worked in the past\nFollow Harvard page",
                        "createdAt": "2021-12-21T03:44:51.396Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a88c68bfdc0428e7d667",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8a868bfdc0428e7da70",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee68553e7ab6730c4ed",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "Adam Grant!",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-03T21:06:17.546Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8a868bfdc0428e7da6e",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Leaders: Who do you look up to for inspiration or mentorship?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-12-20T15:52:49.020Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee58553e7ab6730c4dc",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a87d68bfdc0428e7d534",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee58553e7ab6730c4dc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f00c594dcace72f5c24",
                            "name": "Steven Pietras",
                            "email": "norgoth12@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-08-07T15:35:10.381Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Hello! Looking for someone to talk to?",
                        "createdAt": "2021-12-06T16:02:56.570Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a87b68bfdc0428e7d4eb",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a88068bfdc0428e7d5a2",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee58553e7ab6730c4dc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "One way is to do your research before initiating a conversation. You might take some time to learn about a person's culture by other channels and then take some time to learn about the person in their present context and make it obvious you're curious about their story and not where they fit into a cultural pattern.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-12-09T02:21:31.241Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a88068bfdc0428e7d5a0",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "I want all of my co-workers to feel confident that  I see them for who they are and not as stereotypes. However,  I find it fascinating to compare cultures and backgrounds. Does anyone have advice for safe ways to discuss such things without the risk of seeming boorish or prejudiced?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "62218f00c594dcace72f5c24",
                    "name": "Steven Pietras",
                    "email": "norgoth12@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-08-07T15:35:10.381Z",
                    "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-12-02T13:46:39.977Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eef08553e7ab6730c590",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a80f68bfdc0428e7c579",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef08553e7ab6730c590",
                        "answer": "it had a big toll on all of us and people in my locality and neighbourhood",
                        "createdAt": "2021-02-02T19:15:46.447Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a80f68bfdc0428e7c577",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a80d68bfdc0428e7c534",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef08553e7ab6730c590",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3fdc594dcace72f599f",
                            "name": "Test 30",
                            "email": "test30@inscriptio.in",
                            "createdAt": "2021-01-13T06:23:05.122Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "It affected everyone.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-01-23T05:52:54.101Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a80d68bfdc0428e7c532",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "how the pandemic affected in your place",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3fcc594dcace72f5986",
                    "name": "Hema P H",
                    "email": "hema.vayuz@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-01-06T10:14:53.946Z",
                    "currentRole": "Manager"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-01-06T11:59:06.760Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeed8553e7ab6730c55a",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8b768bfdc0428e7dcbb",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeed8553e7ab6730c55a",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3e6c594dcace72f58aa",
                            "name": "Amarachi Emezie",
                            "email": "amarachieemezie@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2022-01-12T18:41:13.277Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-05-09T15:13:09.331Z",
                            "currentRole": "Other"
                        },
                        "answer": "From experience, the right marketing can go a long way. Regarding start-ups, when you have reached a level of sataisfaction and customers are enjoying the app, the way one markets can take the business even further. One should try to market to its geared audience but also not be opposed to expand the audience and restructure the project to reach more people.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-22T06:31:54.485Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8b768bfdc0428e7dcb9",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "What business functions have the most impact on success?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3e8c594dcace72f58c9",
                    "name": "Nina Blackmon",
                    "email": "ninasblackmon@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2022-02-08T19:19:31.120Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-05-05T17:43:54.724Z",
                    "currentRole": "Other"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-02-22T00:09:15.870Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee98553e7ab6730c520",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8a268bfdc0428e7d97d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee98553e7ab6730c520",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c40dc594dcace72f5aa7",
                            "name": "Nick Welham",
                            "email": "nick.welham@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-04-04T16:02:49.314Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-07T12:56:16.743Z"
                        },
                        "answer": "I would suggest looking at LinkedIn - for people you worked with who have this background - they might be interested or have a 2nd-degree connection. The other option is to start networking on LunchClub.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-26T13:49:56.427Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8a268bfdc0428e7d97b",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "My background is in tech and I am looking for a co-founder who has an operations, hopefully, in addition to a finance background. How can I hone my search? Are there networks outside of just people in your social circle?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                    "name": "Daniel Daws",
                    "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                    "currentRole": "Founder"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-01-21T17:09:10.175Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "63843a1ef448d226dcdfb626",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "b",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:33:34.685Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63843a23f448d226dcdfb649",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vnv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:33:39.043Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63843a26f448d226dcdfb66c",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vbn",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:33:42.626Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63843a30f448d226dcdfb6bc",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vbvv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:33:52.168Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63843a35f448d226dcdfb6e8",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "bnbb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:33:57.268Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63843a3df448d226dcdfb724",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vbvbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "vijay789@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:34:05.191Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63843a3ff448d226dcdfb759",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "v",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:34:07.590Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63843a40f448d226dcdfb785",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "bnv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:34:08.616Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63843abff448d226dcdfb7c2",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "hjhk",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "vijay789@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:36:15.307Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63843acdf448d226dcdfb7f6",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:36:29.671Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63843b1ff448d226dcdfb833",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "cvbvc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "vijay789@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:37:51.337Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63843b25f448d226dcdfb867",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vbbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:37:57.528Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63843c0acfd2f5189098dd5f",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vbcv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:41:46.300Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63843d789a795b13d816cf9f",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "nm,nn,",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:47:52.870Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63843e879a795b13d816d029",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "ghfghfgfggfgfhgf",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:52:23.824Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63843ef99a795b13d816d062",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vnvbnbvbvbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:54:17.426Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63843f159a795b13d816d0fd",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "bnv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:54:45.461Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63843f219a795b13d816d136",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "bnv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:54:57.370Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63843f319a795b13d816d180",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "bvnb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "vijay789@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:55:13.463Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63843f4c87fd671234c48fb5",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vbnbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:55:40.153Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63843f6787fd671234c48ffe",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vvnvb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "vijay789@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:56:07.173Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63843f9a70a6681f2822f8aa",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "nvbvbbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "vijay789@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:56:58.290Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63843fc870a6681f2822f8f1",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "b",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:57:44.276Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63843fc970a6681f2822f92a",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vnv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:57:45.387Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638442721862212498770e94",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vbvc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:09:06.322Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638442af1862212498770eef",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vbvcbvcbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:10:07.525Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638442b51862212498770f2a",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vcbc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "vijay789@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:10:13.875Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638442b91862212498770f78",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vcbcv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:10:17.161Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638442d218622124987710ad",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vcbvc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:10:42.831Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638442ef186221249877113f",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "cvbvc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:11:11.757Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638442f41862212498771178",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "bvcvcbvcbvccbc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:11:16.612Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638442fb18622124987711be",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vcbvc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "vijay789@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:11:23.196Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638442fe1862212498771203",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vcbvb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:11:26.465Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638443031862212498771242",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vbnv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "vijay789@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:11:31.740Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638443611862212498771298",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vcbvc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "vijay789@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:13:05.722Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6384436a18622124987712e0",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vbvv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:13:14.988Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638443721862212498771346",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "v",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:13:22.564Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638443731862212498771376",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "cbc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:13:23.487Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6384438c18622124987713d3",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vcbc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:13:48.964Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638444311862212498771419",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vcbvbvbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "vijay789@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:16:33.709Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6384444e186221249877145e",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vcvc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:17:02.915Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844472125ffc16f40e3b00",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "gnvbnvb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:17:38.673Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638444b0c6928c36fc60fad3",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vbnbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "vijay789@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:18:40.680Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6384451b3064a824cca70d90",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vbnbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:20:27.401Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6384452ee3d6fa0770c93224",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vbnvb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "vijay789@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:20:46.527Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844532e3d6fa0770c93270",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vcbvv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:20:50.114Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844547e3d6fa0770c932d2",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "bvnbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:21:11.779Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6384454be3d6fa0770c93302",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "b",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:21:15.069Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6384454ce3d6fa0770c93332",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "mnb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:21:16.095Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6384455fe3d6fa0770c9339b",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "bnbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "vijay789@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:21:35.143Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844563e3d6fa0770c933df",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "bnbn",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:21:39.345Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844647e3d6fa0770c93445",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "bvnvbnv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:25:27.874Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844757e3d6fa0770c934aa",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vcbvc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "vijay789@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:29:59.515Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6384476ce3d6fa0770c93545",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vbnvb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:30:20.014Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844774e3d6fa0770c935e5",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:30:28.438Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638447c37b2e5c1cd45236ee",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "cvbvc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:31:47.656Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6384480112cf7d323095f5f0",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vcbvnvb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:32:49.827Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6384483212cf7d323095f6b4",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "cvbcv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:33:38.293Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638448a2eef11103c8194c5f",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "jhjhj",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "vijay789@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:35:30.024Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638448a6eef11103c8194c9f",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "cnvcvb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:35:34.840Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638448bfeef11103c8194d3f",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "jhjhkhjkhjkjhkhhjkh",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:35:59.722Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638449bbc5fe67044836c408",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vbnvb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:40:11.979Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844b6dc5fe67044836c4bf",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "bbcvbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:47:25.910Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844b76c5fe67044836c4f8",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vbvcb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:47:34.753Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844b77c5fe67044836c533",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "cb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:47:35.831Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844b78c5fe67044836c56c",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "cbcvbvc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:47:36.837Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844b7ac5fe67044836c5a3",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "cbcvbvc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:47:38.029Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844b7bc5fe67044836c5da",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "cbcvb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:47:39.100Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844b7cc5fe67044836c611",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "cvb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:47:40.125Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844b7dc5fe67044836c64a",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "cvbcvb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:47:41.181Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844b7ec5fe67044836c683",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "cvbvcbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:47:42.259Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844b83c5fe67044836c6c9",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "nbvn",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "vijay789@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:47:47.247Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844b85c5fe67044836c711",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vbvnbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:47:49.735Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844b89c5fe67044836c74e",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vbnvbnv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "vijay789@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:47:53.108Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844b8ac5fe67044836c79f",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "v",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:47:54.980Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844b8bc5fe67044836c7da",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "cbvnbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:47:55.665Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844c29ca68b81e84b42dd6",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vcxcvb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:50:33.247Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844c2eca68b81e84b42fb3",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "cvbvc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:50:38.988Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844c3eca68b81e84b4359d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vbvc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:50:54.298Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844c49ca68b81e84b4396b",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "qqq",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:51:05.023Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844d0eca68b81e84b47d28",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "bnb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:54:22.330Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844d1fca68b81e84b482df",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "www",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:54:39.435Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844d2bca68b81e84b4868d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "cbcbcv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:54:51.104Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844d41ca68b81e84b48dac",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "bcvbvcvbcbvvnvbnvb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:55:13.153Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844dcbeec435051845ab2d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "nvbnbvv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:57:31.401Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844e40903e74369449dbd5",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:59:28.705Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844e59903e74369449e6b3",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "QQAAAASS",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:59:53.647Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844fca117fe41bd0bebb18",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "nbmnmn",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T06:06:02.825Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844fd3117fe41bd0bebb7d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vbnvb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T06:06:11.090Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844fda117fe41bd0bebbb8",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vcbvnvb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T06:06:18.717Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844fe0117fe41bd0bebc01",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "vbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "vijay789@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T06:06:24.692Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844fe3117fe41bd0bebc48",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "v",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T06:06:27.364Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844fe4117fe41bd0bebc83",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63843a18f448d226dcdfb5e9",
                        "answer": "nvbnbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b74617a3ce63a87b81331",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay75@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:35:29.266Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T04:06:31.063Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63843a0df448d226dcdfb4e9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T06:06:28.358Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "bvnv",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6381cbcad8bb3b207822aa79",
                    "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                    "email": "vijay789@yopmail.com",
                    "name": "vijay",
                    "createdAt": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-11-26T08:18:18.132Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-11-28T04:33:17.837Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 93
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeeb8553e7ab6730c53c",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8ae68bfdc0428e7db5e",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeeb8553e7ab6730c53c",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3e6c594dcace72f58aa",
                            "name": "Amarachi Emezie",
                            "email": "amarachieemezie@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2022-01-12T18:41:13.277Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-05-09T15:13:09.331Z",
                            "currentRole": "Other"
                        },
                        "answer": "I started my business because I genuinely wanted to make a difference. I believed there were not enough resources for individuals in my area and that my business could one day change the world if I just started it. As I thought of my business, I decided I wanted to make it a non-profit. Any money that I received would be from donations and partners. Through my non-profit, I am able to help individuals for free and truly make a difference without requiring users to pay.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-11T23:21:01.520Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8ae68bfdc0428e7db5c",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8af68bfdc0428e7db7f",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeeb8553e7ab6730c53c",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                            "name": "Saima Omar",
                            "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "That is great! What is your non-profit business in? What do you do?",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-13T16:42:10.718Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8ae68bfdc0428e7db5c",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8b368bfdc0428e7dc24",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeeb8553e7ab6730c53c",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3e5c594dcace72f5893",
                            "name": "Firzana",
                            "email": "firzana218@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-12-29T20:45:55.686Z",
                            "currentRole": "Other"
                        },
                        "answer": "I started my business with both in mind. I wanted to make a difference in my community but I also knew I needed it to be profitable so that I can continue sustaining my business, making that change, and supporting my family financially. The specific industry that I am in is quite niche but the target demographic would incredibly benefit from my product I would like to believe.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-15T20:26:47.658Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8b368bfdc0428e7dc22",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Did you start your business because you want to make money, or because you genuinely care to make a difference through your offering. (Change the world, improve an experience, deliver for a identified gap in the market)?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-02-11T22:12:33.260Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 3
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee88553e7ab6730c514",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8a468bfdc0428e7d9e0",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee88553e7ab6730c514",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "In what capacity does he seem unreceptive? Is he unclear on what you're asking of him, having difficulty applying your feedback, or is he resistant to the feedback itself? If it's general resistance, do you have room on your startup team for someone that's non-cooperative? Otherwise, it might be worth examining your communication strategy rather than just trying different intervention modes!",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-03T15:49:15.150Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8a468bfdc0428e7d9de",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "I have a certain employee who was recently hired, he was performing decently well at the start but his performance has been deteriorating. I have tried talking to him, and he does not seem very receptible to my efforts to communicate with him. I am currently trying to use goal-setting to improve his performance but am wondering if I should use a combination of different interventions. Should I just use only goal-setting to improve employee performance? What are some interventions you have used in your startup?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3e5c594dcace72f5893",
                    "name": "Firzana",
                    "email": "firzana218@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-12-29T20:45:55.686Z",
                    "currentRole": "Other"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-01-13T23:18:54.908Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eef08553e7ab6730c59b",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a81168bfdc0428e7c5cd",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef08553e7ab6730c59b",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3fdc594dcace72f599b",
                            "name": "Alison Bagwell",
                            "email": "abagwell@shieldtecinc.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-01-11T15:43:43.206Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "You can teach character through demonstration. People want to be valued and an effective leadership demonstrates that through their actions. Some will aqdapt and some will not. Get those that do not out of your organization",
                        "createdAt": "2021-02-04T04:06:44.266Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a81168bfdc0428e7c5cb",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a81368bfdc0428e7c627",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef08553e7ab6730c59b",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3f5c594dcace72f591c",
                            "name": "Jim Red",
                            "email": "rojjim@hotmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2020-11-25T21:44:54.463Z",
                            "currentRole": "Manager"
                        },
                        "answer": "Partly true.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-02-06T00:54:06.820Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a81368bfdc0428e7c625",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a83768bfdc0428e7cb22",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef08553e7ab6730c59b",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c416c594dcace72f5b31",
                            "name": "Todd Harrison",
                            "email": "todd.harrison@deltafaucet.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-04-30T11:58:30.420Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "I think character should be a big factor in selecting all leaders, not just executives.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-04-30T12:33:39.427Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a83768bfdc0428e7cb20",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "What do you think of the statement “Executives should be selected on character. You can teach skills not character”?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3ecc594dcace72f58f8",
                    "name": "MollyDriscoll",
                    "email": "mdriscoll2@luc.edu",
                    "createdAt": "2020-10-07T01:12:14.277Z",
                    "currentRole": "CEO"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-02-01T18:05:31.880Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 3
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eedf8553e7ab6730c48c",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a85268bfdc0428e7cf2b",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedf8553e7ab6730c48c",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c413c594dcace72f5b03",
                            "name": "Arijit Basu",
                            "email": "arijitb962@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-04-21T07:34:56.909Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "A strong purpose needs to be there for the people to remain connected and stay inspired. When we think of communicating purpose, we need to keep in mind articulating the impact and sharing what way that can individually alter or benefit the individual in terms of satisfaction and impacting others in a positive way. ",
                        "createdAt": "2021-09-30T07:47:24.805Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a85268bfdc0428e7cf29",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a85368bfdc0428e7cf44",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedf8553e7ab6730c48c",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f06c594dcace72f5c62",
                            "name": "Dino Maiolo",
                            "email": "dino@cabaretti.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-09-28T16:56:58.702Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "Right, but if they are taking the time to volunteer, don't they already have a strong purpose for being there? If I have an objective that I need buy-in to achieve, how do I get that buy-infrom my members?",
                        "createdAt": "2021-09-30T22:15:56.298Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a85268bfdc0428e7cf29",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a85568bfdc0428e7cfae",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedf8553e7ab6730c48c",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f04c594dcace72f5c4e",
                            "name": "Iryna Chaban",
                            "email": "irynachaban98@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-09-07T19:20:12.002Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "If your workers are not getting paid, they should receive some other form of compensation, such as a learning experience or feeling of altruism. It will motivate them to continue working without monetary gain!",
                        "createdAt": "2021-10-07T13:56:51.163Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a85568bfdc0428e7cfac",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a85868bfdc0428e7d009",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedf8553e7ab6730c48c",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c413c594dcace72f5b03",
                            "name": "Arijit Basu",
                            "email": "arijitb962@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-04-21T07:34:56.909Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "Best ways to “buy in” could be to articulate the purpose in such a way where the stake holders would know “what’s in it there for me”… in a cause like this beyond money there could be many more aspects ranging from esteem, pride, resurrection to just pure feeling good. \nThe buy in will surely happen if the purpose is strong (well articulated) and the stakeholders know why are they into it. Hope this helps! ",
                        "createdAt": "2021-10-12T06:26:38.032Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a85268bfdc0428e7cf29",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "What are ways to motivate people to do things when they are not getting paid, such as in a nonprofit organization?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "62218f06c594dcace72f5c62",
                    "name": "Dino Maiolo",
                    "email": "dino@cabaretti.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-09-28T16:56:58.702Z",
                    "currentRole": "Founder"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-09-28T17:15:59.392Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 4
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eedb8553e7ab6730c447",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84268bfdc0428e7cca6",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedb8553e7ab6730c447",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3f5c594dcace72f5919",
                            "name": "J. Mandell Carter",
                            "email": "j.m.carter2021@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2020-11-23T17:57:09.494Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "My first thought is a S.W.O.T (Strengths, Weakness,  Opportunities and Threats) evaluation followed by a team member eval. Doing so will answer the quesitons of why leadership is having a hard time; are they Leading or Managing? Leaders work WITH teams, demonstrating best practices, empowering members to be innovative, to make mistakes without fear of being \"thrown under the bus\" for a mistake; communicating effectively with the team which means, no egos in the room. Will this elleviate all heistitancy, perhaps not. However, there is a better chance that a team will willing following a respected and trusted leader with a higher buy-in. If those at the top are managing, I have found elevated instances of resistance and push-back. I firmly believe that resources (and people are NOT resources), time, money etc., are managed; team members are lead. If this first hurdle is effectively addressed, the rest will fall into place.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-06-25T18:23:44.295Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84268bfdc0428e7cca4",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84268bfdc0428e7ccaf",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedb8553e7ab6730c447",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c40ac594dcace72f5a68",
                            "name": "SANJEEV KUMAR MEHTA",
                            "email": "perfect2work@yahoo.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-19T03:28:37.568Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "Change is the only constant. It is important roles are understood while implementing change. For every system and process there is the team that does the tasks, influencers who influence the process, auditors who monitor compliance's and the entrepreneur who normally has the decision authority. Implementation of change needs to be carefully crafted to include key stakeholders in the design process prior to implementation.It is a good idea to always selectively test the new process prior to full deployment.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-06-25T19:17:58.037Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84268bfdc0428e7ccad",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Most organizations have high silo barriers between functions, products, geographies. Most organizations want to change but senior leaders typically find leading their teams through change to be very challenging. Customers typically feel these barriers and conclude the organization is difficult to do business with. What are some of the best methods you have found to lead teams through change, have them actually deliver the expected benefits, and have customers see your organization as easy to do business with?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c418c594dcace72f5b57",
                    "name": "Lon Blumenthal",
                    "email": "lon.blumenthal@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-05-07T22:12:48.453Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-05-07T22:28:14.596Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee78553e7ab6730c500",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8a668bfdc0428e7da28",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee78553e7ab6730c500",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "Your executive assessor will more than likely not be giving your company a thumbs up or down. You want to be open and honest with them. The primary goal is to look for what areas you'll excel in without support, and what areas you may need extra support should you be selected for the position.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-03T16:39:15.463Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8a668bfdc0428e7da26",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a89a68bfdc0428e7d85f",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee78553e7ab6730c500",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3e5c594dcace72f589a",
                            "name": "Robert",
                            "email": "yiwexi8958@whecode.com",
                            "createdAt": "2022-01-06T14:42:11.315Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "hello",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-13T06:10:58.463Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a89a68bfdc0428e7d85d",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "I am up for a promotion at CEO of my company. What are the key things that my executive assessor will be looking for? How can I prepare myself for this role?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-01-07T14:05:27.834Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee78553e7ab6730c505",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a89b68bfdc0428e7d883",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee78553e7ab6730c505",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "This is going to depend heavily on what kind of market you're looking to break into and what your financial situation is, opening this up.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-13T16:25:29.045Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a89b68bfdc0428e7d881",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "As a start-up company, is it wise to have a board of advisors? How much do board members expect in terms of payment? How do I find board members?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-01-07T14:12:18.897Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eedd8553e7ab6730c465",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84868bfdc0428e7cdaa",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedd8553e7ab6730c465",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                            "name": "Saima Omar",
                            "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Thank you for taking the time to respond. I'll check this one out.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-07-22T01:29:04.145Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84868bfdc0428e7cda1",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84a68bfdc0428e7cdf4",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedd8553e7ab6730c465",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                            "name": "Saima Omar",
                            "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Thank you for taking the time to respond. I'll check this one out.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-08-07T00:42:03.617Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84968bfdc0428e7cdb1",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84968bfdc0428e7cdb3",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedd8553e7ab6730c465",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c40ac594dcace72f5a68",
                            "name": "SANJEEV KUMAR MEHTA",
                            "email": "perfect2work@yahoo.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-19T03:28:37.568Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "Adizes methodologies of management ",
                        "createdAt": "2021-07-28T18:03:47.195Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84968bfdc0428e7cdb1",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84b68bfdc0428e7ce02",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedd8553e7ab6730c465",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c40ac594dcace72f5a68",
                            "name": "SANJEEV KUMAR MEHTA",
                            "email": "perfect2work@yahoo.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-19T03:28:37.568Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "Your most welcome!! Keep in touch !!",
                        "createdAt": "2021-08-07T18:56:21.330Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84968bfdc0428e7cdb1",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84a68bfdc0428e7cdfb",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedd8553e7ab6730c465",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                            "name": "Saima Omar",
                            "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Thank you for taking the time to respond. I'll check this one out.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-08-07T00:42:07.203Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84968bfdc0428e7cdba",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84868bfdc0428e7cda3",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedd8553e7ab6730c465",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c422c594dcace72f5bf3",
                            "name": "Nic Gaddis-Wyatt",
                            "email": "nicgaddis13@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-07-20T03:31:51.476Z",
                            "currentRole": "Manager"
                        },
                        "answer": "Outliers by Malcolm Gladwell helped me realize it takes a lot of practice to master a skill. This helps me in being patient with my new employees.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-07-21T03:02:21.901Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84868bfdc0428e7cda1",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84968bfdc0428e7cdbc",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedd8553e7ab6730c465",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c424c594dcace72f5c0d",
                            "name": "Matt Maxwell",
                            "email": "matthewhmaxwell@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-07-29T13:05:04.060Z",
                            "currentRole": "Executive Vice President"
                        },
                        "answer": "Principles by Ray Dalio",
                        "createdAt": "2021-07-29T22:52:59.889Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84968bfdc0428e7cdba",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84b68bfdc0428e7ce14",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedd8553e7ab6730c465",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c422c594dcace72f5bf6",
                            "name": "Sarah Smith-Barry",
                            "email": "ssmithbarry@freegoconsulting.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-07-21T22:24:55.438Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "It is not a leadership book, per se, but my favorite development book to date has been The Object Is The Way - Ryan Holiday.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-08-10T13:25:27.005Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84b68bfdc0428e7ce12",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Can you please recommend one of your favourite leadership books? (I'd love to know how that book helped you/shaped you as a leader).",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-07-17T20:33:59.291Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 8
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee68553e7ab6730c4ec",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a88d68bfdc0428e7d6ac",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee68553e7ab6730c4ec",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                            "name": "Saima Omar",
                            "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "How would you suggest that I do this?",
                        "createdAt": "2021-12-22T16:41:35.196Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a88c68bfdc0428e7d670",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a88c68bfdc0428e7d672",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee68553e7ab6730c4ec",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c40ac594dcace72f5a68",
                            "name": "SANJEEV KUMAR MEHTA",
                            "email": "perfect2work@yahoo.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-19T03:28:37.568Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "Marketing your self to your leadership is critical \ndo not miss any opportunity to highlight what your contributions are ",
                        "createdAt": "2021-12-21T03:46:22.478Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a88c68bfdc0428e7d670",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8a868bfdc0428e7da79",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee68553e7ab6730c4ec",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "In what way does your colleague undermine your work?",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-03T21:07:05.907Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8a868bfdc0428e7da77",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "I am an executive in a large organization. My colleague who is also an executive and at the same level as me, keeps making remarks that undermine my work. It is a regular occurrence. I'm not sure how to deal with this. Any ideas on how I confront this situation?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-12-20T15:45:41.034Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 3
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eef48553e7ab6730c5dc",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a83c68bfdc0428e7cbd3",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef48553e7ab6730c5dc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c41bc594dcace72f5b84",
                            "name": "Eric Dupuis",
                            "email": "artonadigitaltechnology@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-05-27T00:41:06.166Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "assuring everyone ",
                        "createdAt": "2021-05-27T01:11:20.244Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a83c68bfdc0428e7cbd1",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a83068bfdc0428e7ca1c",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef48553e7ab6730c5dc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c40dc594dcace72f5a9f",
                            "name": "Sunil Deshmukh",
                            "email": "sd@sunil-deshmukh.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-04-02T04:17:25.511Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Kindness in Leadership is key in this sector.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-04-23T06:42:59.766Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a83068bfdc0428e7ca1a",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "What should be the role of an efficient and effective CEO during this pandemic situation in a 200 bedded hospital?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3fdc594dcace72f5990",
                    "name": "B JEYAKUMAR",
                    "email": "bjeyakumar75@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-01-10T06:43:36.129Z",
                    "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-04-16T07:00:16.859Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee48553e7ab6730c4d5",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a88b68bfdc0428e7d657",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee48553e7ab6730c4d5",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                            "name": "Saima Omar",
                            "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Thank you so much for such a thoughtful response!",
                        "createdAt": "2021-12-20T15:46:28.571Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a87668bfdc0428e7d449",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8a868bfdc0428e7da82",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee48553e7ab6730c4d5",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "The first way would be to identify where their performance or morale",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-03T21:14:21.302Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8a868bfdc0428e7da80",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a87668bfdc0428e7d44b",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee48553e7ab6730c4d5",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f00c594dcace72f5c24",
                            "name": "Steven Pietras",
                            "email": "norgoth12@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-08-07T15:35:10.381Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "I feel like this will be a problem that a lot of us will have going forawrd. Scheduling employee check-ins, not just with managers, but also with peers would be helpful. I have not seen much success with non-work-related activities such as 'online mixers' or ice breaking games in online meetings, so bonding activities based on work needs seem like the way to go. More group and team driven work might engage employees more.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-11-29T17:39:48.607Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a87668bfdc0428e7d449",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "I am a director of an established marketing agency. For 10 years of running this business, we have had a head office. Around 3 months ago, I took the decision to make my staff fully remote. We no longer have a commercial office. How can I, as a leader, improve the engagement and productivity of remote employees?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-11-28T02:11:50.845Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 3
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eedc8553e7ab6730c460",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84368bfdc0428e7cce0",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedc8553e7ab6730c460",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c413c594dcace72f5b03",
                            "name": "Arijit Basu",
                            "email": "arijitb962@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-04-21T07:34:56.909Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "I can try to help through my contact in GLA University, Mathura near Delhi in India ",
                        "createdAt": "2021-07-05T02:50:39.858Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84368bfdc0428e7ccde",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "We have an MSc master program in a new multidisciplinary concept called \"Inspiration Economy\" we are interested to spread it in many universities around the world. Can you help?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c420c594dcace72f5bd3",
                    "name": "Mohamed Buheji",
                    "email": "buhejim@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-07-04T08:19:06.247Z",
                    "currentRole": "Founder"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-07-04T09:41:46.818Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eedd8553e7ab6730c471",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84d68bfdc0428e7ce64",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedd8553e7ab6730c471",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f04c594dcace72f5c4d",
                            "name": "Robert Varnam",
                            "email": "robert@varnam.org.uk",
                            "createdAt": "2021-09-02T09:01:31.012Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Great question. I always start with why, trying to understand the manager's personal sense of purpose and motivation. Why are they here in the first? What makes work satisfying for them? Where is their sense of commitment currently to the organisation and the people around them. There are undoubtedly situations where we just have to let people go, but I've found that investing time in getting \"under the skin\" of the issue can open possibilities for huge turnaround in the person.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-09-02T09:23:18.207Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84d68bfdc0428e7ce62",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How do you give feedback to a manager that is negatively impacting the organization but does not have the interest in receiving that feedback or making any changes?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c422c594dcace72f5bf7",
                    "name": "Isabel Fabre",
                    "email": "ifabre@yahoo.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-07-22T18:36:03.950Z",
                    "currentRole": "Manager"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-08-24T19:20:29.568Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "627a561eb993497cc623a608",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6289c32fd0a01e70a277f420",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6289c31cd0a01e70a277f3fc",
                        "answer": "good question, I want to know too",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6289bcdfd0a01e70a277eef1",
                            "currentRole": "Manager",
                            "email": "z.wang12@icloud.com",
                            "name": "Christy Wang",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-22T04:32:31.532Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-26T22:50:00.514Z"
                        },
                        "question": "627a561eb993497cc623a608",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-22T04:59:27.947Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "62bb1784f6ac59655dde7bc9",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "62bb1781f6ac59655dde7b96",
                        "answer": "nvbn",
                        "question": "627a561eb993497cc623a608",
                        "createdAt": "2022-06-28T15:00:20.239Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "62bb1786f6ac59655dde7c0a",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "62bb1781f6ac59655dde7b96",
                        "answer": "bnbv",
                        "question": "627a561eb993497cc623a608",
                        "createdAt": "2022-06-28T15:00:22.561Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "62bb1787f6ac59655dde7c25",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "62bb1781f6ac59655dde7b96",
                        "answer": "bnbv",
                        "question": "627a561eb993497cc623a608",
                        "createdAt": "2022-06-28T15:00:23.222Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "62bb1787f6ac59655dde7c3d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "62bb1781f6ac59655dde7b96",
                        "answer": "vbn",
                        "question": "627a561eb993497cc623a608",
                        "createdAt": "2022-06-28T15:00:23.877Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "62bb1788f6ac59655dde7c55",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "62bb1781f6ac59655dde7b96",
                        "answer": "vbnbbvn",
                        "question": "627a561eb993497cc623a608",
                        "createdAt": "2022-06-28T15:00:24.498Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "62bb178af6ac59655dde7cad",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "62bb1781f6ac59655dde7b96",
                        "answer": "vbnbvbvnbvnbvnbv",
                        "question": "627a561eb993497cc623a608",
                        "createdAt": "2022-06-28T15:00:26.157Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "What are the various Types of Companies one can form?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "62769590d1728c442a22c4c2",
                    "currentRole": "Director",
                    "email": "kunj@happilyever.co",
                    "name": "Kunj",
                    "createdAt": "2022-05-07T15:51:44.441Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-05-16T06:07:55.938Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-05-10T12:10:06.759Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 7
            },
            {
                "_id": "637e0ee9a00c393d8f8be7a7",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "637e0f30a00c393d8f8be93d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637e0f1fa00c393d8f8be910",
                        "answer": "test.....",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637e0785a00c393d8f8bd566",
                            "currentRole": "Manager",
                            "email": "dev4@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Dev",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-23T11:44:05.621Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-23T12:12:53.797Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637e0ee9a00c393d8f8be7a7",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-23T12:16:48.912Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637e0f49a00c393d8f8be970",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637e0f1fa00c393d8f8be910",
                        "answer": "test111",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637e0785a00c393d8f8bd566",
                            "currentRole": "Manager",
                            "email": "dev4@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Dev",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-23T11:44:05.621Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-23T12:12:53.797Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637e0ee9a00c393d8f8be7a7",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-23T12:17:13.936Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637e0f6fa00c393d8f8be9df",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637e0f1fa00c393d8f8be910",
                        "answer": "test22222",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637e0785a00c393d8f8bd566",
                            "currentRole": "Manager",
                            "email": "dev4@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Dev",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-23T11:44:05.621Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-23T12:12:53.797Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637e0ee9a00c393d8f8be7a7",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-23T12:17:51.919Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637f0ec37b05b546b0911894",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f0ebe7b05b546b091184f",
                        "answer": "test...",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636a78788152c428092ed35a",
                            "currentRole": "Manager",
                            "email": "yo@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Yo",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-08T15:40:40.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:44:24.701Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637e0ee9a00c393d8f8be7a7",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T06:27:15.891Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637f0eeb7b05b546b09119eb",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f0ebe7b05b546b091184f",
                        "answer": "test.......",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636a78788152c428092ed35a",
                            "currentRole": "Manager",
                            "email": "yo@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Yo",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-08T15:40:40.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:44:24.701Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637e0ee9a00c393d8f8be7a7",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T06:27:55.538Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637f10767b05b546b0911c19",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f0ebe7b05b546b091184f",
                        "answer": "hello\n",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636a78788152c428092ed35a",
                            "currentRole": "Manager",
                            "email": "yo@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Yo",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-08T15:40:40.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:44:24.701Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637e0ee9a00c393d8f8be7a7",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T06:34:30.717Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637f10ba7b05b546b0911e38",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f0ebe7b05b546b091184f",
                        "answer": "hii\n",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636a78788152c428092ed35a",
                            "currentRole": "Manager",
                            "email": "yo@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Yo",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-08T15:40:40.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:44:24.701Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637e0ee9a00c393d8f8be7a7",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T06:35:38.197Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637f134e7b05b546b091278a",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f0ebe7b05b546b091184f",
                        "answer": "jhj'",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636a78788152c428092ed35a",
                            "currentRole": "Manager",
                            "email": "yo@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Yo",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-08T15:40:40.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:44:24.701Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637e0ee9a00c393d8f8be7a7",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T06:46:38.290Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637f13607b05b546b091283a",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f0ebe7b05b546b091184f",
                        "answer": "hiiii",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636a78788152c428092ed35a",
                            "currentRole": "Manager",
                            "email": "yo@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Yo",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-08T15:40:40.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:44:24.701Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637e0ee9a00c393d8f8be7a7",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T06:46:56.166Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637f13787b05b546b09128f7",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f0ebe7b05b546b091184f",
                        "answer": "uio",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636a78788152c428092ed35a",
                            "currentRole": "Manager",
                            "email": "yo@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Yo",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-08T15:40:40.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:44:24.701Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637e0ee9a00c393d8f8be7a7",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T06:47:20.760Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637f13fc7b05b546b0912b8a",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f0ebe7b05b546b091184f",
                        "answer": "yyh",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636a78788152c428092ed35a",
                            "currentRole": "Manager",
                            "email": "yo@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Yo",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-08T15:40:40.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:44:24.701Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637e0ee9a00c393d8f8be7a7",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T06:49:32.375Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637f14477b05b546b0912ed7",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f0ebe7b05b546b091184f",
                        "answer": "hiii",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636a78788152c428092ed35a",
                            "currentRole": "Manager",
                            "email": "yo@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Yo",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-08T15:40:40.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:44:24.701Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637e0ee9a00c393d8f8be7a7",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T06:50:47.489Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637f14797b05b546b091301d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f0ebe7b05b546b091184f",
                        "answer": "hjj",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636a78788152c428092ed35a",
                            "currentRole": "Manager",
                            "email": "yo@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Yo",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-08T15:40:40.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:44:24.701Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637e0ee9a00c393d8f8be7a7",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T06:51:37.012Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637f14d87b05b546b0913162",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f0ebe7b05b546b091184f",
                        "answer": "hghhg",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636a78788152c428092ed35a",
                            "currentRole": "Manager",
                            "email": "yo@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Yo",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-08T15:40:40.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:44:24.701Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637e0ee9a00c393d8f8be7a7",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T06:53:12.591Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637f14ea7b05b546b09131f0",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f0ebe7b05b546b091184f",
                        "answer": "sfcd",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636a78788152c428092ed35a",
                            "currentRole": "Manager",
                            "email": "yo@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Yo",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-08T15:40:40.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:44:24.701Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637e0ee9a00c393d8f8be7a7",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T06:53:30.266Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637f15547b05b546b091332f",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f0ebe7b05b546b091184f",
                        "answer": "Testtsttst",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636a78788152c428092ed35a",
                            "currentRole": "Manager",
                            "email": "yo@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Yo",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-08T15:40:40.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:44:24.701Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637e0ee9a00c393d8f8be7a7",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T06:55:16.726Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637f15f37b05b546b0913388",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f0ebe7b05b546b091184f",
                        "answer": "fff",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636a78788152c428092ed35a",
                            "currentRole": "Manager",
                            "email": "yo@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Yo",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-08T15:40:40.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:44:24.701Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637e0ee9a00c393d8f8be7a7",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T06:57:55.400Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637f16347b05b546b09133e1",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f0ebe7b05b546b091184f",
                        "answer": "dc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636a78788152c428092ed35a",
                            "currentRole": "Manager",
                            "email": "yo@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Yo",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-08T15:40:40.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:44:24.701Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637e0ee9a00c393d8f8be7a7",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T06:59:00.048Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637f16617b05b546b091343a",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f0ebe7b05b546b091184f",
                        "answer": "vcv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636a78788152c428092ed35a",
                            "currentRole": "Manager",
                            "email": "yo@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Yo",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-08T15:40:40.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:44:24.701Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637e0ee9a00c393d8f8be7a7",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T06:59:45.271Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637f16a17b05b546b091351c",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f0ebe7b05b546b091184f",
                        "answer": "cv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636a78788152c428092ed35a",
                            "currentRole": "Manager",
                            "email": "yo@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Yo",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-08T15:40:40.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:44:24.701Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637e0ee9a00c393d8f8be7a7",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T07:00:49.148Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637f17097b05b546b091369f",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f0ebe7b05b546b091184f",
                        "answer": "kh\n",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636a78788152c428092ed35a",
                            "currentRole": "Manager",
                            "email": "yo@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Yo",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-08T15:40:40.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:44:24.701Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637e0ee9a00c393d8f8be7a7",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T07:02:33.801Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637f1a187b05b546b091387e",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f0ebe7b05b546b091184f",
                        "answer": "iughj",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636a78788152c428092ed35a",
                            "currentRole": "Manager",
                            "email": "yo@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Yo",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-08T15:40:40.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:44:24.701Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637e0ee9a00c393d8f8be7a7",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T07:15:36.395Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637f1a367b05b546b0913928",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f0ebe7b05b546b091184f",
                        "answer": "mnkj\n",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636a78788152c428092ed35a",
                            "currentRole": "Manager",
                            "email": "yo@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Yo",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-08T15:40:40.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:44:24.701Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637e0ee9a00c393d8f8be7a7",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T07:16:06.560Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "testttttt",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6373a7eea5322d31357ff110",
                    "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer",
                    "email": "ym@yopmail.com",
                    "name": "Ym",
                    "createdAt": "2022-11-15T14:53:34.480Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:40.349Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-11-23T12:15:37.357Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 23
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eef28553e7ab6730c5b9",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a82568bfdc0428e7c8a1",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef28553e7ab6730c5b9",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3f5c594dcace72f591c",
                            "name": "Jim Red",
                            "email": "rojjim@hotmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2020-11-25T21:44:54.463Z",
                            "currentRole": "Manager"
                        },
                        "answer": "Increased pcompensation and added covid19 protection.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-04-16T00:10:10.521Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a82568bfdc0428e7c89f",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How are you managing health care worker fatigue in your organization?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3ecc594dcace72f58f5",
                    "name": "Claire Beltmann",
                    "email": "cbeltmann@luc.edu",
                    "createdAt": "2020-10-20T20:34:37.140Z",
                    "currentRole": "Assistant Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-02-16T16:24:27.459Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eef28553e7ab6730c5b3",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a82168bfdc0428e7c803",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef28553e7ab6730c5b3",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c40bc594dcace72f5a78",
                            "name": "Kevin Lee",
                            "email": "kevin.lee@t32dental.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-24T00:41:36.464Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "1. Always important to set and quantify the desired outcomes with KPIs in the M&A/partnership deal.  2. KPIs is not always in $ terms. KPIs can include number of patients, retention rate of patients, new patients growth rate and number of visits per patients per year. 3. The KPIs will then lead to a $ value which you can measure against your investment cost 4. Set milestones to assess whether your KPIs are met. 5. In terms of deal structure, ideal to have an \"unwinding\" mechanism if KPIs not met and the deal is not up to expectations. (But this is not always possible)",
                        "createdAt": "2021-03-25T00:43:05.074Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a82068bfdc0428e7c801",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "As you pursue mergers, acquisitions, and partnerships, how are you ensuring the end result of the deal will preserve your local market edge?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3ecc594dcace72f58f8",
                    "name": "MollyDriscoll",
                    "email": "mdriscoll2@luc.edu",
                    "createdAt": "2020-10-07T01:12:14.277Z",
                    "currentRole": "CEO"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-02-12T00:23:50.800Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeee8553e7ab6730c56f",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8be68bfdc0428e7dda3",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeee8553e7ab6730c56f",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "You absolutely should, but be mindful of how you choose a consultant. You're going to not only want someone who can perform the analysis broadly but someone who also knows and is current in the industry you're operating in.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-03-03T18:20:03.331Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8be68bfdc0428e7dda1",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "I want to ensure that my start-up doesn't have any missing links or gaps within the entire process, I think a gap analysis is needed by I don't have the knowledge/background for that. Should I hire a consultant for this?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3e5c594dcace72f5893",
                    "name": "Firzana",
                    "email": "firzana218@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-12-29T20:45:55.686Z",
                    "currentRole": "Other"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-03-01T22:02:35.593Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6274e86f303ea01e07c6b17b",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6274e8e5303ea01e07c6b3af",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6274e8d9303ea01e07c6b366",
                        "answer": "using eye contact",
                        "question": "6274e86f303ea01e07c6b17b",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-06T09:22:45.291Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6274ea09303ea01e07c6b5e0",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6274e8d9303ea01e07c6b366",
                        "answer": "thanks for accept request",
                        "question": "6274e86f303ea01e07c6b17b",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-06T09:27:37.122Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "62750a4e303ea01e07c6c3bc",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6274e8d9303ea01e07c6b366",
                        "answer": "vc",
                        "question": "6274e86f303ea01e07c6b17b",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-06T11:45:18.859Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "62750a506b67dd03a0aaae1a",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "62750a4c6b67dd03a0aaadf1",
                        "answer": "rrr",
                        "question": "6274e86f303ea01e07c6b17b",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-06T11:45:20.049Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "62750a646b67dd03a0aaae5d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "62750a4c6b67dd03a0aaadf1",
                        "answer": "cvbvcb",
                        "question": "6274e86f303ea01e07c6b17b",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-06T11:45:40.768Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "62750aa2303ea01e07c6c3dd",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6274e8d9303ea01e07c6b366",
                        "answer": "vcb",
                        "question": "6274e86f303ea01e07c6b17b",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-06T11:46:42.446Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "62750aa8303ea01e07c6c3fd",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6274e8d9303ea01e07c6b366",
                        "answer": "vcbc",
                        "question": "6274e86f303ea01e07c6b17b",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-06T11:46:48.546Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "62750aae303ea01e07c6c41d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6274e8d9303ea01e07c6b366",
                        "answer": "vcbcvcvccvbvc",
                        "question": "6274e86f303ea01e07c6b17b",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-06T11:46:54.559Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "62750ab4303ea01e07c6c43d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6274e8d9303ea01e07c6b366",
                        "answer": "cvbvcbc",
                        "question": "6274e86f303ea01e07c6b17b",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-06T11:47:00.498Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "62750ae36b67dd03a0aab0b9",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "62750a4c6b67dd03a0aaadf1",
                        "answer": "v",
                        "question": "6274e86f303ea01e07c6b17b",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-06T11:47:47.954Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "62750b13303ea01e07c6c45d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6274e8d9303ea01e07c6b366",
                        "answer": "cvbcvbcvbcvbcvbcvbcv",
                        "question": "6274e86f303ea01e07c6b17b",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-06T11:48:35.769Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "62750b106b67dd03a0aab0fa",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "62750a4c6b67dd03a0aaadf1",
                        "answer": "cvbvcb",
                        "question": "6274e86f303ea01e07c6b17b",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-06T11:48:32.869Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "62750b246b67dd03a0aab13b",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "62750a4c6b67dd03a0aaadf1",
                        "answer": "zxcxzczx",
                        "question": "6274e86f303ea01e07c6b17b",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-06T11:48:52.020Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "62750b5c303ea01e07c6c47d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6274e8d9303ea01e07c6b366",
                        "answer": "hello",
                        "question": "6274e86f303ea01e07c6b17b",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-06T11:49:48.184Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6278a133d45e34247c937b3f",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6274e8d9303ea01e07c6b366",
                        "answer": "okay",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "624d5ba9d500ad509757879c",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer",
                            "email": "tehav55741@nuesond.com",
                            "name": "Tehav",
                            "createdAt": "2022-04-06T09:21:45.077Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-10-10T04:11:45.916Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6274e86f303ea01e07c6b17b",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-09T05:05:55.253Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6286115ffa4fe26e53183a23",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 1,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "627697ead1728c442a22c61b",
                        "answer": "The way on how  manages time ",
                        "question": "6274e86f303ea01e07c6b17b",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-19T09:43:59.408Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "how to get best thing from leader?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "624d5ba9d500ad509757879c",
                    "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer",
                    "email": "tehav55741@nuesond.com",
                    "name": "Tehav",
                    "createdAt": "2022-04-06T09:21:45.077Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-10-10T04:11:45.916Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-05-06T09:20:47.513Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 16
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eef48553e7ab6730c5da",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a83868bfdc0428e7cb4a",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef48553e7ab6730c5da",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c417c594dcace72f5b43",
                            "name": "John Lindner",
                            "email": "john@sagresconsulting.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-05-04T14:25:48.846Z",
                            "currentRole": "Co-Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "Use a competency-based evaluation process and agree to a structured approach up front.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-05-14T19:02:21.861Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a83868bfdc0428e7cb48",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a83268bfdc0428e7ca68",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef48553e7ab6730c5da",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c416c594dcace72f5b2b",
                            "name": "Charlie Atkinson",
                            "email": "charlie.atkinson@hfi.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-04-29T16:41:57.283Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "Instincts are shortcuts that we make in decision making. They are vital for us to cope with everyday life. We develop good instincts when we encounter the same situation and the same outcome again and again. Most of us drive mainly on instinct. We don't think about which foot to use to push the brake or how many degrees to turn the wheel. This allows us to invest more of our conscious thought in other tasks such as looking out for other drvers, or following directions on our satnav. But it also stops us forom questioning our decisions. In the US, when I pull up to a red light, I assume it is okay to turn right, and I often do without much thought. That wouldn't go down well in the UK, where other drivers and pedestrians will be assuming that I will stop. When we apply these mental shortcuts to activities such as hiring, we also make decisions without challenging our assumptions, and that is the root of bias. The answer is to use data to challenge decisions. There is an article about this on HBR, https://online.hbs.edu/blog/post/data-driven-decision-making. My business is providing data to support hiring decisions. So connect with me if you are interested and we can discuss further.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-04-29T17:15:34.717Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a83268bfdc0428e7ca66",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a83468bfdc0428e7cab6",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef48553e7ab6730c5da",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c412c594dcace72f5af7",
                            "name": "George Kondrach",
                            "email": "gkondrach@amplikai.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-04-20T02:49:59.436Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "Yes. Have a variety of interviewers use structured questions [scripts], use validated [as of 2021 only 'big5' or 'HEXACO'] diversity assessments that go deep in assessing important factors. Involve at least one manager-once-removed in hiring discussion/decision. Don't delegage to HR.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-04-29T17:40:26.126Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a83468bfdc0428e7cab4",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a83668bfdc0428e7cafe",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef48553e7ab6730c5da",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c416c594dcace72f5b31",
                            "name": "Todd Harrison",
                            "email": "todd.harrison@deltafaucet.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-04-30T11:58:30.420Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Absolutely!  Any hiring manager can fall victim to confirmation bias. Ways to check for bias include using a panel interview of trusted people as part of the hiring process. Also, the use of objective pre-hire assessments focused on the most critical knowledge, skills, and abilities can uncover bias.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-04-30T12:21:17.357Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a83668bfdc0428e7cafc",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a82568bfdc0428e7c8ba",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef48553e7ab6730c5da",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c411c594dcace72f5ae2",
                            "name": "Devin Marks",
                            "email": "devin.ridleymarks@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-04-16T02:36:55.760Z",
                            "currentRole": "President"
                        },
                        "answer": "Depends on the Co. size, but rely on an HR process and POC.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-04-17T01:33:54.077Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a82568bfdc0428e7c8b8",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Can leaders cause confirmation bias in hiring decisions because they trust their instincts too much? What would you do to avoid such bias?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3ecc594dcace72f58f8",
                    "name": "MollyDriscoll",
                    "email": "mdriscoll2@luc.edu",
                    "createdAt": "2020-10-07T01:12:14.277Z",
                    "currentRole": "CEO"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-04-15T16:18:42.773Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 5
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee68553e7ab6730c4f1",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a89268bfdc0428e7d722",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee68553e7ab6730c4f1",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3e4c594dcace72f5884",
                            "name": "Fosan",
                            "email": "fosan73447@xtrempro.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-12-23T05:44:46.221Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Vice President"
                        },
                        "answer": "drhh",
                        "createdAt": "2021-12-28T06:20:00.822Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a89268bfdc0428e7d720",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a88e68bfdc0428e7d6c6",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee68553e7ab6730c4f1",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3ecc594dcace72f58f8",
                            "name": "MollyDriscoll",
                            "email": "mdriscoll2@luc.edu",
                            "createdAt": "2020-10-07T01:12:14.277Z",
                            "currentRole": "CEO"
                        },
                        "answer": "I love listening to Dare to Lead with Brene Brown! I find it entertaining yet informative",
                        "createdAt": "2021-12-23T23:19:32.731Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a88e68bfdc0428e7d6c4",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a88f68bfdc0428e7d6cd",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee68553e7ab6730c4f1",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                            "name": "Saima Omar",
                            "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Thank you for the recommendation!",
                        "createdAt": "2021-12-23T23:37:17.338Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a88e68bfdc0428e7d6c4",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8a768bfdc0428e7da4c",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee68553e7ab6730c4f1",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "I find A Slight Change in Plans a really helpful podcast with its basis in neuroscience and behavior",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-03T16:44:01.933Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8a768bfdc0428e7da4a",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Can you recommend any good podcasts for leaders?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-12-20T16:00:16.169Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 4
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee98553e7ab6730c51e",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a89f68bfdc0428e7d91c",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee98553e7ab6730c51e",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "A couple of options, which both involve asking for feedback can be used to see if the issue is with communication: Asking a peer if your vision is clear. Talk to someone you trust who can hear you objectively about what you're trying to do and then ask that person to tell you what they understand about what you said. The alternative is doing the same thing with your employees. I would suggest the first suggestion followed by the second. If there is a lack of focus, is that because your short-term goals are not clearly connected to your long-term goals?",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-21T20:02:37.899Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a89f68bfdc0428e7d91a",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "I’m worried that my company has lost its vision. I cannot tell whether this is an issues with communication or with focus, but I worry that if I can’t find the source if the issue soon, my team may lose their commitment entirely. What can I do to fix this?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c41dc594dcace72f5b9b",
                    "name": "Madeleine",
                    "email": "maddykindler11@yahoo.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-06-10T18:10:27.425Z",
                    "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-01-20T20:46:34.022Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eedb8553e7ab6730c452",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a83e68bfdc0428e7cc0e",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedb8553e7ab6730c452",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c41cc594dcace72f5b95",
                            "name": "Alec Jiggins",
                            "email": "mralecjiggins@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-06-08T20:46:27.500Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "I have a daily practice of journaling, meditating, and affirmations. It has brought me greater peace and self awareness, and that has helped me be a better leader.\nI am aware of when I am feeling triggered, can quickly identify the source, and then take action to regulate. ",
                        "createdAt": "2021-06-09T20:59:03.545Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a83e68bfdc0428e7cc0c",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a85068bfdc0428e7cedd",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedb8553e7ab6730c452",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3ecc594dcace72f58f8",
                            "name": "MollyDriscoll",
                            "email": "mdriscoll2@luc.edu",
                            "createdAt": "2020-10-07T01:12:14.277Z",
                            "currentRole": "CEO"
                        },
                        "answer": "I've heard good things. Do you practice it yourself every day?",
                        "createdAt": "2021-09-17T17:34:32.688Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84f68bfdc0428e7cec3",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84f68bfdc0428e7cec5",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedb8553e7ab6730c452",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f05c594dcace72f5c55",
                            "name": "Gurbani Luthra",
                            "email": "gurbaniluthra@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-09-16T19:54:21.528Z",
                            "currentRole": "Other"
                        },
                        "answer": "Self compassion is the key to self improvement and self realisation. If one can be compassionate to oneself, then one wishes to help oneself, learning from mistakes and improving.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-09-17T10:16:22.146Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84f68bfdc0428e7cec3",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "What benefits have you experienced from practicing self-compassion?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3ecc594dcace72f58f8",
                    "name": "MollyDriscoll",
                    "email": "mdriscoll2@luc.edu",
                    "createdAt": "2020-10-07T01:12:14.277Z",
                    "currentRole": "CEO"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-06-02T19:46:38.924Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 3
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee38553e7ab6730c4c6",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a87368bfdc0428e7d3bf",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee38553e7ab6730c4c6",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                            "name": "Saima Omar",
                            "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Here!",
                        "createdAt": "2021-11-22T16:09:04.366Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a87368bfdc0428e7d3bd",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Where is my tribe???",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "62218f0ac594dcace72f5cb1",
                    "name": "Michael Angel Casas",
                    "email": "michael@houstonhpllc.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-11-18T03:46:09.696Z",
                    "currentRole": "Founder"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-11-18T03:52:07.430Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeeb8553e7ab6730c538",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8ac68bfdc0428e7db0f",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeeb8553e7ab6730c538",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "It helps to think very carefully about the jobs you're submitting your resume for. Likely you can find responsibilities in previous jobs that either translate or parallel qualifications in the job you're applying for. You'll want to highlight and reframe your duties and experience accordingly!",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-09T18:08:20.766Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8ac68bfdc0428e7db0d",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8ae68bfdc0428e7db75",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeeb8553e7ab6730c538",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3e8c594dcace72f58c9",
                            "name": "Nina Blackmon",
                            "email": "ninasblackmon@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2022-02-08T19:19:31.120Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-05-05T17:43:54.724Z",
                            "currentRole": "Other"
                        },
                        "answer": "It's important to write to the future, not the past. Your resumé is a marketing document, and your current career goals should always determine which parts of your story to highlight and which to minimize. With that, you want to make sure you're showcasing “wow factor”, just a quick hit of information that highlights your achievements and that shows up prominently throughout your resumé. Also as cliché as it may sound, spicing up the design on your resumé can help as well. Cautiously of course, but color, shading, boxes, charts, tables, images and icons can be valuable additions to your resumé, helping to make it stand out. Just make sure your design matches industry norms for your field.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-12T02:03:14.832Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8ac68bfdc0428e7db04",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8ad68bfdc0428e7db31",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeeb8553e7ab6730c538",
                        "answer": "I believe it is key to include a section that highlights your skills. For example, I have been in interviews where they are only interested in my knowledge of a specific application on my resume",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-11T02:48:24.478Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8ad68bfdc0428e7db2f",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8ac68bfdc0428e7db06",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeeb8553e7ab6730c538",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3e8c594dcace72f58c9",
                            "name": "Nina Blackmon",
                            "email": "ninasblackmon@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2022-02-08T19:19:31.120Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-05-05T17:43:54.724Z",
                            "currentRole": "Other"
                        },
                        "answer": "Testing 1 😊",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-08T19:31:52.349Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8ac68bfdc0428e7db04",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How can one enhance their resume?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3e6c594dcace72f58aa",
                    "name": "Amarachi Emezie",
                    "email": "amarachieemezie@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2022-01-12T18:41:13.277Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-05-09T15:13:09.331Z",
                    "currentRole": "Other"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-02-08T19:30:23.139Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 4
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeeb8553e7ab6730c53d",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8b468bfdc0428e7dc3f",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeeb8553e7ab6730c53d",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c41dc594dcace72f5b9b",
                            "name": "Madeleine",
                            "email": "maddykindler11@yahoo.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-06-10T18:10:27.425Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "in terms of funding, based off what it has cost to self-fund, what amount of external funding would not only be sufficient but would allow you to successfully expand your business?",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-15T21:03:53.625Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8b468bfdc0428e7dc3d",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8c168bfdc0428e7de0d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeeb8553e7ab6730c53d",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                            "name": "Saima Omar",
                            "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "But how do I make my company investible?",
                        "createdAt": "2022-03-05T03:41:41.903Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8c068bfdc0428e7dddb",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8b668bfdc0428e7dca9",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeeb8553e7ab6730c53d",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3e8c594dcace72f58c9",
                            "name": "Nina Blackmon",
                            "email": "ninasblackmon@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2022-02-08T19:19:31.120Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-05-05T17:43:54.724Z",
                            "currentRole": "Other"
                        },
                        "answer": "It's important to keep short and long-term plans for growth in mind, this sets realistic expectations and can protect your equity and control. Building relationships with investors is a long game; relationships with investors should be built by showing the progress and mistakes you've made along the way. You should also keep in mind your vision vs your potential investor's, if both parties visions aren't aiming toward the same direction, it could give rise to several problems.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-21T23:55:34.094Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8b668bfdc0428e7dca7",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8c068bfdc0428e7dddd",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeeb8553e7ab6730c53d",
                        "answer": "That self funding is not sustainable and you really, really need outside funding ASAP.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-03-04T04:16:35.570Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8c068bfdc0428e7dddb",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8c168bfdc0428e7de06",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeeb8553e7ab6730c53d",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                            "name": "Saima Omar",
                            "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Thanks! Have you successfully raised before?",
                        "createdAt": "2022-03-05T03:39:19.070Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8b668bfdc0428e7dca7",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "I am self-funding my business at the moment. What must I keep in mind when I am going to look for outside funding?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-02-11T22:14:19.380Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 5
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeec8553e7ab6730c54b",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8b668bfdc0428e7dc97",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeec8553e7ab6730c54b",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c41dc594dcace72f5b9b",
                            "name": "Madeleine",
                            "email": "maddykindler11@yahoo.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-06-10T18:10:27.425Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "A great idea (unfortunately) cannot be successful without proper financial support, so it is often important to alter your vision if it means that your finances are better accounted for.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-21T18:40:01.501Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8b668bfdc0428e7dc95",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8b668bfdc0428e7dca0",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeec8553e7ab6730c54b",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3e8c594dcace72f58c9",
                            "name": "Nina Blackmon",
                            "email": "ninasblackmon@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2022-02-08T19:19:31.120Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-05-05T17:43:54.724Z",
                            "currentRole": "Other"
                        },
                        "answer": "Hiring (the right) amazing talent is both the most difficult thing and the most transformative for business. Not running out of money! Try to only think in terms of cash. It's beneficial for founders to form a strong cash management plan.\nThings might seem all peachy, but you have to ask yourself immediately, 'What if things don't go exactly as I expect them to?'”",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-21T23:44:57.265Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8b668bfdc0428e7dc9e",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8b868bfdc0428e7dce1",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeec8553e7ab6730c54b",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3e6c594dcace72f58a1",
                            "name": "Srijal",
                            "email": "srijalsharma01@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2022-01-10T12:30:06.951Z",
                            "currentRole": "Manager"
                        },
                        "answer": "that's very accurate and helpful. thankyou",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-23T12:29:33.133Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8b668bfdc0428e7dc95",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "What is the most important financial advice you would give to a founder?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3e6c594dcace72f58a1",
                    "name": "Srijal",
                    "email": "srijalsharma01@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2022-01-10T12:30:06.951Z",
                    "currentRole": "Manager"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-02-16T07:55:14.903Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 3
            },
            {
                "_id": "6380b4e25df10215e438e1b9",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6380b4f35df10215e438e333",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380b4ee5df10215e438e2ef",
                        "answer": "vcbvc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380b4e25df10215e438e1b9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:28:35.455Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380b5095df10215e438e39e",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380b4ee5df10215e438e2ef",
                        "answer": "vbv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380b4e25df10215e438e1b9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:28:57.286Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380b5105df10215e438e3de",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380b4ee5df10215e438e2ef",
                        "answer": "vbvc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380b4e25df10215e438e1b9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:29:04.811Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380b5515df10215e438e476",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380b4ee5df10215e438e2ef",
                        "answer": "nbvn",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380b4e25df10215e438e1b9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:30:09.754Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380b5565df10215e438e4b6",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380b4ee5df10215e438e2ef",
                        "answer": "vn",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380b4e25df10215e438e1b9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:30:14.136Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380b5b85df10215e438e4f8",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380b4ee5df10215e438e2ef",
                        "answer": "cvb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380b4e25df10215e438e1b9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:31:52.631Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380b5bc5df10215e438e54e",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380b4ee5df10215e438e2ef",
                        "answer": "c",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380b4e25df10215e438e1b9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:31:56.230Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380b5bd5df10215e438e57e",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380b4ee5df10215e438e2ef",
                        "answer": "vcbvc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380b4e25df10215e438e1b9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:31:57.144Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380b5ca5df10215e438e5ca",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380b4ee5df10215e438e2ef",
                        "answer": "cvbc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380b4e25df10215e438e1b9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:32:10.538Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380b5ee5df10215e438e60b",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380b4ee5df10215e438e2ef",
                        "answer": "cvbvc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380b4e25df10215e438e1b9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:32:46.589Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6380b5f35df10215e438e65e",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [
                            "6295d4235334af3e0848a064"
                        ],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6380b4ee5df10215e438e2ef",
                        "answer": "cvcbcv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6380b4e25df10215e438e1b9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:32:51.066Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "VDDDDDD",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                    "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                    "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                    "name": "vijay",
                    "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-11-25T12:28:18.619Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 11
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeea8553e7ab6730c52c",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8ad68bfdc0428e7db43",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeea8553e7ab6730c52c",
                        "answer": "Find a good support system or team. It it challenging to do it all on your own.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-11T02:53:26.348Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8ad68bfdc0428e7db41",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8ae68bfdc0428e7db55",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeea8553e7ab6730c52c",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                            "name": "Saima Omar",
                            "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Tap into your existing network to see whether the idea resonates.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-11T22:16:43.554Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8ae68bfdc0428e7db53",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "What's the best piece of advice you've received starting your own business?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                    "name": "Daniel Daws",
                    "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                    "currentRole": "Founder"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-02-03T15:03:06.187Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "637bac8d3f1dee1dce572ab3",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "637baf483f1dee1dce573122",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637baf413f1dee1dce5730ec",
                        "answer": "answer",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637b9a6f3f1dee1dce57280b",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "com3@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Comp",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-21T15:34:07.381Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-21T17:11:16.745Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637bac8d3f1dee1dce572ab3",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-21T17:03:04.479Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Test",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "637b99e73f1dee1dce5727d0",
                    "currentRole": "Manager",
                    "email": "com2@yopmail.com",
                    "name": "Com2",
                    "createdAt": "2022-11-21T15:31:51.823Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-11-21T17:01:55.201Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-11-21T16:51:25.240Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "637f1d9275ad19522cd336ee",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "637f1da475ad19522cd33830",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f1d9c75ad19522cd337c8",
                        "answer": "guu\n",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637da81d1a33343c8375a58a",
                            "currentRole": "Manager",
                            "email": "vijay087.rejoice@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-23T04:57:01.461Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-23T04:57:01.462Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f1d9275ad19522cd336ee",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T07:30:44.003Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637f1e0875ad19522cd33886",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f1d9c75ad19522cd337c8",
                        "answer": "xvxcvb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637da81d1a33343c8375a58a",
                            "currentRole": "Manager",
                            "email": "vijay087.rejoice@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-23T04:57:01.461Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-23T04:57:01.462Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f1d9275ad19522cd336ee",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T07:32:24.197Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637f2da575ad19522cd33b07",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f1d9c75ad19522cd337c8",
                        "answer": "nm,m",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637e1dd2d77248167cfea1a6",
                            "currentRole": "Founder",
                            "email": "vijay0877.rejoice@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-23T13:19:14.205Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-23T13:19:14.206Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f1d9275ad19522cd336ee",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T08:39:01.644Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637f2da675ad19522cd33b60",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f1d9c75ad19522cd337c8",
                        "answer": "nm,m",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637e1dd2d77248167cfea1a6",
                            "currentRole": "Founder",
                            "email": "vijay0877.rejoice@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-23T13:19:14.205Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-23T13:19:14.206Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f1d9275ad19522cd336ee",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T08:39:02.779Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637f2da975ad19522cd33bfb",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f1d9c75ad19522cd337c8",
                        "answer": "nm,mn",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637e1dd2d77248167cfea1a6",
                            "currentRole": "Founder",
                            "email": "vijay0877.rejoice@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-23T13:19:14.205Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-23T13:19:14.206Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f1d9275ad19522cd336ee",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T08:39:05.678Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637f2daa75ad19522cd33c49",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f1d9c75ad19522cd337c8",
                        "answer": "nm,",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637e1dd2d77248167cfea1a6",
                            "currentRole": "Founder",
                            "email": "vijay0877.rejoice@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-23T13:19:14.205Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-23T13:19:14.206Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f1d9275ad19522cd336ee",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T08:39:06.888Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637f2dab75ad19522cd33c9d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f1d9c75ad19522cd337c8",
                        "answer": "mn,m",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637e1dd2d77248167cfea1a6",
                            "currentRole": "Founder",
                            "email": "vijay0877.rejoice@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-23T13:19:14.205Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-23T13:19:14.206Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f1d9275ad19522cd336ee",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T08:39:07.946Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637f2dad75ad19522cd33cef",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f1d9c75ad19522cd337c8",
                        "answer": "nm,mn",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637e1dd2d77248167cfea1a6",
                            "currentRole": "Founder",
                            "email": "vijay0877.rejoice@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-23T13:19:14.205Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-23T13:19:14.206Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f1d9275ad19522cd336ee",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T08:39:09.181Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637f2dae75ad19522cd33d46",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f1d9c75ad19522cd337c8",
                        "answer": "nm,",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637e1dd2d77248167cfea1a6",
                            "currentRole": "Founder",
                            "email": "vijay0877.rejoice@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-23T13:19:14.205Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-23T13:19:14.206Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f1d9275ad19522cd336ee",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T08:39:10.954Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637f2daf75ad19522cd33d5b",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f1d9c75ad19522cd337c8",
                        "answer": "nm,mn,",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637e1dd2d77248167cfea1a6",
                            "currentRole": "Founder",
                            "email": "vijay0877.rejoice@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-23T13:19:14.205Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-23T13:19:14.206Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f1d9275ad19522cd336ee",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T08:39:11.368Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637f2db075ad19522cd33db6",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f1d9c75ad19522cd337c8",
                        "answer": "nm,",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637e1dd2d77248167cfea1a6",
                            "currentRole": "Founder",
                            "email": "vijay0877.rejoice@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-23T13:19:14.205Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-23T13:19:14.206Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f1d9275ad19522cd336ee",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T08:39:12.030Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637f2db175ad19522cd33df2",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f1d9c75ad19522cd337c8",
                        "answer": "nm,n",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637e1dd2d77248167cfea1a6",
                            "currentRole": "Founder",
                            "email": "vijay0877.rejoice@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-23T13:19:14.205Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-23T13:19:14.206Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f1d9275ad19522cd336ee",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T08:39:13.106Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637f2db175ad19522cd33e2f",
                        "isUpdated": true,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f1d9c75ad19522cd337c8",
                        "answer": "m,nm,nm,mn",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637e1dd2d77248167cfea1a6",
                            "currentRole": "Founder",
                            "email": "vijay0877.rejoice@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-23T13:19:14.205Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-23T13:19:14.206Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f1d9275ad19522cd336ee",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T08:39:13.814Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637f2db275ad19522cd33e5b",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f1d9c75ad19522cd337c8",
                        "answer": "nm,mn,",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637e1dd2d77248167cfea1a6",
                            "currentRole": "Founder",
                            "email": "vijay0877.rejoice@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-23T13:19:14.205Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-23T13:19:14.206Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f1d9275ad19522cd336ee",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T08:39:14.241Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637f2db475ad19522cd33f36",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637f1d9c75ad19522cd337c8",
                        "answer": "n,nmn,mn,,mn,mn,nm,mn,mn,mn,mn,nm,",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637e1dd2d77248167cfea1a6",
                            "currentRole": "Founder",
                            "email": "vijay0877.rejoice@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-23T13:19:14.205Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-23T13:19:14.206Z"
                        },
                        "question": "637f1d9275ad19522cd336ee",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-24T08:39:16.965Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "AAAAA",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "637e1dd2d77248167cfea1a6",
                    "currentRole": "Founder",
                    "email": "vijay0877.rejoice@yopmail.com",
                    "name": "vijay",
                    "createdAt": "2022-11-23T13:19:14.205Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-11-23T13:19:14.206Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-11-24T07:30:26.382Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 15
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeeb8553e7ab6730c535",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8ac68bfdc0428e7db21",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeeb8553e7ab6730c535",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "A couple of the best ways is to clarify exactly what your start-up is offering, then, if you don't have a market researcher on your team, outsource one.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-09T18:13:03.434Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8ac68bfdc0428e7db1f",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "What are some of the best ways to understand market demand for your start-up idea?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-02-06T18:56:32.040Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eedf8553e7ab6730c48f",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a85368bfdc0428e7cf3d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedf8553e7ab6730c48f",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f06c594dcace72f5c69",
                            "name": "Dom Ramirez",
                            "email": "dom+lb@betacanon.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-09-30T17:27:34.155Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "Test answer!",
                        "createdAt": "2021-09-30T17:31:52.355Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a85268bfdc0428e7cf3b",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "test question",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "62218f06c594dcace72f5c64",
                    "name": "Sage Fiorentino-Lange",
                    "email": "sage.fio.lange@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-09-29T00:01:18.088Z",
                    "currentRole": "Other"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-09-29T00:10:18.077Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee88553e7ab6730c50a",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a89868bfdc0428e7d822",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee88553e7ab6730c50a",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "Being aware that I'm not going to automatically be rid of my biases just because I strive to be is a good starting place. It's helpful to take a third-person perspective of what you're doing and why you're making the decisions you're making.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-12T21:41:53.564Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a89868bfdc0428e7d820",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How have you committed to being mindful of your cognitive biases in judgement and decision-making, especially when in a professional environment?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c41dc594dcace72f5b9b",
                    "name": "Madeleine",
                    "email": "maddykindler11@yahoo.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-06-10T18:10:27.425Z",
                    "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-01-11T16:05:11.254Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eef28553e7ab6730c5bc",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a82768bfdc0428e7c902",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef28553e7ab6730c5bc",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c411c594dcace72f5ae2",
                            "name": "Devin Marks",
                            "email": "devin.ridleymarks@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-04-16T02:36:55.760Z",
                            "currentRole": "President"
                        },
                        "answer": "Not sharing it.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-04-17T01:40:23.255Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a82768bfdc0428e7c900",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "What is your method for keeping confidential information private?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3ecc594dcace72f58f5",
                    "name": "Claire Beltmann",
                    "email": "cbeltmann@luc.edu",
                    "createdAt": "2020-10-20T20:34:37.140Z",
                    "currentRole": "Assistant Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-02-18T16:31:16.686Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee88553e7ab6730c50b",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a89868bfdc0428e7d819",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee88553e7ab6730c50b",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "What's more important is to be shrewd with your resources. If this involves naming a COO, do that. But be attentive to what level of oversight your operations require before building out your C-suite.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-12T21:37:31.679Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a89868bfdc0428e7d817",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "As a start-up company, is it important to have a COO?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3e6c594dcace72f58a1",
                    "name": "Srijal",
                    "email": "srijalsharma01@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2022-01-10T12:30:06.951Z",
                    "currentRole": "Manager"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-01-12T10:12:26.328Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee88553e7ab6730c513",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a89b68bfdc0428e7d89a",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee88553e7ab6730c513",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "હેલો",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-13T16:28:42.474Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a89a68bfdc0428e7d866",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "My e-commerce start-up is hitting a wall with digging into a niche market. I know there are researchers out there who do this kind of work, but I'm not sure how to find one. Does anyone have suggestions about choosing a market researcher?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                    "name": "Daniel Daws",
                    "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                    "currentRole": "Founder"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-01-12T21:15:53.757Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee68553e7ab6730c4ea",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a88b68bfdc0428e7d647",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee68553e7ab6730c4ea",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "It's important to set some strict boundaries there. If it's email that keeps dragging you into work mode, then utilize some do not disturb features so that you won't be tempted in the first place. If that's not enough put your phone or laptop in a difficult to get to space so that you'll have to make more conscious decisions to engage with them rather than defaulting to habit.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-12-17T20:50:34.333Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a88b68bfdc0428e7d645",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "With the holidays coming up, how do you best manage balancing work, life, and family? I am someone who struggles to separate from my work sometimes, but I don't want that to takeaway from making memories with my loved ones.",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c41dc594dcace72f5b9b",
                    "name": "Madeleine",
                    "email": "maddykindler11@yahoo.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-06-10T18:10:27.425Z",
                    "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-12-16T20:25:26.390Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eede8553e7ab6730c47a",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a85068bfdc0428e7cee6",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eede8553e7ab6730c47a",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c413c594dcace72f5b03",
                            "name": "Arijit Basu",
                            "email": "arijitb962@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-04-21T07:34:56.909Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "1) assess the mega trends (digital push, flexible working, windows of oppprtujities, etc )\n2) set direction with flexibility in mind \n3) adopt\n4) focus on collaboration - Less is More!\n5) never give up !  ",
                        "createdAt": "2021-09-20T03:51:28.264Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a85068bfdc0428e7cee4",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a85168bfdc0428e7ceed",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eede8553e7ab6730c47a",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3ecc594dcace72f58f5",
                            "name": "Claire Beltmann",
                            "email": "cbeltmann@luc.edu",
                            "createdAt": "2020-10-20T20:34:37.140Z",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Hi, thanks for your response! This is solid advice. Regarding your fourth point - collaboration - how do know when enough is enough? I'm newer to managing/leading others and this is something I'm still learning how to balance.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-09-20T16:23:26.051Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a85068bfdc0428e7cee4",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How do you lead others when you yourself are unsure of what direction to go in?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3ecc594dcace72f58f5",
                    "name": "Claire Beltmann",
                    "email": "cbeltmann@luc.edu",
                    "createdAt": "2020-10-20T20:34:37.140Z",
                    "currentRole": "Assistant Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-09-13T16:51:27.934Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeea8553e7ab6730c527",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8a568bfdc0428e7d9fb",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeea8553e7ab6730c527",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "If you are looking to set your own bar, you will want to consult with recruiters. But on a more elementary scale you can scope sites like Glassdoor to see what baseline salaries for a particular role are in your region!",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-03T15:51:08.191Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8a568bfdc0428e7d9f9",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How transparent are you about pay scales when hiring new staff? Do you advertise with your salary? Do you put \"competitive salary\" - and if so, how do you make it competitive?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-01-29T00:59:53.282Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6289c277d0a01e70a277f16a",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "628b8088eefa4111a8547d99",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 1,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "628b8084eefa4111a8547d76",
                        "answer": "gfhfgfgffgfg",
                        "question": "6289c277d0a01e70a277f16a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-23T12:39:36.933Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "628b80c207ad1c0a1cfee401",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 1,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "628b8084eefa4111a8547d76",
                        "answer": "gjghjg",
                        "question": "6289c277d0a01e70a277f16a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-23T12:40:34.973Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "628b80d707ad1c0a1cfee42e",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 1,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "628b8084eefa4111a8547d76",
                        "answer": "nghggh",
                        "question": "6289c277d0a01e70a277f16a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-23T12:40:55.755Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "628b80eb07ad1c0a1cfee545",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 1,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "628b8084eefa4111a8547d76",
                        "answer": "vbnbv",
                        "question": "6289c277d0a01e70a277f16a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-23T12:41:15.959Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "628b8be26930aa31d45a6884",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "628b8be16930aa31d45a6867",
                        "answer": "bmn",
                        "question": "6289c277d0a01e70a277f16a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-23T13:28:02.932Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "628b8c0a7dd2a8111094044d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "628b8be16930aa31d45a6867",
                        "answer": "vnv",
                        "question": "6289c277d0a01e70a277f16a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-23T13:28:42.177Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "628b8f0c0382b9470009e964",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "628b8be16930aa31d45a6867",
                        "answer": "nvb",
                        "question": "6289c277d0a01e70a277f16a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-23T13:41:32.022Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "What is the future of crypto?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6289bcdfd0a01e70a277eef1",
                    "currentRole": "Manager",
                    "email": "z.wang12@icloud.com",
                    "name": "Christy Wang",
                    "createdAt": "2022-05-22T04:32:31.532Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-26T22:50:00.514Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-05-22T04:56:23.889Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 7
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeeb8553e7ab6730c534",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8ae68bfdc0428e7db67",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeeb8553e7ab6730c534",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3e8c594dcace72f58c9",
                            "name": "Nina Blackmon",
                            "email": "ninasblackmon@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2022-02-08T19:19:31.120Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-05-05T17:43:54.724Z",
                            "currentRole": "Other"
                        },
                        "answer": "Thought they may differ by industry, some ways can include using the voice of the customers (VoC), IHUTs (In-Home Usage Testing), in-depth interviews, focus groups, even online surveys.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-12T01:46:29.508Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8ae68bfdc0428e7db65",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8ae68bfdc0428e7db6e",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeeb8553e7ab6730c534",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3e8c594dcace72f58c9",
                            "name": "Nina Blackmon",
                            "email": "ninasblackmon@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2022-02-08T19:19:31.120Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-05-05T17:43:54.724Z",
                            "currentRole": "Other"
                        },
                        "answer": "Thought they may differ by industry, some ways can include using the voice of the customers (VoC), IHUTs (In-Home Usage Testing), in-depth interviews, focus groups, even online surveys.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-12T01:47:17.255Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8ae68bfdc0428e7db65",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "What are some ways to conduct market research for my first product prototype?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-02-06T18:55:55.845Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eedb8553e7ab6730c44b",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84168bfdc0428e7cc8b",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedb8553e7ab6730c44b",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3f5c594dcace72f5919",
                            "name": "J. Mandell Carter",
                            "email": "j.m.carter2021@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2020-11-23T17:57:09.494Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "Languishing can be defeated with purpose, ideas and goals. I find it helpful to focus on a particular area of my work that may need improvement, lets say I want a better way to track my productivity or that of my team. I may choose to create a tool that will provide the data I need to inturn make adjustments to workflow. By doing so I have forced myself to be creative and I have saved money in the process. It may take a bit of time so start with one project and keep records of your progress.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-06-25T17:59:46.658Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84168bfdc0428e7cc89",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84968bfdc0428e7cdce",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedb8553e7ab6730c44b",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c424c594dcace72f5c0d",
                            "name": "Matt Maxwell",
                            "email": "matthewhmaxwell@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-07-29T13:05:04.060Z",
                            "currentRole": "Executive Vice President"
                        },
                        "answer": "I brought in a Zen priest through Zoom to lead meditation sessions to help people connect to themselves.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-07-29T22:56:24.531Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84968bfdc0428e7cdcc",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How do you alleviate languish in the workplace, especially in light of the current pandemic?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3ecc594dcace72f58f8",
                    "name": "MollyDriscoll",
                    "email": "mdriscoll2@luc.edu",
                    "createdAt": "2020-10-07T01:12:14.277Z",
                    "currentRole": "CEO"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-05-21T01:17:28.637Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee18553e7ab6730c4a9",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a86768bfdc0428e7d21f",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee18553e7ab6730c4a9",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "It depends on your relationship. Are you the same height, or is there a large height disparity?",
                        "createdAt": "2021-11-02T14:45:53.883Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a86768bfdc0428e7d21d",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Is it more difficult to build a start-up with a single founder versus having two founders?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-10-26T02:44:23.477Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eedd8553e7ab6730c46a",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84968bfdc0428e7cdd7",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedd8553e7ab6730c46a",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c417c594dcace72f5b45",
                            "name": "Scott Kuperman",
                            "email": "scott.kuperman@paintplatoon.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-05-04T18:23:00.565Z",
                            "currentRole": "President",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T16:24:41.811Z"
                        },
                        "answer": "No. Masculinity nor feminity simply never enters my mind in those situations. ",
                        "createdAt": "2021-07-30T21:49:13.419Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84968bfdc0428e7cdd5",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84a68bfdc0428e7cde0",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedd8553e7ab6730c46a",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c40ac594dcace72f5a68",
                            "name": "SANJEEV KUMAR MEHTA",
                            "email": "perfect2work@yahoo.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-19T03:28:37.568Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "My answer to such situations is the  following \n\n1. knowledge of the subject will make you earn respect \n2. If you are right make sure you voice it, if required put your foot down \n3. If you are doubtful or wrong simply accept with humility ",
                        "createdAt": "2021-07-31T17:19:18.532Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84a68bfdc0428e7cdde",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "62bf5decf6ac59655ddf324b",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "62bf5d3ef6ac59655ddf322e",
                        "answer": "This depends on the context for me as a woman. If I am in a situation in which the male leader I am dealing with is supportive and welcoming of me, then no. However, if they act in a misogynistic way or are not supportive of me, I might enact more agentic behaviors.",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62bf5a68f6ac59655ddf308c",
                            "currentRole": "Other",
                            "email": "mschaefer14@outlook.com",
                            "name": "Madison Schaefer",
                            "createdAt": "2022-07-01T20:34:48.547Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-01T20:59:40.239Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6229eedd8553e7ab6730c46a",
                        "createdAt": "2022-07-01T20:49:48.485Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Do you often feel pressure to act more 'Masculine' when dealing with others men in leadership roles to gain their respect? I often find myself doing this without even noticing and I am not sure how to feel about it. I would appreciate any insight or advice!",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c421c594dcace72f5be4",
                    "name": "Steven J. Pietras",
                    "email": "spietras43@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-07-13T15:28:46.788Z",
                    "currentRole": "Manager",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-29T15:36:07.160Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-07-30T20:48:59.021Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 3
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee58553e7ab6730c4e7",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8a968bfdc0428e7da94",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee58553e7ab6730c4e7",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "Going remote",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-03T21:15:02.286Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8a968bfdc0428e7da92",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Attrition is a big concern of big business, in regards to the mandates around Covid and retaining top talent. What are some strategies that your organization is suggesting to tackle these concerns?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c423c594dcace72f5bfc",
                    "name": "Maurice L Coleman",
                    "email": "maurice.l.coleman@accenture.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-07-24T01:58:22.065Z",
                    "currentRole": "Product Manager"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-12-11T02:51:51.859Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "636f8fdc41830c7233cb2d9c",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "636f8ff241830c7233cb2e4e",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 1,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "636f8fec41830c7233cb2e40",
                        "answer": "okay",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6368acc678440371fa3f108b",
                            "currentRole": "Executive Vice President",
                            "email": "y1@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Y1",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-07T06:59:18.546Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T09:03:47.274Z"
                        },
                        "question": "636f8fdc41830c7233cb2d9c",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-12T12:22:10.273Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "636f908f41830c7233cb315b",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 1,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "636f8fec41830c7233cb2e40",
                        "answer": "hello",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6368acc678440371fa3f108b",
                            "currentRole": "Executive Vice President",
                            "email": "y1@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Y1",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-07T06:59:18.546Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T09:03:47.274Z"
                        },
                        "question": "636f8fdc41830c7233cb2d9c",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-12T12:24:47.122Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "636f909b41830c7233cb31c4",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 1,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "636f8fec41830c7233cb2e40",
                        "answer": "I want to ask a question ",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6368acc678440371fa3f108b",
                            "currentRole": "Executive Vice President",
                            "email": "y1@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Y1",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-07T06:59:18.546Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T09:03:47.274Z"
                        },
                        "question": "636f8fdc41830c7233cb2d9c",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-12T12:24:59.396Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637e0d0e94b8da45048ab74f",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637dba62a00c393d8f8b5205",
                        "answer": "hii",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "636f8fdc41830c7233cb2d9c",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-23T12:07:42.411Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "I'm a founder seeking funding. I am confused as to why I am receiving such different and conflicting feedback from investors? Has anyone else experienced this?\n",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "636a78788152c428092ed35a",
                    "currentRole": "Manager",
                    "email": "yo@yopmail.com",
                    "name": "Yo",
                    "createdAt": "2022-11-08T15:40:40.132Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:44:24.701Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-11-12T12:21:48.031Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 4
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eedf8553e7ab6730c483",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a85668bfdc0428e7cfc0",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedf8553e7ab6730c483",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f04c594dcace72f5c4e",
                            "name": "Iryna Chaban",
                            "email": "irynachaban98@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-09-07T19:20:12.002Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "You have to make sure that you are taking care of your mental health and focusing on yourself. Practicing self-compassion is a great start to managing imposter syndrome!",
                        "createdAt": "2021-10-07T14:03:30.671Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a85668bfdc0428e7cfbe",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "As a new leader of a large organization, how do you beat imposter syndrome?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-09-21T14:08:23.824Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeea8553e7ab6730c526",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8a568bfdc0428e7da04",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeea8553e7ab6730c526",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "It probably depends on your startup, but the baseline answer is: imminently important.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-03T15:51:50.459Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8a568bfdc0428e7da02",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8a968bfdc0428e7daa6",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeea8553e7ab6730c526",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c41dc594dcace72f5b9b",
                            "name": "Madeleine",
                            "email": "maddykindler11@yahoo.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-06-10T18:10:27.425Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "At least as a starting point, I would say it's pretty important. Knowing who specifically you want to market to at the start can definitely help more clearly shaping your ideas for your start up",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-03T21:35:36.695Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8a968bfdc0428e7daa4",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How important is to find a niche market for my start-up?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-01-29T00:58:29.890Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "63786fe7d8437d697e1ebaae",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "637b099ddf12177d2f4681b4",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637b0997df12177d2f46817c",
                        "answer": "test.....",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b6ecb7a3ce63a87b809a1",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer",
                            "email": "vijay74@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:11:39.718Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-25T08:54:15.709Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63786fe7d8437d697e1ebaae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-21T05:16:13.693Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637b0ba3df12177d2f468549",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 1,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637b0b95df12177d2f4684f5",
                        "answer": "test2",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6378c0db89e55b771e3f390a",
                            "currentRole": "Executive Vice President",
                            "email": "test77@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "test",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-19T11:41:15.769Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-21T05:24:22.071Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63786fe7d8437d697e1ebaae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-21T05:24:51.136Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637b0d58df12177d2f4688c9",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637b0d54df12177d2f46888f",
                        "answer": "test3...",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63786fe7d8437d697e1ebaae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-21T05:32:08.707Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "637b0deddf12177d2f4689f9",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637b0997df12177d2f46817c",
                        "answer": "t1..",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636b6ecb7a3ce63a87b809a1",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer",
                            "email": "vijay74@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-09T09:11:39.718Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-25T08:54:15.709Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63786fe7d8437d697e1ebaae",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-21T05:34:37.456Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "tytytyty",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6373a7eea5322d31357ff110",
                    "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer",
                    "email": "ym@yopmail.com",
                    "name": "Ym",
                    "createdAt": "2022-11-15T14:53:34.480Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:40.349Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-11-19T05:55:51.249Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 4
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeee8553e7ab6730c56a",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8bc68bfdc0428e7dd70",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeee8553e7ab6730c56a",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "A start-up is essentially a long series of redirections and model adjustments. It's very rare for an idea to crystalize exactly as it needs to manifest in the marketplace on its first conception. The bottom line when considering this question is: What am I trying to do? That will inform what your team should look like. And your team may have to look different than what it 'should' look like. But the goal is to keep moving forward while you figure out exactly what you need to do.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-03-01T16:04:44.123Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8bc68bfdc0428e7dd6e",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "What are the key components of a start-up? What should my team look like? How often should I be adjusting my model? Is there ever a time to stop/redirect a start-up?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3e6c594dcace72f58aa",
                    "name": "Amarachi Emezie",
                    "email": "amarachieemezie@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2022-01-12T18:41:13.277Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-05-09T15:13:09.331Z",
                    "currentRole": "Other"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-02-25T18:26:11.819Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeeb8553e7ab6730c53f",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8b268bfdc0428e7dc06",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeeb8553e7ab6730c53f",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "A lot of venture capitalist firms accept applications/partnerships on a rolling basis. So the main thing you need is a pitch that includes your product, the market you're trying to fill, your vision, and your plan for expansion (more often than not).",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-15T17:20:48.811Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8b268bfdc0428e7dc04",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8af68bfdc0428e7db88",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeeb8553e7ab6730c53f",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                            "name": "Saima Omar",
                            "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "You can start by creating a pitch deck and then sending it to a list of investors that are interested in your niche/sector/industry.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-13T16:46:08.288Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8af68bfdc0428e7db86",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How do I ask investors to help fund my startup?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3e8c594dcace72f58c9",
                    "name": "Nina Blackmon",
                    "email": "ninasblackmon@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2022-02-08T19:19:31.120Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-05-05T17:43:54.724Z",
                    "currentRole": "Other"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-02-12T02:30:48.670Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeee8553e7ab6730c56e",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8bd68bfdc0428e7dd8b",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeee8553e7ab6730c56e",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3e5c594dcace72f5893",
                            "name": "Firzana",
                            "email": "firzana218@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-12-29T20:45:55.686Z",
                            "currentRole": "Other"
                        },
                        "answer": "I think the first step you need to take is identifying the cause of this problem. You need to have an open discussion with your waitstaff on why there are sudden resignations. If some staff have complains about your GM, further ask them exactly why. Having effective communication between frontline workers and upper management is essential especially if you are currently seeing a fast turnover rate. You need to act quickly.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-03-01T21:54:35.099Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8bd68bfdc0428e7dd89",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8bd68bfdc0428e7dd92",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeee8553e7ab6730c56e",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "Thank you for this! We're torn right now between our profits and our employees, but it seems that if we don't address our employees, our profits may soon take a hit.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-03-02T19:33:26.455Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8bd68bfdc0428e7dd89",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "I'm a director of a regional restaurant group. We have recently promoted a GM to our highest profit restaurant. She's had great success at smaller restaurants although we've had scattered staff complaints about her manner. Now we are seeing really quick turnover among our waitstaff. This is unprecedented for us and I'm struggling with how to approach this problem.",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                    "name": "Daniel Daws",
                    "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                    "currentRole": "Founder"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-03-01T16:00:14.180Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeda8553e7ab6730c444",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6243a0461d94997cc0a0fb54",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6243a0121d94997cc0a0fb3a",
                        "answer": "There was a study years ago that physically taking a step back inspired novel approaches to problem solving. Weird, but I have found it works for me.",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62439eb01d94997cc0a0fa17",
                            "currentRole": "Founder",
                            "email": "ldwight@galacticsmarties.com",
                            "name": "Lili Dwight",
                            "createdAt": "2022-03-30T00:05:04.292Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-03-30T00:05:04.292Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6229eeda8553e7ab6730c444",
                        "createdAt": "2022-03-30T00:11:50.151Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "What strategies have helped you move out of a thinking rut?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3ecc594dcace72f58f8",
                    "name": "MollyDriscoll",
                    "email": "mdriscoll2@luc.edu",
                    "createdAt": "2020-10-07T01:12:14.277Z",
                    "currentRole": "CEO"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-05-05T19:35:27.818Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "63654739f4f4e45f9d950337",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "63654841f4f4e45f9d950abe",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6365482df4f4e45f9d950aa4",
                        "answer": "it helps to increase online visibility ",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "63653d02f4f4e45f9d94ebdd",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Director",
                            "email": "doe@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "DOE",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-04T16:25:38.281Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-04T16:51:18.908Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63654739f4f4e45f9d950337",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-04T17:13:37.479Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63654b08f4f4e45f9d9514db",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63654aa4f4f4e45f9d95125b",
                        "answer": "v",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63654739f4f4e45f9d950337",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-04T17:25:28.788Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63654b08f4f4e45f9d9514de",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63654aa4f4f4e45f9d95125b",
                        "answer": "b",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63654739f4f4e45f9d950337",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-04T17:25:28.867Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63654b09f4f4e45f9d9514e6",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63654aa4f4f4e45f9d95125b",
                        "answer": "v",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63654739f4f4e45f9d950337",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-04T17:25:29.035Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63654b09f4f4e45f9d9514ea",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63654aa4f4f4e45f9d95125b",
                        "answer": "b",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63654739f4f4e45f9d950337",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-04T17:25:29.096Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63654b09f4f4e45f9d9514f3",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63654aa4f4f4e45f9d95125b",
                        "answer": "v",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63654739f4f4e45f9d950337",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-04T17:25:29.349Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63654b09f4f4e45f9d9514fd",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63654aa4f4f4e45f9d95125b",
                        "answer": "b",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63654739f4f4e45f9d950337",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-04T17:25:29.577Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63654b09f4f4e45f9d9514ff",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63654aa4f4f4e45f9d95125b",
                        "answer": "b",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63654739f4f4e45f9d950337",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-04T17:25:29.579Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63654b0af4f4e45f9d951525",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63654aa4f4f4e45f9d95125b",
                        "answer": "v",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63654739f4f4e45f9d950337",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-04T17:25:30.360Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63654b0af4f4e45f9d951557",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63654aa4f4f4e45f9d95125b",
                        "answer": "d",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63654739f4f4e45f9d950337",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-04T17:25:30.842Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63654b0bf4f4e45f9d951575",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63654aa4f4f4e45f9d95125b",
                        "answer": "f",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63654739f4f4e45f9d950337",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-04T17:25:31.077Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63654b0bf4f4e45f9d9515b4",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63654aa4f4f4e45f9d95125b",
                        "answer": "g",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63654739f4f4e45f9d950337",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-04T17:25:31.710Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63654b0df4f4e45f9d951607",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63654aa4f4f4e45f9d95125b",
                        "answer": "f",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63654739f4f4e45f9d950337",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-04T17:25:33.505Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63654b0ff4f4e45f9d95164c",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63654aa4f4f4e45f9d95125b",
                        "answer": "f",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63654739f4f4e45f9d950337",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-04T17:25:35.522Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63654b0ff4f4e45f9d95164f",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63654aa4f4f4e45f9d95125b",
                        "answer": "g",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63654739f4f4e45f9d950337",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-04T17:25:35.533Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63654b12f4f4e45f9d9516a7",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63654aa4f4f4e45f9d95125b",
                        "answer": "d",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63654739f4f4e45f9d950337",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-04T17:25:38.055Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63654b12f4f4e45f9d9516a9",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63654aa4f4f4e45f9d95125b",
                        "answer": "k",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63654739f4f4e45f9d950337",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-04T17:25:38.063Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63654b12f4f4e45f9d9516b2",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63654aa4f4f4e45f9d95125b",
                        "answer": "j",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63654739f4f4e45f9d950337",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-04T17:25:38.500Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63654b12f4f4e45f9d9516b8",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63654aa4f4f4e45f9d95125b",
                        "answer": "n",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63654739f4f4e45f9d950337",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-04T17:25:38.683Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63654b12f4f4e45f9d9516be",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63654aa4f4f4e45f9d95125b",
                        "answer": "g",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63654739f4f4e45f9d950337",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-04T17:25:38.716Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63654b12f4f4e45f9d9516c1",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63654aa4f4f4e45f9d95125b",
                        "answer": "f",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63654739f4f4e45f9d950337",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-04T17:25:38.721Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63654b12f4f4e45f9d9516c3",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63654aa4f4f4e45f9d95125b",
                        "answer": "k",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63654739f4f4e45f9d950337",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-04T17:25:38.872Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63654b13f4f4e45f9d9516cb",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63654aa4f4f4e45f9d95125b",
                        "answer": "j",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63654739f4f4e45f9d950337",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-04T17:25:39.062Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63654b13f4f4e45f9d9516cd",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63654aa4f4f4e45f9d95125b",
                        "answer": "n",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63654739f4f4e45f9d950337",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-04T17:25:39.070Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63654b13f4f4e45f9d9516cf",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63654aa4f4f4e45f9d95125b",
                        "answer": "f",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63654739f4f4e45f9d950337",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-04T17:25:39.089Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63654b13f4f4e45f9d9516d3",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63654aa4f4f4e45f9d95125b",
                        "answer": "g",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63654739f4f4e45f9d950337",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-04T17:25:39.102Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63654b13f4f4e45f9d9516d5",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63654aa4f4f4e45f9d95125b",
                        "answer": "k",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63654739f4f4e45f9d950337",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-04T17:25:39.106Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63654b13f4f4e45f9d9516d8",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63654aa4f4f4e45f9d95125b",
                        "answer": "j",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63654739f4f4e45f9d950337",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-04T17:25:39.252Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63654b13f4f4e45f9d9516db",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63654aa4f4f4e45f9d95125b",
                        "answer": "d",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63654739f4f4e45f9d950337",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-04T17:25:39.260Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63654b13f4f4e45f9d9516dd",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63654aa4f4f4e45f9d95125b",
                        "answer": "n",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63654739f4f4e45f9d950337",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-04T17:25:39.261Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63654b13f4f4e45f9d9516e4",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63654aa4f4f4e45f9d95125b",
                        "answer": "f",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63654739f4f4e45f9d950337",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-04T17:25:39.462Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63654b13f4f4e45f9d9516e9",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63654aa4f4f4e45f9d95125b",
                        "answer": "k",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63654739f4f4e45f9d950337",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-04T17:25:39.482Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63654b13f4f4e45f9d9516f6",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63654aa4f4f4e45f9d95125b",
                        "answer": "j",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63654739f4f4e45f9d950337",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-04T17:25:39.871Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63654b13f4f4e45f9d9516f9",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63654aa4f4f4e45f9d95125b",
                        "answer": "k",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63654739f4f4e45f9d950337",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-04T17:25:39.883Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63654b14f4f4e45f9d95170b",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63654aa4f4f4e45f9d95125b",
                        "answer": "j",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63654739f4f4e45f9d950337",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-04T17:25:40.452Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "What are the benefits of online marketing?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "63654326f4f4e45f9d94f82e",
                    "currentRole": "Partner",
                    "email": "doe2@yopmail.com",
                    "name": "Doe",
                    "createdAt": "2022-11-04T16:51:50.156Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-11-04T16:51:50.157Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-11-04T17:09:13.539Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 35
            },
            {
                "_id": "62b8ddf5f6ac59655ddd9f1b",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "62b8e2d3f6ac59655ddda471",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "62b8e2c0f6ac59655ddda453",
                        "answer": "most likely, since inflation can't be curbed",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6289bcdfd0a01e70a277eef1",
                            "currentRole": "Manager",
                            "email": "z.wang12@icloud.com",
                            "name": "Christy Wang",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-22T04:32:31.532Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-26T22:50:00.514Z"
                        },
                        "question": "62b8ddf5f6ac59655ddd9f1b",
                        "createdAt": "2022-06-26T22:50:59.441Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "62b9b494f6ac59655dddba10",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "62b9b456f6ac59655dddb9f3",
                        "answer": "Depending on where you draw the line for a crisis, it might be said that it has come already and how intensely it persists is yet to be seen.",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "question": "62b8ddf5f6ac59655ddd9f1b",
                        "createdAt": "2022-06-27T13:45:56.961Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "62b9c897f6ac59655dddc05c",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "62b9c82df6ac59655dddc03e",
                        "answer": "I am not sure but here is a great site to read more about this https://www.forbes.com/advisor/investing/is-a-recession-coming/",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62b9c632f6ac59655dddbd5c",
                            "currentRole": "Co-Founder",
                            "email": "criojasp@nd.edu",
                            "name": "Cristina Riojas",
                            "createdAt": "2022-06-27T15:01:06.793Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-01T14:41:37.907Z"
                        },
                        "question": "62b8ddf5f6ac59655ddd9f1b",
                        "createdAt": "2022-06-27T15:11:19.714Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "62c2e02af6ac59655ddf83ac",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "62c2dfe2f6ac59655ddf8237",
                        "answer": "do you think a financial crisis is coming?",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "628dc2f3942ead2b0d93e54e",
                            "currentRole": "Director",
                            "email": "jatulkumar02@gmail.com",
                            "name": "Jatul kumar",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-25T05:47:31.454Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-04T12:04:31.549Z"
                        },
                        "question": "62b8ddf5f6ac59655ddd9f1b",
                        "createdAt": "2022-07-04T12:42:18.546Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "do you think a financial crisis is coming?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "626591fb6b39681abb55d829",
                    "currentRole": "Product Manager",
                    "email": "christyz@stanford.edu",
                    "name": "Christy Wang",
                    "createdAt": "2022-04-24T18:07:55.617Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-05-09T05:35:10.337Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-06-26T22:30:13.400Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 4
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeec8553e7ab6730c540",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8b268bfdc0428e7dbfd",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeec8553e7ab6730c540",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "You first need to decide on what social metrics you want to use. This is a good question, but the caveat is that you have to decide for yourself. What do you want to measure: access to food, affordable healthcare, transportation, political awareness, environmental safety...etc. Do you see what I mean?",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-15T17:02:44.319Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8b268bfdc0428e7dbfb",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8b668bfdc0428e7dc85",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeec8553e7ab6730c540",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3e5c594dcace72f5893",
                            "name": "Firzana",
                            "email": "firzana218@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-12-29T20:45:55.686Z",
                            "currentRole": "Other"
                        },
                        "answer": "I agree, I think using a survey is a great objectifiable way to measure social impact and customer satisfaction! You can also measure the social impact of your startup by evaluating whether the production/processes of your product are more ethically sourced and produced in comparison to your competitors.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-19T19:31:37.943Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8b668bfdc0428e7dc83",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8b368bfdc0428e7dc36",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeec8553e7ab6730c540",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c41dc594dcace72f5b9b",
                            "name": "Madeleine",
                            "email": "maddykindler11@yahoo.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-06-10T18:10:27.425Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "great question! I think a good measure is to try and determine how many lives your have directly impacted (hopefully in a mostly positive way). what data helps to determine this is a little more subjective. satisfaction surverys regarding your product, for example, are a great starting point.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-15T21:02:04.348Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8b368bfdc0428e7dc34",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How do you measure your social impact?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3e8c594dcace72f58c9",
                    "name": "Nina Blackmon",
                    "email": "ninasblackmon@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2022-02-08T19:19:31.120Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-05-05T17:43:54.724Z",
                    "currentRole": "Other"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-02-12T02:34:12.126Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 3
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eedc8553e7ab6730c464",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84868bfdc0428e7cd91",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedc8553e7ab6730c464",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                            "name": "Saima Omar",
                            "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Very interesting perspective, thank you for taking the time to answer my question!",
                        "createdAt": "2021-07-20T23:59:26.881Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84668bfdc0428e7cd61",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84668bfdc0428e7cd63",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedc8553e7ab6730c464",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c407c594dcace72f5a43",
                            "name": "Mike Harshfield",
                            "email": "mikeharshfield@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-13T20:54:29.255Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "I think that totally depends on what you are trying to accomplish long term - be known to many or do a fanatstic job and be known to the few that matter. I peresonally don't spend a lot of time on this as a smaller, more focused network of people is what I desire",
                        "createdAt": "2021-07-18T17:48:40.221Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84668bfdc0428e7cd61",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "As a Leader, do you think creating a personal brand on social media is important? (why?) Do you take time to create thought leadership content and be recognised as a Leader in your industry? What are the benefits of doing this?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-07-17T20:31:11.460Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee58553e7ab6730c4df",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a87e68bfdc0428e7d54f",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee58553e7ab6730c4df",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c417c594dcace72f5b45",
                            "name": "Scott Kuperman",
                            "email": "scott.kuperman@paintplatoon.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-05-04T18:23:00.565Z",
                            "currentRole": "President",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T16:24:41.811Z"
                        },
                        "answer": "I guess that's what they mean when they say it's lonely at the top. ",
                        "createdAt": "2021-12-07T03:56:49.286Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a87e68bfdc0428e7d54d",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a87f68bfdc0428e7d590",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee58553e7ab6730c4df",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "Yes, this is a hard feeling. You might try connecting with other leaders at your level or in tangential branches.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-12-09T02:19:56.406Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a87f68bfdc0428e7d58e",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a88268bfdc0428e7d5d6",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee58553e7ab6730c4df",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c423c594dcace72f5bfc",
                            "name": "Maurice L Coleman",
                            "email": "maurice.l.coleman@accenture.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-07-24T01:58:22.065Z",
                            "currentRole": "Product Manager"
                        },
                        "answer": "Hello, Team building excercises are a great way to connect with your team. IE Cadence Virtual Happy Hours, Name that tune,Etc. I have found it very usful to connect on a human level, to demonstrate you are human and just like them.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-12-10T21:41:21.041Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a88268bfdc0428e7d5d4",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Has anyone ever felt a sense of isolation after spending too much time leading a project? I talk to my team daily, but never seem to connect. I've been working all the time so most of my interactions in a week are with people who simply want a question answered, a problem solved, or direction given.",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "62218f00c594dcace72f5c24",
                    "name": "Steven Pietras",
                    "email": "norgoth12@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-08-07T15:35:10.381Z",
                    "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-12-06T16:29:56.789Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 3
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee18553e7ab6730c4aa",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a85c68bfdc0428e7d0a8",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee18553e7ab6730c4aa",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f08c594dcace72f5c8d",
                            "name": "cahora",
                            "email": "cahora7821@bomoads.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-27T09:04:53.338Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "cftdtydtyfyuguyhvfgngfjngfjnfftgfgymfy",
                        "createdAt": "2021-10-27T10:27:30.238Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a85c68bfdc0428e7d0a6",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a85c68bfdc0428e7d0b1",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee18553e7ab6730c4aa",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f08c594dcace72f5c8d",
                            "name": "cahora",
                            "email": "cahora7821@bomoads.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-27T09:04:53.338Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "cftdtydtyfyuguyhvbhjbjhbjhb",
                        "createdAt": "2021-10-27T10:27:47.151Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a85c68bfdc0428e7d0af",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a86768bfdc0428e7d20d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee18553e7ab6730c4aa",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "You may like to see if staggering their work schedules can help accommodate whatever life needs are getting in their way of consistent performance. However, if this person can't communicate with you about what they need, then stricter enforcement may be necessary.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-11-02T14:26:45.577Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a86768bfdc0428e7d20b",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How do I manage employees who are late on their deliverables and take too many breaks a day and are on their personal phone too much?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-10-26T02:49:28.242Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 3
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eedd8553e7ab6730c470",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84c68bfdc0428e7ce4a",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eedd8553e7ab6730c470",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c422c594dcace72f5bf7",
                            "name": "Isabel Fabre",
                            "email": "ifabre@yahoo.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-07-22T18:36:03.950Z",
                            "currentRole": "Manager"
                        },
                        "answer": "I would like for this employee to share his/her knowledge. When I have been in this situation, I have asked the employee to create some guides that would help others gaing the knowledge he/she has. It would also be good to have them transfer knowledge directly to others.  Have him/her give a presentation of things they are most knowledgeable about.  Have them pinpoint gaps in the group and give you ideas. You'll be surprised how much valuable information you can get from them.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-08-24T19:17:26.506Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84c68bfdc0428e7ce48",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "If a highly valued, experienced employee on your team gave notice (let's say, two weeks notice)--how would you like to see that  person spend their time? Let's assume her most important work tasks were just about finished or could be handed off. And let's assume she wasn't planning to use unused vacation days.",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "62218f02c594dcace72f5c30",
                    "name": "Audrey E Bloom",
                    "email": "audrey@dulyknowted.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-08-11T17:38:29.484Z",
                    "currentRole": "Founder"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-08-24T00:30:55.226Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee68553e7ab6730c4f2",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8a668bfdc0428e7da31",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee68553e7ab6730c4f2",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "You may want to create seasonal part-time or contract positions",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-03T16:40:36.755Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8a668bfdc0428e7da2f",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Employees don't want to work on certain holidays, but the business needs to be open on those days. How can I staff if they aren't accepting the holiday differential we are offering?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c421c594dcace72f5be4",
                    "name": "Steven J. Pietras",
                    "email": "spietras43@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-07-13T15:28:46.788Z",
                    "currentRole": "Manager",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-29T15:36:07.160Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-12-20T19:33:35.916Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeec8553e7ab6730c541",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8b268bfdc0428e7dc0f",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeec8553e7ab6730c541",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "It depends on what stage you're at, but generally, you'll want someone who can help you market, someone who can help you budget (if that's not you).",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-15T17:21:59.440Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8b268bfdc0428e7dc0d",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How do I build a founding team for my start-up in tech?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-02-13T16:42:40.025Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee78553e7ab6730c504",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a89b68bfdc0428e7d88c",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee78553e7ab6730c504",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "If your product and service is clear and fully developed and the value is digestibly communicated, you are probably ready. The pros are more obvious: you have access to funds, and potentially insights from people who want to see an ROI, so in addition to the money you have some tier of collaborators. Additionally, the morale that investors can add shouldn't be overlooked. However, you may find yourself beholden to some of them and your freedom to pivot may be reigned in.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-13T16:27:46.553Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a89b68bfdc0428e7d88a",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How do I know that my start-up is ready for its first round of funding? What are some of the pros and cons for raising funds from investors?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-01-07T14:11:13.966Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee68553e7ab6730c4eb",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8a868bfdc0428e7da8b",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee68553e7ab6730c4eb",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "What?",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-03T21:14:40.189Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8a868bfdc0428e7da89",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How to develop a project feasibility of a new business",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c41ac594dcace72f5b76",
                    "name": "shahma zahid",
                    "email": "shahmazahid@yahoo.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-05-17T18:17:17.955Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-12-18T04:35:03.384Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee98553e7ab6730c519",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8a068bfdc0428e7d952",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee98553e7ab6730c519",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "Usually, a board does not need to be kept abreast of unless it concerns their Chief Officers. Then it would be highly unlikely that you wouldn't consult them...However, it's also rare for you to hire someone. It is within your authority, but normally outside of your range of priorities.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-22T00:18:28.871Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8a068bfdc0428e7d950",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Do I have to run all major decisions across the board? Such as hiring a new member of staff? Or hiring external support? Can I make an executive decision as the Founder and CEO?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-01-17T16:42:34.512Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee58553e7ab6730c4de",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a87f68bfdc0428e7d587",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee58553e7ab6730c4de",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "This really depends on the nature of the disagreement. If it does not affect the team at large outside of whatever frictions are arising, it is likely that they don't need to be involved in a formal meeting and whatever resolution is reached will likely be dispersed through gossip.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-12-07T22:26:36.468Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a87f68bfdc0428e7d585",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a87e68bfdc0428e7d558",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee58553e7ab6730c4de",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c417c594dcace72f5b45",
                            "name": "Scott Kuperman",
                            "email": "scott.kuperman@paintplatoon.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-05-04T18:23:00.565Z",
                            "currentRole": "President",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T16:24:41.811Z"
                        },
                        "answer": "Keep it private for now. Don't bring in a team. Tell them that you are aware that \"we all  need to work through this matter\". But before you get started, first tell them a joke. Continue explaining about blah....blah....blah. Then put the meeting off to another day.  Before the 2nd meeting arrives, fire the one that didn't laugh at your joke. That's the troublemaker. ",
                        "createdAt": "2021-12-07T04:13:09.910Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a87e68bfdc0428e7d556",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a88268bfdc0428e7d5df",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee58553e7ab6730c4de",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c423c594dcace72f5bfc",
                            "name": "Maurice L Coleman",
                            "email": "maurice.l.coleman@accenture.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-07-24T01:58:22.065Z",
                            "currentRole": "Product Manager"
                        },
                        "answer": "Identify and understand each persons point of disagreement separately, problem solve with a counterpart that is neutral and  identify the best course of action to create a conducive enviroment where you can perform conflict resolution activities (set the rules of respect). At the conclusion, ensure that you conclude the activities with mutual positivity and respect. Once this is fostered, schuedule a cadence of team building excercises with the group that strengthens the groups stability, respect and positivity.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-12-10T21:57:11.734Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a88268bfdc0428e7d5dd",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "There have been issues at my office handling disagreement between two employees. Neither will address the problem and it is starting to effect team morale. Would it be a good idea to sit them both down and air their grievances in private, or should this be a larger discussion as a team?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "62218f00c594dcace72f5c24",
                    "name": "Steven Pietras",
                    "email": "norgoth12@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-08-07T15:35:10.381Z",
                    "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-12-03T14:35:01.547Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 3
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeeb8553e7ab6730c53a",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8b768bfdc0428e7dcb2",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeeb8553e7ab6730c53a",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3e8c594dcace72f58c9",
                            "name": "Nina Blackmon",
                            "email": "ninasblackmon@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2022-02-08T19:19:31.120Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-05-05T17:43:54.724Z",
                            "currentRole": "Other"
                        },
                        "answer": "You can start by creating a target list of VC firms that are a good fit for your company and/or that invest in companies like yours/the kind of deal you’re offering. Check out the firm's past deals, and make sure they invest in the stage of funding you seek. Also include/consider location.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-22T00:04:34.682Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8b768bfdc0428e7dcb0",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How do I choose the right venture capital firm to work with? I'm worried that some might be predatory, or offer more than they can or will deliver.",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                    "name": "Daniel Daws",
                    "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                    "currentRole": "Founder"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-02-09T18:39:05.871Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "63844db1df651d77c17f80a9",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "63845207dd20fd17320f71cf",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6373a7eea5322d31357ff110"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63844de6df651d77c17f81a9",
                        "answer": "hiii",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63844db1df651d77c17f80a9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T06:15:35.569Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63845273dd20fd17320f723c",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6373a7eea5322d31357ff110"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63844de6df651d77c17f81a9",
                        "answer": "HEllo",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63844db1df651d77c17f80a9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T06:17:23.521Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63845377dd20fd17320f732a",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6373a7eea5322d31357ff110"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63844de6df651d77c17f81a9",
                        "answer": "heee",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63844db1df651d77c17f80a9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T06:21:43.605Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6384540add20fd17320f737b",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6373a7eea5322d31357ff110"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63844de6df651d77c17f81a9",
                        "answer": "RRRRRRRR",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63844db1df651d77c17f80a9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T06:24:10.495Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63845524dd20fd17320f73cc",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6373a7eea5322d31357ff110"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63844de6df651d77c17f81a9",
                        "answer": "rtrt",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63844db1df651d77c17f80a9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T06:28:52.955Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638455dbdd20fd17320f74a3",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6373a7eea5322d31357ff110"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63844de6df651d77c17f81a9",
                        "answer": "Hiiii",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63844db1df651d77c17f80a9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T06:31:55.836Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638455f3dd20fd17320f750c",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6373a7eea5322d31357ff110"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63844de6df651d77c17f81a9",
                        "answer": "hjhj\n",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63844db1df651d77c17f80a9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T06:32:19.404Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63845626dd20fd17320f755c",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6373a7eea5322d31357ff110"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63844de6df651d77c17f81a9",
                        "answer": "GGG",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63844db1df651d77c17f80a9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T06:33:10.894Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6384569cdd20fd17320f764b",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6373a7eea5322d31357ff110"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63844de6df651d77c17f81a9",
                        "answer": "AAA",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63844db1df651d77c17f80a9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T06:35:08.960Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638456dfdd20fd17320f769c",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6373a7eea5322d31357ff110"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63844de6df651d77c17f81a9",
                        "answer": "fvfgv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63844db1df651d77c17f80a9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T06:36:15.412Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6384575cdd20fd17320f76ec",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6373a7eea5322d31357ff110"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63844de6df651d77c17f81a9",
                        "answer": "hh",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63844db1df651d77c17f80a9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T06:38:20.218Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638457aadd20fd17320f77f2",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6373a7eea5322d31357ff110"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63844de6df651d77c17f81a9",
                        "answer": "hh",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63844db1df651d77c17f80a9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T06:39:38.773Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638457b5dd20fd17320f7842",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6373a7eea5322d31357ff110"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63844de6df651d77c17f81a9",
                        "answer": "ytt",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63844db1df651d77c17f80a9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T06:39:49.905Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "638457d9dd20fd17320f78aa",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6373a7eea5322d31357ff110"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63844de6df651d77c17f81a9",
                        "answer": "vvv",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6295d4235334af3e0848a064",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "vijay085.rejoice@gmail.com",
                            "name": "vijay",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-31T08:38:59.593Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:28.341Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63844db1df651d77c17f80a9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T06:40:25.250Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "testtt",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6373a7eea5322d31357ff110",
                    "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer",
                    "email": "ym@yopmail.com",
                    "name": "Ym",
                    "createdAt": "2022-11-15T14:53:34.480Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:40.349Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:57:05.043Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 14
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eef28553e7ab6730c5b1",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a81468bfdc0428e7c648",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef28553e7ab6730c5b1",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3f9c594dcace72f5961",
                            "name": "John Cruz",
                            "email": "johncruzrn@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2020-12-18T23:38:21.151Z",
                            "currentRole": "Manager"
                        },
                        "answer": "By establishing from the get go that quality, safety, and timely delivery of care are paramount. With that in mind, expenses and projects are classified under tiers of importance and maximum impact for quality and safety.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-02-12T01:03:09.523Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a81468bfdc0428e7c646",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How have you managed the tension between financial pressure, service delivery demands, the patient experience/quality and safety?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3ecc594dcace72f58f8",
                    "name": "MollyDriscoll",
                    "email": "mdriscoll2@luc.edu",
                    "createdAt": "2020-10-07T01:12:14.277Z",
                    "currentRole": "CEO"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-02-11T15:14:47.210Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee98553e7ab6730c524",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8a268bfdc0428e7d98a",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee98553e7ab6730c524",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "What kind of team do you have?",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-26T15:24:56.277Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8a268bfdc0428e7d988",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How do you incentivise your team? Do you participate in any incentive programmes?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-01-26T15:15:24.314Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eef38553e7ab6730c5c8",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a81c68bfdc0428e7c753",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef38553e7ab6730c5c8",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c40ac594dcace72f5a6c",
                            "name": "Idris Abiodun Tayo Olufowobi",
                            "email": "idris.olufowobi@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-20T00:23:17.898Z",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Cost of implementation and negative attitude of employee towards the new age technology",
                        "createdAt": "2021-03-21T21:50:05.646Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a81c68bfdc0428e7c751",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a82268bfdc0428e7c838",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef38553e7ab6730c5c8",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c409c594dcace72f5a66",
                            "name": "Tejveer Singh",
                            "email": "tejveer_s@yahoo.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-19T02:12:43.203Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Thanks! Appreciate your response. So what do you suggest as an approach to get the organization aligned with the thought of Technology Adoption.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-04-01T06:02:34.151Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a81c68bfdc0428e7c751",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84668bfdc0428e7cd44",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef38553e7ab6730c5c8",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c420c594dcace72f5bce",
                            "name": "Jan Zucker",
                            "email": "jan.z@digitalcc.us",
                            "createdAt": "2021-07-01T13:43:59.062Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "Be Flexible and surround yourself with smart people who know what you don't.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-07-14T18:42:40.184Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84668bfdc0428e7cd42",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a81c68bfdc0428e7c75c",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef38553e7ab6730c5c8",
                        "answer": "Hi",
                        "createdAt": "2021-03-22T08:45:18.514Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a81c68bfdc0428e7c75a",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84268bfdc0428e7cc9d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef38553e7ab6730c5c8",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3f5c594dcace72f5919",
                            "name": "J. Mandell Carter",
                            "email": "j.m.carter2021@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2020-11-23T17:57:09.494Z",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer"
                        },
                        "answer": "I have found that one of the biggest and long lasting challenges is overcoming \"that's always how we have done it\" which may be another way of actually saying \"we're afraid to try something new\". When team members feel they have the support of leadership; that mistakes will not result in undue reprimands, the team is more willing to more forward with something new. Another challange may be finding the right API to ensure a smooth integration between the legacy system and the new. The last challeng I'll mention is cost. Even though the new tech may be needed, without the green light from the C-Suite and/or Board, progress will be slow if at all. There needs to be a practicle real-life understanding and connection established to help those making the decisions fully appreciate just what the new tech will do both in the short-term and long-run.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-06-25T18:14:17.042Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84168bfdc0428e7cc9b",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "628b806cfeaf4c30f888a5df",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "628b8050feaf4c30f888a5bb",
                        "answer": "assssssssssssssssssss",
                        "question": "6229eef38553e7ab6730c5c8",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-23T12:39:08.306Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "What are the challenges faced by business leaders in adopting to new age Technology?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c409c594dcace72f5a66",
                    "name": "Tejveer Singh",
                    "email": "tejveer_s@yahoo.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-19T02:12:43.203Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-03-19T02:49:06.457Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 6
            },
            {
                "_id": "6290c6f05de93c50a045f9d7",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6295edec5ab7d43ebe61a6f1",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295ede65ab7d43ebe61a6bd",
                        "answer": "this is not good",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "628e0f5c942ead2b0d942d26",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "xacivel676@lockaya.com",
                            "name": "xacivel",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-25T11:13:32.977Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-28T09:16:59.974Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6290c6f05de93c50a045f9d7",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T10:29:00.780Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6295ee8f5ab7d43ebe61a7e8",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6295ede65ab7d43ebe61a6bd",
                        "answer": "hello",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "628e0f5c942ead2b0d942d26",
                            "currentRole": "Assistant Vice President",
                            "email": "xacivel676@lockaya.com",
                            "name": "xacivel",
                            "createdAt": "2022-05-25T11:13:32.977Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-28T09:16:59.974Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6290c6f05de93c50a045f9d7",
                        "createdAt": "2022-05-31T10:31:43.086Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "we are want to hack nasa how it will possible?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "624d5ba9d500ad509757879c",
                    "currentRole": "Chief Operating Officer",
                    "email": "tehav55741@nuesond.com",
                    "name": "Tehav",
                    "createdAt": "2022-04-06T09:21:45.077Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-10-10T04:11:45.916Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-05-27T12:41:20.663Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeee8553e7ab6730c568",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8bc68bfdc0428e7dd5e",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeee8553e7ab6730c568",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                            "name": "Saima Omar",
                            "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "If you want to be investible, you need to know your numbers and they need to look good! Why should an investor part with their money? It's going to be a risk but you need to show them your numbers look good. You have potential. That you have a growth plan. And their money will make money in the future without them having to do much.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-03-01T01:17:25.864Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8bc68bfdc0428e7dd5c",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8bd68bfdc0428e7dd79",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeee8553e7ab6730c568",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "They look for a market niche, something they personally see value in, and viable plans to expand your product or grow awareness and thereby increase profit so that they feel confident there will be a high ROI",
                        "createdAt": "2022-03-01T16:05:52.104Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8bd68bfdc0428e7dd77",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "What qualities do investors look for when deciding whether to invest in your business?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3e6c594dcace72f58aa",
                    "name": "Amarachi Emezie",
                    "email": "amarachieemezie@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2022-01-12T18:41:13.277Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-05-09T15:13:09.331Z",
                    "currentRole": "Other"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-02-25T18:22:45.613Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "63805ad98760ee61cb82b909",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "63805b4e8760ee61cb82bab9",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "63805b4a8760ee61cb82ba72",
                        "answer": "Hello",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "637f791b231ce456a1a40bf3",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Financial Officer",
                            "email": "baju@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Baju",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-24T14:00:59.327Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:56:41.026Z"
                        },
                        "question": "63805ad98760ee61cb82b909",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-25T06:06:06.016Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "Yaro teat",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "63805a078760ee61cb82b662",
                    "currentRole": "Executive Vice President",
                    "email": "fal@yopmail.com",
                    "name": "Fal",
                    "createdAt": "2022-11-25T06:00:39.573Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T08:50:17.677Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-11-25T06:04:09.900Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee78553e7ab6730c4fa",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8a668bfdc0428e7da3a",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee78553e7ab6730c4fa",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "What would you like to talk about?",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-03T16:42:17.034Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8a668bfdc0428e7da38",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "I am interested in speaking with someone who knows about data center site selection",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3e5c594dcace72f5890",
                    "name": "Hugh Taylor",
                    "email": "hugh@hughtaylor.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-12-28T09:42:29.035Z",
                    "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-12-28T09:45:45.588Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eede8553e7ab6730c478",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "62bf6293f6ac59655ddf36cf",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 1,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "62bf61f2f6ac59655ddf36c1",
                        "answer": "I definitely think encouraging your employees to give you feedback is a great way to build trust and psychological safety! I would be careful about putting any contingencies on the feedback you are asking they give you though, because this could damage the ability to build respect",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62bf5a68f6ac59655ddf308c",
                            "currentRole": "Other",
                            "email": "mschaefer14@outlook.com",
                            "name": "Madison Schaefer",
                            "createdAt": "2022-07-01T20:34:48.547Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-01T20:59:40.239Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6229eede8553e7ab6730c478",
                        "createdAt": "2022-07-01T21:09:39.325Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "I want to encourage my employees to give me more feedback without undermining my authority. I feel like this should increase their respect for me rather than harm it. Thoughts?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3ecc594dcace72f58f5",
                    "name": "Claire Beltmann",
                    "email": "cbeltmann@luc.edu",
                    "createdAt": "2020-10-20T20:34:37.140Z",
                    "currentRole": "Assistant Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-09-10T17:01:58.086Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee88553e7ab6730c507",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a89768bfdc0428e7d7e1",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee88553e7ab6730c507",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c3ecc594dcace72f58f8",
                            "name": "MollyDriscoll",
                            "email": "mdriscoll2@luc.edu",
                            "createdAt": "2020-10-07T01:12:14.277Z",
                            "currentRole": "CEO"
                        },
                        "answer": "I would think getting them to talk to each other could help. You could mediate a conversation to come up with a solution that benefits everybody.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-09T18:21:56.629Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a89768bfdc0428e7d7df",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a89a68bfdc0428e7d84d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee88553e7ab6730c507",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "It sounds like you may be tapping into the wrong market. If you're confident your marketing material is on point and accurately reflects your service or product, you may want to do additional research on who you should be targeting if your sales force (provided they're properly trained) is having trouble closing.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-13T00:42:29.998Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a89968bfdc0428e7d84b",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a89c68bfdc0428e7d8a1",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee88553e7ab6730c507",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                            "name": "Saima Omar",
                            "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Thanks",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-13T18:32:02.450Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a89968bfdc0428e7d84b",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "I am a B2B company CEO. I have noticed conflict between the sales team and marketing team. Marketing is responsible for generating leads, the sales team are responsible for closing them. The sales team complains about poor leads and your marketing team complains about low close rates. How best can I resolve this conflict?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-01-07T14:17:30.532Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 3
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeed8553e7ab6730c55c",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8b768bfdc0428e7dccd",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeed8553e7ab6730c55c",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                            "name": "Saima Omar",
                            "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "You must consider who your audience is first. Then figure out where they like to hang out. Then you put your marketing messages in the places they hang out. For example, my business' audience might be women, aged 40+ with incomes of over £100k per year to purchase a luxury item. I would place an advert in somewhere like Conde Nast Magazine or places/items where I know the audience likes to engage or read.",
                        "createdAt": "2022-02-22T14:22:42.282Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8b768bfdc0428e7dccb",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How can one expand their business’ audience?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3e6c594dcace72f58aa",
                    "name": "Amarachi Emezie",
                    "email": "amarachieemezie@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2022-01-12T18:41:13.277Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-05-09T15:13:09.331Z",
                    "currentRole": "Other"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-02-22T06:33:14.493Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee98553e7ab6730c517",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a8a068bfdc0428e7d949",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee98553e7ab6730c517",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                            "name": "Daniel Daws",
                            "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                            "currentRole": "Founder"
                        },
                        "answer": "The Executive Assessment is not necessarily harder, so much as it is more tailored to executive-oriented MBAs",
                        "createdAt": "2022-01-21T20:10:44.296Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a8a068bfdc0428e7d947",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How hard is the Executive Assessment compared to GMAT?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-01-17T16:37:34.417Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eef28553e7ab6730c5b2",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a82868bfdc0428e7c929",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": true,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eef28553e7ab6730c5b2",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c411c594dcace72f5ae2",
                            "name": "Devin Marks",
                            "email": "devin.ridleymarks@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-04-16T02:36:55.760Z",
                            "currentRole": "President"
                        },
                        "answer": "Contractors first. Second. Third. Then hire.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-04-17T01:41:44.297Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a82868bfdc0428e7c927",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "How do you manage rightsizing within your organization?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c3ecc594dcace72f58f5",
                    "name": "Claire Beltmann",
                    "email": "cbeltmann@luc.edu",
                    "createdAt": "2020-10-20T20:34:37.140Z",
                    "currentRole": "Assistant Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-02-11T19:13:40.681Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "62b78a52f6ac59655ddd97d9",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "62bc6a29f6ac59655ddeecc3",
                        "isUpdated": true,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "62bc6969f6ac59655ddeeca6",
                        "answer": "Could it be that different investors are using different types evaluation criteria? It may come down to investors with differing interests scoring different properties with higher or lower importance. Maybe if you had a spreadsheet of feedback you've received you could even work out a ranking of what different types of investors consider most important.",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c421c594dcace72f5be4",
                            "name": "Steven J. Pietras",
                            "email": "spietras43@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-07-13T15:28:46.788Z",
                            "currentRole": "Manager",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-29T15:36:07.160Z"
                        },
                        "question": "62b78a52f6ac59655ddd97d9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-06-29T15:05:13.251Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "62bcee9ff6ac59655ddef8d8",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 1,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "62bcee0ff6ac59655ddef8c9",
                        "answer": "i think everyone will give you their advice if you ask it for and no one is actually right. as a founder the hardest part is to distinguish good advice from bad advice but ultimately remember its your call and you are typically closer to the problem. find investors that understand or have invested in similar problem spaces and believe in what you are doing ",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62b9c632f6ac59655dddbd5c",
                            "currentRole": "Co-Founder",
                            "email": "criojasp@nd.edu",
                            "name": "Cristina Riojas",
                            "createdAt": "2022-06-27T15:01:06.793Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-07-01T14:41:37.907Z"
                        },
                        "question": "62b78a52f6ac59655ddd97d9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-06-30T00:30:23.664Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844b22df651d77c17f7af1",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637dee25a00c393d8f8bb17d",
                        "answer": "Hiii",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6373a7eea5322d31357ff110",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer",
                            "email": "ym@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Ym",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-15T14:53:34.480Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:40.349Z"
                        },
                        "question": "62b78a52f6ac59655ddd97d9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:46:10.911Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "63844ba6df651d77c17f7bec",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "seenBy": [],
                        "sentTo": [
                            "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a"
                        ],
                        "deliveredTo": [],
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "637dee25a00c393d8f8bb17d",
                        "answer": "hiiiii",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6373a7eea5322d31357ff110",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer",
                            "email": "ym@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Ym",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-15T14:53:34.480Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:49:40.349Z"
                        },
                        "question": "62b78a52f6ac59655ddd97d9",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-28T05:48:22.502Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "I'm a founder seeking funding.  I am confused as to why I am receiving such different and conflicting feedback from investors? Has anyone else experienced this? ",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                    "name": "Saima Omar",
                    "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                    "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                    "currentRole": "Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-06-25T22:21:06.136Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 4
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eeda8553e7ab6730c442",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a84268bfdc0428e7ccb8",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eeda8553e7ab6730c442",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c41fc594dcace72f5bc1",
                            "name": "Kevin Reid",
                            "email": "kreid7@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-06-26T06:59:01.493Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "Once our country reaches a high level of vaccination active cases of COVID19 will most likely be limited to the conscientious objectors who refuse to vaccinate. When the return to the workplace by the majority of employees occurs one of the challenges we may face may well be remotivating the workforce to the same levels of productivity that we experienced pre-COVID. Naturally there will be some industries such as healthcare that will have been on full steam ahead mode throughout the pandemic so the challenge here will be to give them some form of opportunity to recharge and recover from the intense workload. Building resilience again after this will be an ongoing challenge. Vigilance is what we will need post-pandemic. We are facing a very challenging future with respect to the epidemiology of COVID19 in whatever variant it presents.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-06-26T07:16:03.545Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a84268bfdc0428e7ccb6",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "What challenges will leaders in organizations face in the post-pandemic workplace?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6220c416c594dcace72f5b31",
                    "name": "Todd Harrison",
                    "email": "todd.harrison@deltafaucet.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-04-30T11:58:30.420Z",
                    "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-04-30T12:35:46.448Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 1
            },
            {
                "_id": "6229eee48553e7ab6730c4d3",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a87768bfdc0428e7d45d",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee48553e7ab6730c4d3",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "62218f00c594dcace72f5c24",
                            "name": "Steven Pietras",
                            "email": "norgoth12@gmail.com",
                            "createdAt": "2021-08-07T15:35:10.381Z",
                            "currentRole": "Senior Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "I am not sure about tools, but if possible, have the employee list the specific ways in which they think racism is at play and discuss each point after thinking about it and conversing with the development team. The employee may or may not have valid critques and it is important to be honest with yourselves during this process. If you can show them that this has been considered and explain why the process occurs the way that it does, perhaps they will be understanding.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-11-29T17:46:50.217Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a87768bfdc0428e7d45b",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6231a87668bfdc0428e7d432",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "question": "6229eee48553e7ab6730c4d3",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6220c406c594dcace72f5a2a",
                            "name": "Saima Omar",
                            "email": "socontentmarketing@gmail.com",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-06-25T22:11:11.669Z",
                            "createdAt": "2021-03-09T15:30:46.259Z",
                            "currentRole": "Director"
                        },
                        "answer": "It is important to take this issue seriously as you have said. Firstly, when assessing candidates on promotions, you may have used a competency chart or compared the two candidates solely on their experience, expertise, competency and so forth. It might be a good idea to discuss the feedback in detail of how this candidate ranked against the other, their shortfalls, how they can improve and discuss how serious you are about helping them achieve their goal. A timeline of how you envision them progressing to the role they wanted should they wish to stay with your company. This shows that you not only used a set criteria that had nothing to do with race, to make the promotion decision, but you are activiely interested in mentoring the employee to reach their potential and their goal.",
                        "createdAt": "2021-11-28T02:15:20.863Z",
                        "roomId": "6231a87568bfdc0428e7d430",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "An angry employee who was passed over for a promotion said that our employee development culture is racist. However, I and my team feel that we picked the person most qualified for the job. Are there any useful tools for addressing this issue? I want to take the issue seriously, but don't know where to begin.",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "62218f07c594dcace72f5c75",
                    "name": "Daniel Daws",
                    "email": "danielwaynedaws@gmail.com",
                    "createdAt": "2021-10-06T17:12:39.069Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-07-05T18:46:32.223Z",
                    "currentRole": "Founder"
                },
                "createdAt": "2021-11-23T22:07:06.140Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "636ba7df7a3ce63a87b871b4",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "636ba7f67a3ce63a87b87234",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 1,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "636ba7f07a3ce63a87b87226",
                        "answer": "hello",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "636a78788152c428092ed35a",
                            "currentRole": "Manager",
                            "email": "yo@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Yo",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-08T15:40:40.132Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T05:44:24.701Z"
                        },
                        "question": "636ba7df7a3ce63a87b871b4",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-09T13:15:34.798Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "636ba8097a3ce63a87b872b3",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "636ba7f07a3ce63a87b87226",
                        "answer": "Hello",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6368acc678440371fa3f108b",
                            "currentRole": "Executive Vice President",
                            "email": "y1@yopmail.com",
                            "name": "Y1",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-07T06:59:18.546Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T09:03:47.274Z"
                        },
                        "question": "636ba7df7a3ce63a87b871b4",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-09T13:15:53.661Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "What are some of the greatest technological achievements? How do we make sure that technology serves us, and not the other way around? Can you name a country or culture that is using technology in an interesting or unique way right now? How does technology affect the economy?",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6368acc678440371fa3f108b",
                    "currentRole": "Executive Vice President",
                    "email": "y1@yopmail.com",
                    "name": "Y1",
                    "createdAt": "2022-11-07T06:59:18.546Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-11-28T09:03:47.274Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-11-09T13:15:11.318Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 2
            },
            {
                "_id": "6363d19855785a45832c9407",
                "Responsegivenbyheuser": [
                    {
                        "_id": "6363d74955785a45832c9a49",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6363d6c055785a45832c9a20",
                        "answer": "You need to share the scope and benefits with the students. They should know how it will add value in their life",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6363d45b55785a45832c9750",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer",
                            "email": "rozysharma09@gmail.com",
                            "name": "Rozy Sharma",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-03T14:46:51.749Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-03T14:46:51.750Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6363d19855785a45832c9407",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-03T14:59:21.556Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6363d9a755785a45832ca01a",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6363d6c055785a45832c9a20",
                        "answer": "Already did that but they are not interested. should I start it for free ",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6363cfee55785a45832c9320",
                            "currentRole": "Product Manager",
                            "email": "alan@johnbehrgroup.com",
                            "name": "Alan",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-03T14:27:58.277Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-03T15:01:57.172Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6363d19855785a45832c9407",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-03T15:09:27.485Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6363d9d655785a45832ca25c",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": 0,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6363d6c055785a45832c9a20",
                        "answer": "Any other way I can handle this",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6363cfee55785a45832c9320",
                            "currentRole": "Product Manager",
                            "email": "alan@johnbehrgroup.com",
                            "name": "Alan",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-03T14:27:58.277Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-03T15:01:57.172Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6363d19855785a45832c9407",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-03T15:10:14.436Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    },
                    {
                        "_id": "6363da5955785a45832ca42c",
                        "isUpdated": false,
                        "isAbuse": false,
                        "isStar": false,
                        "status": null,
                        "user_type": "user",
                        "roomId": "6363d6c055785a45832c9a20",
                        "answer": "Start for free and see how many people are interested ? ",
                        "createdBy": {
                            "_id": "6363d45b55785a45832c9750",
                            "currentRole": "Chief Executive Officer",
                            "email": "rozysharma09@gmail.com",
                            "name": "Rozy Sharma",
                            "createdAt": "2022-11-03T14:46:51.749Z",
                            "lastLogin": "2022-11-03T14:46:51.750Z"
                        },
                        "question": "6363d19855785a45832c9407",
                        "createdAt": "2022-11-03T15:12:25.946Z",
                        "__v": 0
                    }
                ],
                "question": "I am working as a cricket coach with a school and the management is in favour of starting an academy with school but the students are not interested. what should I persue discussion with Students regarding the same ",
                "Askedby": {
                    "_id": "6363cfee55785a45832c9320",
                    "currentRole": "Product Manager",
                    "email": "alan@johnbehrgroup.com",
                    "name": "Alan",
                    "createdAt": "2022-11-03T14:27:58.277Z",
                    "lastLogin": "2022-11-03T15:01:57.172Z"
                },
                "createdAt": "2022-11-03T14:35:04.781Z",
                "as": [],
                "ResponseCount": 4
            }
        ],
        "count": 226
    }
}